Chapter 577: Attention from Everywhere, Black Star Army

Godora paid close attention to the coverage. Nagakin had already reported Han Xiao's personal strength, so the focus of the upper echelons was on another problem. Han Xiao had already declared to the galaxy through the reporters that Planet Aquamarine was a part of Floating Dragon.

Despite Floating Dragon being a neutral organization with no regime, its influence was not to be underestimated.

With the brand of Floating Dragon labeled on them, even though Planet Aquamarine was in Godora's territory, it would be difficult for them to control or manage Planet Aquamarine. This planet would then become a special region within Godora's territory.

Floating Dragon's value had far exceeded the value of a low-grade planet like Planet Aquamarine. As long as there was no conflict between the two, Godora could only choose to close one eye.

Of course, compared to DarkStar, Planet Aquamarine was a tiny problem. After the news got out, Godora's official media team also came forward to join in the fun and spread the news. As long as they could dampen DarkStar's momentum, it would not matter who it was that defeated DarkStar.

As Jenny watched the news, her face turned dark, and she immediately contacted Ames.

Ames was currently roaming the galaxy, and Jenny's holographic figure appeared on her communicator.

"What's the matter?"

"Go and take a look at the news! Black Star is creating trouble again!" Jenny pressed a few buttons on her communicator and sent the news over.

After watching it for a while, Ames smiled calmly. "He's not too bad."

"That isn't the point! Before gaining my approval, he announced to the galaxy that Planet Aquamarine is a division of Floating Dragon!" Jenny looked as though she was about to go crazy.

"But I agreed." Ames blinked innocently.

Jenny had no choice but to force all her curses back down her throat.

"I took in two disciples recently, and they are both from Planet Aquamarine. Black Star will be bringing them to Floating Dragon Island soon, and you should look after them."

After saying that, Ames cut off the line.

"Argh! Black Star!"

The employees outside the room heard Jenny's enraged roar and all jumped out of their seats.

In some random place within the Shattered Star Ring where a beyond Grade A organization was located.

"Tanking the main cannon... he does have my style. Ames finally has a powerful officer."

In the darkness, a giant who was seven meters tall sat on his throne and watched the news with a look of deep thought.

"Floating Dragon has begun to expand, and Ames is finally interested in building her organization. Hmm, I should find some time to propose to her again. Maybe I will succeed."

The DarkStar mothership that had ambushed Planet Aquamarine was currently floating in space, and the three Calamity Grade Supers also saw the news.

"Bullsh*t! When did he beat us up‽" Degulish flew into a fit of rage. "It was obviously Black Star who was beaten to the point he couldn't fight back. These reporters really know how to bullsh*t!"

"The truth is, we weren't able to kill him," Terry said helplessly.

Ember snorted but did not comment. He was thinking about how he could get rid of Han Xiao.

"He must have a weakness. We have to quickly plant spies within his mercenary group. We will only be able to find his weaknesses by coming into close contact with him."

"Then, what should we do next?" Terry asked.

Degulish frowned and slowly said, "Black Star's ability was out of our expectations, and our mission has failed. The leader said that this isn't our fault as none of us knew how much strength Black Star is hiding. He ordered us to regroup with the main fleet and prepare for the next step of the plan."

"Next step of the plan?"

"I am not aware of the exact details, but since he is gathering all the motherships, it will definitely be a large mission," Degulish said.

DarkStar was still planning their next attack.

However, DarkStar did not know that Han Xiao had already snuck into their backyard.

All the hidden motherships were exposed under Risda's surveillance, but DarkStar was still in the dark.

With the news being spread throughout the entire Shattered Star Ring, Black Star's name was being discussed everywhere. His name spread far and wide, and Han Xiao received plenty of bonus Renown points.

DarkStar had finally paused for a moment after failing twice.

However, this was only the calm before the storm. The large storm that was being directed by Han Xiao was currently brewing.

Every now and then, Han Xiao would send the coordinates of the DarkStar motherships to the upper echelons of the War Bureau through Nagakin. Godora intended to destroy DarkStar in one fell swoop and secretly mobilized their forces without making any rash moves.

At the same time, Godora kept the mercenary groups on the payroll as insurance but did not reveal their exact plan to them. Godora only got Sky Ring, Purple Gold, Blades, and the other large mercenary groups to await their orders.

Han Xiao was still on Planet Aquamarine carrying out his plan to recruit the players. The plan was now at its most crucial phase.

By making use of this event, Han Xiao changed the name of his faction through the faction interface and Mercenary Alliance.

The [Black Star Mercenary Group] was renamed to...

[Black Star Army]!

Only large mercenary groups would dare have the word 'Army' in their name.

Because of the addition of a large number of players, Han Xiao's faction had more than ten thousand members. His faction was already at the right level, and the mercenary world probably would not have any complaints about it.

Regarding this decision, Han Xiao gave a speech to all the players and emphasized the fact that their faction was only able to change their name thanks to the players. He wanted to make the players feel as though they were contributing to the growth of the faction.

By changing their name because of such a reason, Han Xiao would be able to cultivate a stronger sense of belonging and team spirit among the players. The players would then feel as though Black Star Army was a faction that belonged to them.

At the same time, this was a signal to the players that they were about to leave Planet Aquamarine and start the next phase of their journey. This was so that the players would have some mental preparation.

The way the players saw it, a change of name in the faction meant that they were about to enter the galaxy!

Of course, all his plans would only work if there were sufficient benefits provided to the players. Han Xiao had to make sure to launch new products from time to time.

Through the exchange center in the galaxy, Han Xiao spent more than 100,000 Enas to purchase new Pugilist and Esper knowledge and placed them in the faction store. What shocked the players the most was that the new knowledge did not require money like in the past but experience!

At the same time, there were no Favorability requirements to fulfil.

With respect to this incident, Han Xiao made an explanation through Phillip.

"The Black Star Army will provide these two Advanced Knowledges 'free of charge' to groom and train the new mercenaries."

This action of his immediately drove the players mad with excitement!

Han Xiao sold his own Mechanic knowledge using the [Skill Impartation] method, but he sold the knowledge from the other two classes through the faction store. This meant that as long as players joined the Black Star Army, they would be able to learn those two Advanced Knowledges for 'free'!

This immediately became a beginner benefit for those in the faction. It was just like how the players who joined the Godoran faction would be able to acquire knowledge if they accumulated sufficient merit. It was just that Han Xiao had removed all those restrictions and allowed the players to spend experience points to learn the knowledge without spending any money.

The players were overjoyed and felt as though they had made a huge profit!

The players who had entered the galaxy in Version 1.0 shared the price of that Advanced Knowledge in the galaxy. If they did not join a faction, the Advanced Knowledge would cost them tens of thousands of Enas to purchase.

In comparison, the Black Star Army seemed to be the kindest of saints!

The way the players saw it, this was all due to their contribution. It was because of them that the faction could grow to such a size. It was because of them that the faction could change its name and provide such benefits. This was truly a faction that could grow!

Han Xiao intentionally made it so that only experience was required to learn the Advanced Knowledge. His target customers were the players of the other two classes, and his intention was to accumulate experience so that he could quickly hit level 140.

The Great Mechanic Han had over 10,000,000 Enas in his account, and the 100,000 that he had spent was peanuts in his eyes. In fact, he was even too lazy to collect a symbolic fee. Even if he only collected 1 Ena, the effect would have been grossly different from providing it for free.

Advanced Knowledge was a necessity, and the market was essentially all the Planet Aquamarine players of the two other classes!

After spending 100,000 Enas, if Han Xiao could not harvest a good amount of experience, he would be going against his conscience!

This was the only shop where they could purchase Advanced Knowledge at such a good price. None of the players hesitated in the slightest, and the experience points on Han Xiao's interface rapidly shot up.

300,000... 600,000... 1,000,000,000...

The effect of it being 'free' was truly frightening!

Looking at the explosion of his experience points, Han Xiao was in a great mood.

After this harvest of experience, apart from being able to reach level 140, it will probably last me a long while.

In just one day, the amount of experience accumulated was enough to bring Han Xiao up to level 140.

In order to get to Grade A, Han Xiao did not even bother repairing his Mechanic Army. This ambush had allowed him to understand that it was best to harvest the vegetables when they were ripe. If he had already been at the Calamity Grade when facing the encirclement of the three Calamity Grade Supers, it would not have been so dangerous for him.

Han Xiao then walked into the training room of his second base and locked the door.

Taking in a deep breath, Han Xiao opened the interface and channeled his experience into increasing his level.

I can finally reach the Calamity Grade and step into the ranks of the powerhouses!

Han Xiao was truly excited.

Chapter 579: It's Time

After checking the changes from entering the Calamity Grade, Han Xiao tidied up his clothes before walking out of the training room.

As he walked down the corridor of the base, he met Aroshia.

"Where are you going?"

"Back to my room." Aroshia was prepared to walk past Han Xiao but suddenly paused beside Han Xiao and began sniffing him with a strange look in her eyes.

"What's the matter? Do I smell good?" Han Xiao then looked down at his own body.

Aroshia shook her head, and a look of uncertainty could be seen on her usually calm face. When she walked past Han Xiao, she could sense something different about Han Xiao's aura, and she thought that her senses were wrong.

"What kind of change have you undergone?" Aroshia would never beat about the bush and went straight to the point.

"Oh? You have felt it? I achieved a breakthrough in my strength, and I am already at the Calamity Grade." Han Xiao did not bother hiding anything. His Officers would find out eventually anyway.

Aroshia nodded indifferently in response. To her, regardless of what Han Xiao did, she would never doubt him in the slightest. Besides, Han Xiao had just survived a huge battle, and it was extremely normal for him to achieve a breakthrough.

To NPCs like them without an interface, battling was indeed the best way to raise their strength.

Han Xiao suddenly thought about something and smiled.

"Don't be in a rush to leave. Let me show you a little trick."

As he said that, Han Xiao activated his [Chaos Entity - Release], and his entire body turned into a grayish fog.

Aroshia looked at the fog before her with her eyes wide open in shock. Such a domain like transformation was extremely similar to her energy body. As she stretched out her hands to touch the fog; her entire hand passed through the fog, and she could not feel anything. The grayish fog before her was no different from an ordinary fog.

Hum!

Aroshia transformed her own body into her energy form and entered the grayish fog. The glowing golden energy body was tangled together with the grayish fog, and she could feel a warm sensation that she would only feel when present in the energy furnace.

Upon thinking about charging, Aroshia subconsciously attempted to absorb energy from the grayish fog. However, the Chaos Body was maintained by Han Xiao's energy, and this energy was controlled by Han Xiao. Thus, it could not be absorbed by Aroshia.

Feeling Aroshia's action, Han Xiao released a small portion of his energy for Aroshia to absorb. Aroshia suddenly turned into a bright ball of light that began flickering. Absorbing the energy from the Chaos Body made her feel a great sense of comfort, and she could not even be bothered to maintain her human form. If not for the fact that she did not have vocal cords in her energy form, she would have let out a groan of satisfaction.

The energy of a Calamity Grade Super was far thicker, and it had the brand of Han Xiao's genes. Thus, it naturally felt extremely different from an energy furnace.

Energy was the HP of the Chaos Body, and with a small portion of his energy being absorbed, Han Xiao's HP decreased. Han Xiao was then surprised to realize that he could send a telepathic message with the Chaos Body and sent Aroshia a message. He asked her to channel some of her energy into the gray fog as well. Theoretically, the both of them should be able to exchange their energy.

A golden streak of energy was then transmitted into the gray fog, and the HP of his Chaos Body was filled up to the brim. Han Xiao was suddenly struck by a thought. Because the majority of his talents were locked up in his Chaos Body form, Aroshia was not only his 'battery' but was also a moving HP potion for him.

He then sent another thought to Aroshia, and Aroshia transformed into the Chaos Body form to merge together with the gray fog. The gray fog immediately shone with a golden tint, and the two of them were able to have a deeper connection, which increased the efficiency of their energy transfer. This was akin to Aroshia becoming one with the Chaos Body.

After experimenting for a moment, Han Xiao deactivated the Chaos Body and transformed back to his original body. Aroshia also separated from his body and cancelled her energy form.

"Is this your new ability?" Aroshia could not help but ask. For some reason, her beautiful face had a slightly red hue.

"Yeah, I have acquired Void abilities."

Han Xiao's expression was a little odd, and he felt as though he had just done something strange.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao disposed of all the strange thoughts in his head. He then tried to think back about what he had just felt. Because his Chaos Body was a domain type lifeform that also had energy as its lifeline, he had tried experimenting with Aroshia. In the end, things were as he had expected, and as long as they were connected and consciously willed it, they would be able to transmit energy to each other.

However, while Aroshia could take the initiative to absorb energy, the Chaos Body could not. The Chaos Body could only passively absorb energy from its surroundings. Aroshia's Esper ability had another defining feature. She could make use of energy in almost every form possible.

The talents of the Chaos Observer are special, and there should be many more ways to use it, Han Xiao thought to himself.

After entering the Calamity Grade, Han Xiao had many new abilities that he had to familiarize himself with.

He then casually threw an [Observer's Mark] onto Aroshia before parting ways.

Along the way, Han Xiao thought about Risda's request. He did not intend to go back on his word. When Risda completed his mission, he would aid Aroshia in regaining her memories.

In any case, Han Xiao could already more or less guess what the final mission requirement of [Reboot] would be. He just had to ensure that he did not need to face Manison from the [Mechanic Empire].

Over the next few days, the various officers of the Mercenary Group found out about Han Xiao stepping into the Calamity Grade. Compared to Aroshia's calmness, they were all shocked.

That was the Calamity Grade!

Before their captain reached the Calamity Grade, he could already tank the attacks from three Calamity Grade Supers. Now that he had joined the ranks of the Calamity Grade Supers, just how powerful would he be‽

The person who was most shocked was naturally Herlous. He had joined the Black Star Mercenary Group before Han Xiao had entered Grade B and had personally watched how Han Xiao caught up to him, exceeded him, and left him in the dust without any hope of catching up!

Han Xiao had gone from Grade C to Grade A in just a short few years‽

Herlous had only touched the boundary of Grade B+!

He had never heard of such a growth rate before! Just what did Han Xiao eat when growing up‽

Sylvia was the happiest. After living together with the mercenaries for the past few years, she treated the Black Star Army as her second home.

There was finally a Calamity Grade Super to prop up the Black Star Army, and Black Star was also her own teacher. Thus, she naturally felt it a great honor.

However, the officers of the Black Star Army had not seen Han Xiao much over the past few days as he had locked himself up in the machinery modification room.

Entering Grade A was the prerequisite to merging a few blueprints, and Han Xiao could upgrade his equipment again. He did not need to change the type of equipment that he equipped but could use more powerful equipment of the same type. Han Xiao had lost a large number of machines during the battle, and this was the best time to make up for the gap in his weapons.

The Void Dragon had already been destroyed, and the only thing left of it was the core material, Void Dragon Bone. Han Xiao merged a new blueprint that was of a higher grade and was prepared to construct a new and more powerful battle suit to keep up with his Calamity Grade strength.

There were three core materials to the new mechanical suit: Kyle Alloy, PR-909 Super Nano Polymer Fiber, and Refined Overga Metal. These were all military grade materials and were extremely pricey. Furthermore, the ones controlling these materials were civilizations of the Star Cluster Grade.

These three materials were considered strategic military resources being used for transactions between civilizations and could not be found on the market at all. As long as it appeared on the black market, it would be purchased anonymously within seconds. Just a kilogram of Kyle Alloy would be the same price as a small spaceship. It was a market with demand but no supply. Even if one had the money and wanted to purchase it, it was impossible to do so.

However, as the ruler of a galactic civilization, Godora would have some in stock that they had bought from Star Cluster grade civilizations.

When he was selling the Mutation Source, one of the conditions was for Godora to allow him to purchase these restricted materials.

However, while Godora did agree to his condition, they added one of their own. The amount of restricted materials that he could purchase annually was limited. Godora would not allow too much of those restricted materials to enter the outside world.

Taking out his communicator, Han Xiao wanted to contact Nagakin to purchase the materials. However, he never imagined that Nagakin would be the first to speak when the call connected.

"Black Star, it is time," Nagakin said in a solemn tone.

As Han Xiao heard that, he placed the matter of purchasing the materials aside and said with his eyes narrowed, "Is Godora ready?"

"The fleet has been deployed, and all the DarkStar motherships are within our grasp. The head will command an attack very soon. This is a confidential mission, and its code name is [Operation Hodellas]!"

This code name was a direct translation from an ancient Godoran language, which meant 'uprooting the enemy' and 'cutting the weeds at the root'.

Han Xiao's face was solemn. From the day he sold the intelligence to Godora, he knew that such a day would arrive. Godora was currently starting their retaliation against DarkStar, and this was all caused by him.

Such an event did not happen in his past life.

"Black Star, we need you," Nagakin said.

Hearing that, Han Xiao became slightly excited as he said with a teasing smile, "Heh, you must know that providing intelligence and personally joining the battle are two different things. Are you officially hiring me?"

"We will give you remuneration that will make you satisfied. It will be of the same level as the large sized mercenary groups like the Sky Ring Army."

Han Xiao intended to join the battle anyway and was only casually mentioning the matter of remuneration. However, he never imagined that Godora would be willing to pay him the same amount as the other large mercenary groups.

It seemed like Godora wanted to get rid of DarkStar at all costs.

After causing them so much trouble for so many years, Godora was already thoroughly enraged at DarkStar. As long as they had an outlet to vent their anger, their attack would be akin to the avalanche of a snowy mountain.

Without their ability to remain hidden, DarkStar had to suffer the rage of Godora without being prepared in the slightest.

It was finally time for both parties to resolve their many years of hatred and enmity.

This was also an opportunity for Han Xiao to complete the [Godora's Ally] mission and perhaps an important part of the [Bloodline] mission.

Hanging up the communicator, Han Xiao stroked his chin and called Herlous over.

"Ol' Her, we have a job to do. Gather all the mercenaries and prepare to set off."

"Including the new Inhumans?"

"Yes, everyone."

Han Xiao revealed a smile.

This intergalactic battle would be the opportunity for him to take the players into the galaxy! It did not seem too bad.

It was time to let the galaxy have a new understanding of the Black Star Army!

Chapter 580: Depart

Dusk approached.

The clouds seemed to have caught fire, painting the Sanctuary that was under reconstruction in a pale-yellow color. Above the base, a fleet of mercenary ships was quietly docked, causing those on the ground to constantly turn their heads up to glance at it, a sense of envy and respect appearing in their eyes.

What had happened in the past few months had completely subverted the world view of Planet Aquamarine's people. It was like a dream, where one would wake up the next morning feeling dazed as they recalled the happenings of that day. It would always take a while before they regained their senses.

The suspended spaceships resembled a banner, constantly reminding them that this planet had entered a new era. It was not about the exchange of power from an 'old era' to a 'new era' but rather a brand-new age as a result of the breaking down of barriers, truly connecting them to the interstellar regions.

In the eyes of Planet Aquamarine's inhabitants, the past few months had heralded an unparalleled change in the times, subverting all their old patterns and ideologies. However, in the eyes of those from the galaxy, it was just another indigenous planet that had been baptized with a new world view. For the Black Star Mercenaries, this was merely another mission.

In the eyes of the players, everything happening on Planet Aquamarine was just another storyline event.

The players were more concerned by when they would truly step foot into space.

All signs pointed to the Black Star Army being the faction that would guide them into space. Furthermore, it was a faction that showed promising growth and lots of benefits. Hundreds of thousands of players had already joined the Black Star Army. Players were still passing the assessment every day.

In the base's square, with Herlous' call, the players arrived one after another, resulting in a mass of bobbing heads.

When Han Xiao returned, he had taken out a mechanical throne for his speech. That had been used to showcase his power. He had floated in the middle of the square to allow all the players to be able to see him.

Now that they were leaving, in order to improve his image in the players' minds, he planned to give a speech to end the storyline on Planet Aquamarine. At the same time, he planned to give an opening about the new phase, to increase the expectations of the players. This, he felt, would make the whole process more complete.

As he thought, Han Xiao spoke.

"A few months ago, I returned to Planet Aquamarine to fulfill my promise, helping Planet Aquamarine overcome its disaster. Now, I've completed my promise; the disaster has been resolved, and the enemy has retreated. Today is the day I leave."

Now that the Mutation Disaster had been resolved by him, and the civilization of Planet Aquamarine had survived, he had saved hundreds of millions of living beings, ensuring their safety.

Compared to his past, this result was much better.

It was time for him to continue his journey in the galaxy, and the players in front of him would be the best warriors to do so.

Not out of his expectations, all the players began to get excited, their eyes glowing.

We can finally step into the interstellar region! We've been waiting for so long, to the point the flowers are already withering!

Looking over everyone present, Han Xiao continued.

"The Black Star Army will follow alongside me in leaving. In the past few months, tens of thousands of you have passed the assessment, becoming a part of my team. I'll join you in the battles to come, and we'll carve out a corner for ourselves in the galaxy!

"As for those that have yet to join, if you guys are willing, I've already set up a base on Planet Aquamarine. You can apply to join at any time you wish, and no matter your identity, as long as you can pass the test, the Black Star Army will welcome the strong. There will be spaceships on standby to welcome new recruits at all times that will bring you to our base in the galaxy, making you an official member."

The objective of his recruiting was not just to the players. Even normal civilians from Planet Aquamarine could participate. After all, there would always be people aspiring for a higher stage.

The hundreds of thousands of players in the faction revealed expressions of joy. Indeed, only by joining the Black Star Army would they be able to enter the galaxy. The selections were just to select the first batch of interstellar explorers. This was the greatest benefit of being in his faction, which was that they would be ahead!

The other players were a little depressed, but there was no way to go around it. Who told them not to be capable enough to win in the selection? But they did not need to feel too uncomfortable. While they did not obtain the chance to be the first batch to leave for the interstellar regions, Black Star had left behind a channel for further admissions. As long as they continuously took the assessment, they would have a chance to enter the second batch or even the third batch.

In addition, Planet Aquamarine now required a large amount of manpower for post-disaster reconstruction, and remaining meant that they would obtain lots of profits.

At present, joining Black Star would be the most cost-effective way to travel to the interstellar regions.

Furthermore, in the eyes of the majority of players, there were many hints showing that joining Black Star was akin to following a potential main storyline!

In other words, it was the prior requirement for them to open the storyline of interstellar exploration!

At this point, Han Xiao's words took a turn.

"The size of the Black Star Army has expanded many times over. We've received our first large-scale employment, which is to have us participate in a war. This will be the first battle after the expansion of our army, allowing the universe to see our strength."

As he spoke, he sent out a Faction Mission to the players through the interface. Tens of thousands of players received the notification simultaneously.

You have triggered Faction Mission [Black Star Army: The First Battle].

This is the first large-scale mission for the Black Star Army. There will be a war in the interstellar regions, and those who fight with the army would be awarded 500 Faction Favorability.

The rewards that he could hand out were limited, so Han Xiao only chose to issue a reward related to Favorability. However, this was only the first mission, and when he met with the Godoran troops, he would naturally get a formal war employment mission.

At that time, the players would also trigger sub-missions through him, receiving experience and monetary reward. That would be the true substantial benefit.

This was also the original intention of Han Xiao adopting the mercenary regiment model. As his own reward quota was not enough, he would borrow the tasks of the employer to supply his faction with resources. Basically, he was akin to a human resource intermediary or even a pimp.

Only the first batch of players would make it in time for the war.

"There's a battle the moment we enter the interstellar region. This is going to be fun!"

"What a unique coincidence."

The crowd could not help but burst into excitement, discussing fervently.

Han Xiao finally surveyed the entire area.

Bennett, standing by his side, expressed his gratitude to Han Xiao. He had decided to stay there to continue managing the Sanctuary.

As for Hila and Aurora, they had already decided to leave Planet Aquamarine. After this incident, Han Xiao would be sending them over to Floating Dragon Island for further studies. Thus, they would leave together. The two sisters did not have any luggage, just whatever was on themselves.

Emerald Grass had also decided to join Black Star to see the galaxy. However, she was different. She brought hundreds of boxes of her medicinal ingredients with her, with the group of prisoners from Bell of Death Island who had finished the training helping her carry them. They were almost totally covered by the boxes.

Han Xiao paused for a moment before saying aloud.

"Now, let us depart!"

The spaceships suspended above slowly lowered themselves, unfolding the gangway.

The tens of thousands of player mercenaries stepped onto the spaceships with boiling blood.

Almost all the clubs and professional players were within the first batch of players leaving. They secretly cheered to themselves. While you guys are still building sandcastles here on the planet, we are off to explore space!

The officers also boarded the BlackLight Stealth, with Han Xiao being the last on.

As the hatches closed, with the BlackLight Stealth at the head, the twenty or so mercenary spaceships took tens of thousands of players as they disappeared into space. The last rays of sunlight disappeared with the spaceships, signaling the end of dusk and the heralding of the night.

The people on the planet raised their heads, looking at the fleet until they disappeared from view.

"Black Star..."

The emotions of countless people were surging wildly.

It was as though they had witnessed a legendary departure.

...

Nagakin's spaceship had been waiting outside the atmosphere for a long time. They would take the Black Star Mercenary Group to join with the other mercenary groups, which would require a few days.

This was the first time that most of the players had entered the galaxy, and they were extremely excited. Through the interstellar communicators, they learned more about the structure of the galaxy. Because the spaceship was equipped with sufficient facilities, the players were able to familiarize themselves with everything, repeating the actions that Frenzied Sword and the others had done in the past.

However, on the forums, this event was sensational. The first batch of players to reach the interstellar regions raised a huge ruckus, and numerous foreign players came over to watch the news, curious and envious.

This group of players were a key part of Han Xiao's plans. By bringing players into the galaxy in advance, it would allow them to quickly develop their own forces, further enriching his own pockets. The Godoran war mission was an opportunity to allow the players to understand the mercenary industry and the forces that occupied the galaxy. At the same time, the ability of the Black Star Army would allow them to refresh their impression of him, improving his reputation.

The Black Star Army was no longer the small-scale mercenary group of the past but had been promoted into a large-scale legion. As long as their reputation spread, the missions would flow in ceaselessly.

This first battle was also good to allow the players to familiarize themselves with the playstyle of interstellar battles.

...

A few days passed, and the spaceships of the Black Star Army as well as Nagakin arrived at the meeting place. The combined fleet of the mercenary group was watching as they moved slowly through the universe.

Han Xiao's spaceship was ushered in, and he immediately received a communication request. The other party was the Sky Ring Army Commander, Gureja. The two of them had cooperated many times before, and their relationship was not too bad.

"Black Star, why are you here as well?" Gureja, complete with a beard that resembled steel bristles, asked in a surprised tone.

"Godora also hired me to take part in the war." Han Xiao laughed.

"Haha, I thought you only acted as a middleman. To think that you would come here personally. It seems like we'll be fighting side by side again."

Gureja let out a loud laugh. Their last mission on Planet Golden Gate had been a success because Han Xiao had helped in the dark. He remembered this favor.

Han Xiao shrugged in response. "Godora can afford the expense, so I'm here."

"That's right. You've gotten quite close to Godora recently. Do you know what this strategic operation is about?" Gureja asked.

Godora had prevented any information from leaking, only keeping the mercenary groups on standby. They did not disclose the fact that this was a complete offensive against DarkStar, so all the mercenaries there were in the dark.

"Since Godora did not tell you guys, I can't either. It's a secret."

"Ha, you indeed have close relations with them." Gureja did not press the issue, instead changing topics. "All of the captains are having a meeting on Sky Ring at the moment, assigning tasks. You've come at the right time."

"Hmm, then I'll head over now."

After hanging up the communicator, Han Xiao piloted the BlackLight Stealth to enter the array leading to the Sky Ring Army. Sky Ring was a flagship, built to resemble a mountain.

After docking the spaceships, Han Xiao led his officers to board Sky Ring. There were already mercenaries from the Sky Ring Army stationed at the entrance to greet them, taking them into the great hall.

The great hall was spacious, with a circular sofa placed in the middle. A dozen Army Commanders sat on the sofa, each occupying a position. Their respective officers would stay behind their factions' leader.

The moment Han Xiao walked into the great hall, everyone turned around.

Aurora pulled on the clothes of Hila, carefully whispering, "Sister, the life force of all these people is really huge."

The mercenaries present came from various star systems and star zones and were all outstanding in their own regions.

For example, the Sky Ring Army had Gureja and another Calamity Grade Super, whereas all the other commanders were at the Calamity Grade as well. Furthermore, those officers that were selected to come along with them were also all strong. This could be described as a gathering of the strong.

Hila's expression was grave. The gazes of those mercenaries gave her huge pressure, as though everyone present could easily deal with her.

However, at this point, a few of the army commanders smiled and passionately greeted them. The atmosphere calmed down.

"It's... it's Black Star!"

"We've not seen you for a while."

"Brother, come, sit beside me."

At least half of the commanders there had ties with Han Xiao or had worked with him before, so they were familiar with him.

There was a smile on Han Xiao's face as he replied to each and every one of them.

Situated in the midst of powerful allies, he felt more secure.

Herlous and the rest also began to greet the mercenaries whom they knew. The two sisters did not know anyone, so they did not speak a word.

Hila secretly scrutinized the group of mercenaries.

Are all these people Han Xiao's counterparts? They look formidable!

As Han Xiao walked toward the sofa, one of the commanders, code named 'Underworld Feather', shifted before patting the seat beside her, gesturing for him to take a seat.

Just as Han Xiao was about to sit, a commander who was short in stature opened his mouth, his tone harsh.

"Black Star, with just a small number of people in your mercenary group, you've come here to have fun?"

The laughter of everyone present suddenly halted.

Han Xiao paused for a moment before looking over. The speaker was foreign to him, and they had not worked together before. Most likely, he had been called over by another mercenary group.

Who was he?

True, his own expansion had happened not too long ago, so it had only just been filed with the Mercenary Alliance. News had not yet spread.

Han Xiao now understood.

That was to say, in the eyes of all those large mercenary groups, he was just a small-scale group with little over a hundred members.

Chapter 581: Refreshing Everyone's Understanding

Phillip's scan quickly located the origins of this person.

The person talking was an Army Commander called Justin. He was a Mage, and the Expeditionary Army that he led was a large mercenary group in one of the Star Systems within the Colton Star Cluster. He was a comrade who had been called there by the Purple Gold Army.

The top-notch mercenary groups within the Shattered Star Ring had their own circle, and Han Xiao had paid close attention to the various famous mercenary groups in the region. In the past, he did not have any dealings with the Expeditionary Army.

As Floating Dragon's Field Team, Black Star had gained a place within this circle because of the Dragon Emperor's fame. Justin had also heard about Black Star before and knew that despite the small size of the Black Star Mercenary Group, they were a special bunch.

While the other large mercenary groups were willing to network with Black Star due to Floating Dragon, he did not have such an interest. When roaming in the mercenary world, he had seen far too many things. So what if the Dragon Emperor was powerful? Justin felt that both of their jobs were completely different. He did not wish to provoke the Dragon Emperor but was too lazy to network with her.

To him, Han Xiao was no more than a fellow mercenary who he had heard of before. He did not have anything against Han Xiao but could not help but speak the truth and doubt the size of Black Star's Mercenary Group.

While Black Star had a large network, they were about to take part in a war, which carried a huge risk. As an experienced mercenary, Justin doubted that his comrade had the strength to fight alongside him.

If a third-rate mercenary was hired and caused the battle line to collapse, everyone would be affected.

The way Justin saw it, Black Star was no more than a third-rate mercenary who was there to join in the fun. All of them had to shoulder the burden of the war, but what kind of a burden could Black Star shoulder? Their remuneration was earned through placing their lives on the line, but Black Star would be able to earn his by slacking off at the back. Thus, Justin was not too pleased.

"Since we are going to participate in a war, every Army present has over a hundred battleships and a few ten thousand mercenaries invested into the battle," Justin said with a deep voice. "How many troops can you bring out?"

The other Army Commanders looked at Justin before looking at the standing Han Xiao and did not interrupt.

None of them present were aware that the battle in which they were about to participate was a result of Han Xiao's actions. With a lack of information, they naturally thought that Han Xiao was only making use of his network to earn a quick buck.

While they did not say anything, all of them felt this way.

"Army Commander Justin, your doubts are justified and understandable," Han Xiao replied with a calm expression. Everyone present had some kind of status, and it was not wrong for them to voice their doubts.

It was also the best opportunity for him to refresh the understanding that those Army Commanders had of the Black Star Army. Since they were about to fight together, he naturally had to display sufficient strength to put all of them at ease.

"All of your understanding of me is a little outdated. My Black Star Army has already expanded, and we are no longer the same as before. We now have more than ten thousand mercenaries, and they all have the strength of Grade C at least."

"More than ten thousand Supers‽"

Justin's eyes widened in shock, and the other Army Commanders were also dumbfounded.

Such a scale was something that even they found frightening.

Just a while ago, the Black Star Mercenary Group had only been a middle-sized mercenary group. How did they grow so rapidly?

Many of them doubted the validity of Han Xiao's words, and Han Xiao immediately got Phillip to pull up the registration file of the Black Star Army.

Justin did not say another thing. Black Star did indeed have the right to participate in this war with those numbers.

At this moment, Han Xiao's gaze swept past everyone present and said, "Everyone knows about the immortals under my charge, right?"

Everyone nodded. It was no secret that Black Star had a couple of immortal mercenaries under him.

Han Xiao smiled and added, "These new recruits are all immortals."

The entire room fell silent.

"They are all immortals‽" Gureja stood up abruptly and broke the silence.

All the other Army Commanders also snapped back into their senses.

All of them understood the significance of those words. This meant that the mercenaries would never be 'expended', and the Black Star Army would always maintain its size. Furthermore, they would be able to take on risky missions without the slightest bit of hesitation and would not need to worry about deaths or compensation!

This was like their dream team!

More than ten thousand low grade Supers would be enough to rank any Mercenary Group at the top. If those Supers were immortals, they could only imagine what kind of a stir this would create in the mercenary world.

They would be the best cannon fodder... no, partners!

Many of them could not help but think about Han Xiao's other identity.

The Black Star Army was also the Field Team of Floating Dragon!

These immortals would be the strength of Floating Dragon after their expansion!

Just when Justin was tongue tied, he heard Han Xiao's voice.

"Army Commander Justin, these are the forces that I have brought for the battle. Are you satisfied?" Han Xiao asked.

Justin's mouth cramped up and had nothing to say.

"Or do you doubt my personal strength? If you have any doubts, we can have a little spar." Han Xiao raised his brows. He was not angered by Justin doubting him, but since he wanted to display his strength, it was best for him to take on a harder stance.

Gureja coughed and resolved the situation. "Black Star single handedly fought off three Calamity Grade Supers recently and tanked a main cannon. While the news may have been exaggerated slightly, I believe that the majority is still the truth. I believe no one here will doubt your combat capability."

Justin then stood up with a solemn expression with his height only up to Han Xiao's waist. Raising his arm out toward the sofa, he invited Han Xiao to take a seat.

"I apologize for my doubts previously. Please take a seat."

Just when Han Xiao was about to take a seat, he interrupted Han Xiao's actions with his words. Now that he understood the strength of the Black Star Army, Justin naturally admitted his mistake and invited Han Xiao to take a seat.

The moment Justin took a step back, the other Army Commanders nodded in agreement, and the atmosphere became lively again.

Han Xiao sat beside Underworld Feather, and Herlous and his other officers sat behind him.

After he sat down, Underworld Feather handed him a bag of snacks.

"You want?"

"What is this?" Han Xiao looked into the bag, which was filled with a pile of black dried meat.

"Dried lizards. I made it myself," Underworld Feather said with her brows raised.

Han Xiao hesitated for a moment before picking up a piece and eating it. He then asked curiously, "What kind of lizards did you use to make this?"

"I once completed a mission to wipe out an entire lizard tribe." Underworld Feather picked up another piece and ate it merrily.

Han Xiao placed the second piece that he had just picked up back down.

She was truly too ferocious.

Underworld Feather was a female Dark Elf and had all the characteristics of one. Her chest and ass were well developed, and she had the beauty of an elf. Her physique was strong and healthy, and she looked like a lazy panther. She had inherited the cold blooded and blood thirsty nature of the Dark Elves. Despite looking tender and flirtatious, no one dared underestimate her. She was like a female dragon.

The Dark Underworld Army that she led had the background of a civilization, and her backing was a magic civilization led by elves belonging to the Colton Star Cluster.

In the universe, elves were also known as the long ears clan and had the ability to hear the sound of nature. They had many different species such as Child of the Forest, Tall Elf, Dark Elf, and so on. The elves were not considered common in the universe, but they were not especially rare either.

It was not too strange for a mercenary group that was half run by a civilization to exist. Because of the agreements between civilizations, any movement of a civilization's army was extremely sensitive. As such, it was much more convenient to grow a private army. Completing their mercenary missions was no more than a cover for their private and more sensitive missions in the dark.

Many civilizations would groom such an army in the dark, and there were many such examples within the top mercenary circle of the Shattered Star Ring. In fact, Han Xiao's Black Star Army was also Floating Dragon's Field Team in name.

The higher one climbed in the universe, the more complicated things would get. The universe was far too large, and no single organization or individual would be able to dominate it.

Gureja led the meeting ahead of their battle to allocate everyone's role clearly. Han Xiao kept quiet throughout the entire meeting and did not say a word.

"Black Star, what role are you going to take?" Someone asked.

Han Xiao thought for a while before saying, "I will take care of them if a melee fight breaks out."

He did not wish to participate in the battle between spaceships at all. He would have to repair the spaceships if they were damaged, and it would not be worth it. Furthermore, he only had twenty or so spaceships with him, and the spaceships were mainly used for transportation, not battle.

Since the players were not afraid of death, they would be the best choice to deal with the DarkStar warriors.

After a short discussion, the jobs of the various armies were decided, and the Army Commanders dispersed.

Han Xiao boarded the BlackLight Stealth and returned to his own fleet. Looking out of the window, his twenty or so spaceships were currently following the troops of the alliance.

The players had just entered the galaxy, and everything was still extremely fresh to them. However, Han Xiao understood that if they got rid of DarkStar now, many of the future storylines would disappear.

In his previous life, the players could only join Godora or DarkStar. After entering the galaxy, both parties would be in opposing factions. However, this was completely changed because of Han Xiao's presence. As such, this meant that all the players no longer had this Main Storyline.

The way Han Xiao saw it, while he did not want to give up the missions, getting rid of DarkStar was a must.

The storyline between DarkStar and Godora has been replaced by me. To the players, joining the Black Star Army has become their new Main Storyline. This is the best time to cultivate the player's sense of belonging. If I can borrow the strength of the players to expand, I will also be able to let them feel a sense of honor. It seems like I need a few big events to let the players feel a sense of accomplishment. This attack on DarkStar can be the beginning.

Han Xiao was extremely concerned about the players. The accumulation in Version 2.0 was extremely important, and it was akin to building a strong foundation.

The players formed the core of his plan in Version 2.0 because the next version refresh would only take place ten years later. While it was still a while before the end of Version 2.0, Han Xiao was used to making preparations early.

However, he had to first take care of the battle before him.

Opening his communicator, Han Xiao looked at the message sent by Risda.

DarkStar's troops were scattered around the different regions of the Garton Star System, and the largest cluster had gathered a total of six motherships as though they were planning another attack. The other motherships were roaming the galaxy independently.

The location of the six motherships would probably be the main battlefield for the mercenaries.

The war was about to begin.

At the same time on a DarkStar mothership, Degulish and the others were in a meeting again to discuss their next plan. This time, their leader had given the order for them to attack the Rainbow Prison.

Their previous two assaults had failed, and they were not able to increase Godora's losses or get rid of Black Star. Before they could find a way to get rid of Black Star, DarkStar had decided not to touch the calamity planets but attack the Rainbow Prison instead. They wanted to save their former comrades. There were even a few Calamity Grade Supers locked up in there.

DarkStar took action without any fear or wariness. With Godora being in the light and them in the dark, DarkStar was confident that their ambush work.

However, DarkStar did not know that they had already lost the advantage of being hidden, and their locations had been exposed by Han Xiao. A calamity capable of wiping DarkStar out was brewing silently, and they were completely unaware of that.

Just as Degulish and the others were planning their next mission, Ember suddenly frowned and pressed down on his chest.

For some odd reason, he had a bad premonition.

Chapter 582: The Counterattack Begins

In an empty area of the universe, not far away from the large army of the six DarkStar motherships, a huge Godoran fleet was hidden behind a barren planet. Various battleships were densely packed to form neat rows. This was one of the temporary formations created for Operation Hodellas.

On the screen of the command ship, the coordinates of all the motherships of DarkStar were marked in red on the star map. The six motherships were slowly moving toward the ambush area, and it was those enemy troops that were the objectives of the Godorans.

"Target is approaching ambush site. Estimated time of arrival is 11 hours and 25 minutes."

The fleet commander reported the situation to the upper echelons, and he was one of the members in the War Bureau who was aware of the identity of their target.

In order to prevent any leaks, every commander responsible for Operation Hodellas had been thoroughly screened. Only those that were absolutely loyal knew the target of their operation.

The fleet commander was also secretly excited at the thought of launching a counterattack against DarkStar. He was an old-fashioned, pureblood Godoran official with deep-rooted hostility toward DarkStar. He looked forward to removing this tumor every day.

This was an important operation, and to be selected as one of the commanders by the upper echelons was undoubtedly an honor. The sense of responsibility on his shoulders was also extremely heavy.

After completing his report to the upper echelons, the fleet commander then contacted the leaders of all the other formations to exchange information. Their strategy was to perform simultaneous strikes on all DarkStar units, so there was a need for communication.

After confirming the operation time, another commander raised a topic within the encrypted military communication channel.

"Do all of you know the source of intelligence for this operation? When I asked about the relationship with the party, I was actually told that it was labelled as a secret of the highest level."

"Highest level secret? Seems like the channels our superiors have for obtaining information are really mysterious."

In the eyes of those senior officers, Godora had already been warring with DarkStar for so many years to no avail. To suddenly obtain a set of coordinates for the DarkStar motherships, there was some strangeness to this whole situation, so they could not help but wonder about the source of this intelligence. However, no one could inquire about the specifics.

"I do have some information though. I heard that this counterattack was organized by Godora because they managed to buy some information from a mysterious person. Otherwise, the War Bureau would not have been able to stop DarkStar leading them by their nose."

"Mysterious person?"

"That person can actually monitor the coordinates of DarkStar. Haha. Could it be that there's a traitor among the upper echelons of DarkStar?"

Everyone shared their views, secretly curious about the mysterious person who provided the intelligence.

Who was this sacred person who single-handedly provoked such a huge war? They were the hero of Godora!

After ending their communications, the respective commanders began handing down their new orders.

"It's about time. Inform the mercenary fleets on standby. Tell them to cooperate with our attack.

...

During this standby period, there was little to do, but the players were not idle, often looking for the mercenaries to improve favorability, trying out new tasks, as well as discovering new and interesting gossip. They did not require Han Xiao to pay close attention to them.

Han Xiao took the chance to visit the different spaceships in the fleet, interacting with the players and continuing to harvest experience from them. He also looked for the various heads of the large mercenary groups to exchange pleasantries. The rest of his time was used to make machinery.

In such a manner, a few days passed, and Gureja called over all the commanders. The orders from Godora had been passed down, and it was finally time for them to start the mission.

The mercenary fleet sped up, arriving at the predetermined location for the ambush. The Black Star Army followed as well.

Returning to his BlackLight Stealth, Han Xiao accepted the private communication from Godora.

"Black Star, the operation is about to begin. We need you to control your Artificial Intelligence that has snuck in to create chaos for the enemy."

"Got it." Han Xiao nodded in response.

To have the whistleblower cause a ruckus within, that was a simple task.

"The remuneration for this employment has been notarized with the Mercenary Alliance and the official employment mission sent to the file of the Black Star Army."

Opening the Mercenary Group interface, the official employment of Godora had been authorized with the name Operation Hodellas.

A war employment was not a private transaction and needed to be recorded in the Mercenary Alliance. After it was completed, a large number of Credibility Points would then be added to raise the Credibility Rating of the Mercenary Group. Furthermore, the mission details would be added to their mission files.

This was also the first war-level employment for the Black Star Army.

The interface popped up a notification of the corresponding hire, with a total of 18,000,000 experience as well as 1500 Favorability for the Godoran Faction.

As the Army Commander, his remuneration was the highest, receiving 3.4 million Enas. In addition, the officers and mercenaries would be remunerated individually.

This was especially so for the players. Other than Black Star's mission of [Black Star Army: The First Battle], all of them also triggered the mission [Operation Hodellas - War Employment]. They all received substantial experience and monetary rewards, although they were a far cry from his own.

This was a war-level employment, so while the players only got to drink a bit of soup from the pot, the rewards were far beyond their current standards, which was extremely generous.

On the forums, the tens of thousands of players were in high spirits, posting to show off the many rewards of their first battle upon joining the Black Star Army. This piqued everyone's interest in the Black Star Army further.

This large-scale employment allowed players to understand that they shared common interests with their faction, thus helping them strengthen their sense of belonging. Han Xiao had led them to participate in the war for this purpose.

Because most players desired to take on a 'role', the various influences in the game allowed them to fulfill their dreams and fantasies. In order for the Black Star Army to become the faction akin to their 'first love', Han Xiao had to utilize plotlines, feelings, interests, and other means.

When Han Xiao first set up his faction, he had already made this plan.

...

In the vast universe, the mercenaries stayed by their ambush point. It would only take a short jump for them to reach their battlefield position. During this time, the enemy's actions were monitored through the coordinates on the star map, which were shared by Godora.

The formation of the Black Star Army was placed behind the rest, as they were not participating in the frontal attack of the DarkStar motherships.

Inside his BlackLight Stealth, Han Xiao watched the actions of DarkStar through the feedback provided by Risda.

His monitor was different. While others could only see the coordinates on the star map, he could see the internal conditions of the mothership. At this moment, the members of the DarkStar fleet were still unaware of their impending doom, conducting their businesses as usual.

Attacking Planet Aquamarine and giving me such huge losses... it's time for you to pay your debts.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

As time progressed, the six DarkStar motherships finally entered the ambush site.

They're here!

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

"Attack!" Gureja's command spread through the entire army in an instant.

The next instant, the joint mercenary fleet jumped simultaneously. The universe outside of their spaceships turned into flowing streams of light as they activated their hyperdrive.

In just a few seconds, the fleet had crossed a long distance, and the undefended DarkStar motherships appeared in front of their eyes.

On the other side, streams of light appeared as the Godoran fleet emerged. They attacked from both sides, instantly surrounding the DarkStar fleet.

The ambush sites for both were out of DarkStar's radar detection range, and they appeared at the same time, catching them off guard.

Without another word, Godora and the mercenaries began to open fire, and countless cannons and lasers bombarded the six DarkStar motherships. With such deliberate calculations, the troops in the mothership were immediately thrown into chaos.

Inside the mothership where Degulish was located, the lights turned red as they sounded the warning alarms.

The people on the ship were shocked, immediately rushing to their positions. The mothership was being rocked around from the explosions, causing people to fall from time to time.

"What's happening‽"

Degulish had an expression of anger as he called for the observation equipment. When he saw that the attackers were from Godora, he lost his composure immediately.

How could it be Godora‽

Did Godora plan to ambush us?

How could they know our location‽

The projection of their Head of Intelligence appeared on the screen, with a face of worry. "Degulish, we're being ambushed, and the enemy is well prepared. Not just our fleet, the other DarkStar motherships in the other Star Zones are also under attack! Godora has planned this for a long time. They've cracked our stealth equipment and grasped our movements!"

This was the first time that DarkStar had been attacked by Godora while in stealth mode!

This ability to go into stealth mode was DarkStar's biggest reliance. Now that it had failed, Degulish immediately realized the seriousness of their situation.

"Send orders to all fleets. Do not engage and seek opportunities to breakthrough. This is Godora's trap, and it is an important life or death situation. We cannot fight head on with them!"

Degulish issued the order.

There was no warning of Godora's attack, and the incident happened too quickly. The upper echelons of DarkStar had no time to react, and they did not even have time to think about how Godora had managed to grasp their whereabouts.

Right now, their top priority was to escape!

If Godora had come with a plan, DarkStar would not be able to stand up to the attack and could only escape.

However, the command was not sent out. A notification on the communication interface showed that the link had been cut off.

Not only Degulish, but the entire DarkStar motherships had their connection cut off from the outside world.

This was because Degulish was residing in the mothership that Risda was controlling.

Risda had totally cut off their connection to the outside world.

The whistleblower had begun his actions!

Chapter 583: The Ending Is Usually Decided Before the Battle Even Starts

The battle entered the climax as soon as it started.

Outside the porthole, the Godoran fleet, mercenary fleet, and DarkStar fleet blasted at each other. The light from the cannon fire brought multiple colors to this space in the universe, along with countless deaths.

Cannons shot through the armor plates of one spaceship after another, turning the people inside into ashes.

Since Degulish could not send out any orders, the DarkStar fleet lost command and unity, fighting for themselves. Only after quite some time did they start to unite into groups under the orders of other furious DarkStar superiors and tried to break through the situation.

Sadly, as the initial order did not arrive on time, so DarkStar lost their best chance to escape. The way they pushed forward under the heavy fire was like trying to move in mud.

"Looks like we don't even need to do anything."

Han Xiao shook his head as he looked at the situation of the battlefield.

With Godora and the mercenaries working together, the strength of their fleets completely outpowered the six DarkStar mothership fleets. It was highly likely that there would not even be a need to enter the melee battle stage; they could turn these DarkStar armies into wrecks floating in space with just nonstop cannon fire.

Black Star Army's mission was handling the melee battle, so they had no chance to showcase their abilities and could only stay back and wait.

DarkStar started to show signs of collapsing. Some of the DarkStar frigates became deserters, wanting to escape from the slow mothership. Unsurprisingly, they were turned into fireworks midway.

Han Xiao thought for a while. Doing nothing did not fit his goal of building a name for Black Star Army, so he decided to create an opportunity for himself.

"Risda, can you control the movement of that mothership?"

"Sure."

"Drive the mothership and carry out a short distance hyperdrive, crashing into the closest planet. I will convince Godorans to let you go."

As he was saying, Han Xiao contacted the War Bureau through a private channel.

"This is Black Star. I'm going to control a mothership to crash into the surface of a planet and carry out land battle. The deputy leader of DarkStar is on that mothership. This is a chance to capture him alive while simultaneously seizing a DarkStar mothership."

Degulish was also a mission target of [Godora's Ally], so capturing him alive and giving him to Godora would result in a reward just like killing him. Also, giving them a mothership also had a high reward.

Godora had come prepared. This war might be DarkStar's last struggle, so Han Xiao wanted to increase the mission rating as much as possible.

The War Bureau had been paying close attention to the battle. With how things turned out, the superiors had no reason to doubt Han Xiao. Besides, capturing Degulish alive and seizing a mothership was very useful. After some discussion, the superiors decided to try Han Xiao's plan. They were confident in controlling the situation, so they took the risk and quickly sent orders to the fleet commander.

This order made the fleet commander very confused. Nonetheless, he was used to obeying orders as a soldier, so he quickly did as he was told.

Risda controlled the DarkStar mothership and deviated from the fleet, slowing speeding up as the attacks targeted at it became scattered.

The other motherships, of course, did not receive such treatment. They faced heavier fire as they watched Risda's mothership slowly move away.

Before the passengers on this mothership knew what was going on, they entered hyperdrive and arrived at the nearest planet—the barren planet that the Godoran fleet had hidden behind previously.

Boom!

The mothership immediately crashed through the atmosphere and toward the ground, forming a crater as dust shot into the sky like a fountain.

The DarkStar members inside the mothership were thrown about from the impact.

Degulish was the only Calamity Grade Super on that mothership. With his body strength, he was not injured, but his face was filled with surprise.

As soon as the communication was cut off earlier, he had already started to be suspicious, and the fact that the mothership had moved on its own proved his suspicion. Clearly, the mothership was under the enemy's control.

No wonder their whereabouts had been exposed to the enemy—even their mothership belonged to them!

When did the enemy do that? Degulish was furious and shocked.

The intelligence of the mothership crashing into the planet surface reached the mercenary fleet, and Gureja quickly contacted Han Xiao.

"Black Star, it's your turn."

"On it." Han Xiao nodded.

The BlackLight Stealth turned around, followed by the rest of the Black Star fleet. They diverged from the alliance fleet and entered hyperdrive, arriving at the planet where the mothership had crashed in the blink of an eye.

All the DarkStar members including Degulish were trapped on the planet surface, and a ground war was a stage exceptionally suitable for the players.

"Touch down, deploy the mercenaries!" Han Xiao ordered. The spaceships slowly descended toward the planet's surface.

The players inside the spaceship were already waiting behind the hatch, ready to strike at any time.

There should be tens of thousands of DarkStar members inside a mothership, with quite a number of them being Grade B Supers. Of course, the strong ones would be dealt with by the officers; the players only needed to deal with the normal soldiers.

This time, Hila, who was standing beside Han Xiao, frowned and asked, "What about us?"

Han Xiao turned around, pondered for a moment, and said, "You guys can join the battle this time, too."

Hila and Aurora would not die so easily. Furthermore, they would eventually need to familiarize themselves with the feeling of a space battle, so they needed training. This was a rather safe chance to do so. Hence, Han Xiao did not plan to stop Hila.

Feeling Han Xiao's trust, Hila's brows loosened, and she nodded.

She did not like to always be protected and had always hoped to be of use.

The DarkStar soldiers on the surface guarded the mothership closely as the mercenary spaceships carrying the players surrounded them from all directions.

Whoosh!

Hatches opened one after another.

Players walked out of the spaceship, and hundreds of thousands of them surrounded the DarkStar warriors.

The BlackLight Stealth hovered in midair, and Han Xiao jumped down. He did not need the standard superhero landing. Mechanical Force surrounded his body and created a repulsion force when he was about to land on the ground. He hovered just less than twenty centimeters above the ground.

"Black Star! It's you again!"

Degulish clenched his teeth.

With a poker face, Han Xiao slowly said, "Last time, the three of you fought me together. Now, it's only you, and no one will come to save you no matter how loud you scream."

Now that he was Calamity Grade just like Degulish, their strength difference was tremendously reduced. There was only one ending for Degulish if they fought one on one—defeat!

A tint of nervousness flashed within Degulish's eyes. He indeed dreaded Han Xiao's tankiness, so he quickly thought of what he could do. However, the more he thought about it, the more hopeless he got. He could not think of any possibility in which he would be able to escape. The fleet could barely hold on; no one would come to help him.

His only advantage was that, although it was extremely difficult to kill Black Star, Black Star was just Grade B, so he might be able to stall for a very long time.

Hum!

Just as Degulish had this thought, electric sparks shot out from Han Xiao's body, and compressed orbs opened one after another. This was the first time that he had used his full power since he entered the Calamity Grade. Thick, dense energy splashed in all directions, showcasing the energy level that belonged to the Calamity Grade!

Noticing the energy rank, Degulish's face changed drastically.

"Yo—You've achieved the Calamity Grade‽"

When they fought not long ago, Black Star had been Grade B!

How could he improve so fast‽

Without saying another word, Degulish turned around, turned into a stream of light, and immediately escaped, disappearing into the horizon and leaving the DarkStar warriors behind.

Before Black Star was Calamity Grade, he had already been unkillable. Now that he was Calamity Grade, how was he supposed to fight him‽

"I'll chase him. You guys deal with DarkStar's army."

At this point, the new mechanical suit was not yet built. Han Xiao wore the backup mechanical suit, turned the thrusting module up to its full power, and dashed toward Degulish like a bolt of lightning, disappearing before everyone else's eyes.

Not long after, the deafening sound of fighting came from afar, and the ground trembled.

As if this was a signal, the battle erupted!

DarkStar warriors fiercely fought back against the hoard of players coming from all directions.

Boom!

Countless abilities and bullets covered the sky, bringing chaos to the battlefield.

Players fell onto the ground like wheat being harvested. After all, DarkStar members were galactic warriors; their average strength was much stronger.

However, as the battle continued, DarkStar warrior's faces changed as well. First, they were fiery, then tired, and after some time, they became numb. Finally, the DarkStar warriors noticed the fact that the players were immortal.

The enemies would not die, so no matter how many times they kill them, it was useless. Realizing this, the minds of the DarkStar warriors were instantly defeated.

From having the upper hand in the battle, the DarkStar warriors slowly began to get defeated. Tens of thousands of people could not hold the line of defense anymore; they were eaten up bit by bit. Not long after, the entire DarkStar army was drowned by the players.

Ember, whose Esper ability was extremely powerful against crowds, was not here, so the players had no nemesis.

The stronger DarkStar officers were held back and defeated by Herlous and others, and the rest of the DarkStar soldiers were no match for the players.

...

Sometime later, the chaotic battlefield gradually quietened down, only left with scattered screams of agony. The battle was ending, and the ground was covered in the corpses of DarkStar soldiers. The remaining DarkStar members surrendered and were tied up and thrown aside.

The players excitedly cleaned up the battlefield. The DarkStar warriors' equipment was everywhere. There were even players who fought for them once in a while. Herlous did not stop them. According to the rules of the mercenary industry, that equipment all belonged to the mercenaries.

"How's Han Xiao doing?"

Hila wiped off a bloodstain on her face and walked to Herlous.

She had taken part in the battle and had experienced the strength of regular galactic warriors first hand.

Tiny streams of red flew out from the tens of thousands of dead DarkStar warriors and were absorbed by Hila.

Living creatures that had recently died could provide energy to her. Hila could increase the strength of her Esper ability through large scale slaughters. In Han Xiao's previous life, she had slaughtered many races and used this method to increase her strength. Now that she was not that extreme, of course, she would not choose that method anymore.

"The captain could deal with three Grade As even before. There will definitely not be a problem."

Herlous was not worried at all. He took out the communicator and contacted Han Xiao.

"Captain, you done?"

"What a coincidence, I just finished up with the battle. Wait there, I'm on my way back."

...

Hanging up the communication, Han Xiao looked at Degulish, who was not far away.

Degulish was breathing heavily and in a very bad state. He had almost zero stamina left and was staring at Han Xiao.

The marks from their battle extended hundreds of miles. The ground was dented everywhere, covered in craters created by them. Some places had even become trenches.

Han Xiao had used his Calamity Grade strength without holding back, enjoying his destructive powers.

The aftermath of a full-on Calamity Grade battle could easily change the terrain.

Degulish could crack the surface with just a punch or a kick, but he could not penetrate Han Xiao at all.

Han Xiao was also Calamity Grade, so Degulish could not overwhelm him like he did when he attacked Planet Aquamarine. He could not defeat Han Xiao, nor could he run away. His situation was very frustrating. He would get battered if he did not fight back, but if he did fight back, he would unavoidably waste his energy without even being able to hurt Black Star.

High-intensity battles were highly draining. As his energy levels fell, his strength continuously diminished. Han Xiao's attacks brought dealt more and more injuries, and the vicious cycle repeated.

A battle of stamina was where Han Xiao excelled. Although the Mechanical Army had yet to recover and he had yet to update his own equipment, with his talents and rare abilities, he wore Degulish down steadily.

Degulish coughed, clenched his teeth, and started to activate the energy that he had only just recovered.

"Stop it, do you even have the strength to fight anymore?"

Han Xiao was speechless. Degulish was a Calamity Grade Pugilist after all. Even though his stamina was completely drained, he could recover it in a matter of seconds.

Seeing Degulish was still trying to regain energy, Han Xiao pondered and asked, "Do you know why your location was exposed?"

Degulish's face drastically changed. His movement became stiff, and his just recovered energy disappeared.

"Could it be..."

"Before you people attacked Planet Aquamarine, I had already invaded your mothership when you attacked Planet Golden Gate. The person that gave Godora intelligence and started this war was me."

Degulish's face turned black.

This time, the communicator rang again; it was a message from Gureja.

"Black Star, the battle here is almost finished. All the DarkStar motherships have been destroyed. Only a few DarkStar members escaped through the gaps created by the mothership in small spaceships. The Godorans are chasing them down. We still don't know if any of the DarkStar upper echelons are among them. We are preparing to fetch you. Are you done over there?"

"Yes, the mission is complete. Come over."

The war was a complete victory just as he expected. The intelligence provided by Risda was extremely detailed. Not only did they know DarkStar's location, they also knew the number of DarkStar troops. Plus, Godora had more than enough time to gather enough troops to attack them when they least expected it.

Godora controlled an entire Star System, and if they still could not achieve an overwhelming victory with such an enormous advantage, it would have been way too embarrassing.

Without their stealth advantage, DarkStar could not match a Star System Civilization that attacked them with all they had. If not for their stealth ability, DarkStar would have been destroyed a long time ago.

What Han Xiao had provided was what Godora needed most.

He could very well be considered the main reason that DarkStar had been destroyed.

Han Xiao did not mind that Degulish was just beside him. He ended the communication in front of him.

Degulish kneeled onto the floor with a plop and stopped resisting. He closed his eyes with agony and whimpered, "DarkStar is done for..."

Chapter 584: Escaped Fish

"DarkStar is done for..."

At the last moment, Degulish realized that it was the end for the warriors he led, and he had nowhere to run. He lost the will to fight and gave up resisting. His exhausted and enormous body fell to the floor, facing down.

Han Xiao did not have an easy time dealing with Degulish, and many of his adorable machines had been destroyed.

Since he did not have enough time to recover the machines that he had lost during the Planet Aquamarine battle, he was using the backup machinery that he built before, and Degulish had destroyed two-third of his stash.

Nonetheless, after this battle, Han Xiao had a very clear understanding of his own strength, so it was well worth it.

His current battle mode was rather impressive, and the synergy between his talents and abilities were quite perfect. For regular Grade A Supers, he was basically undefeated just with how strong his body was. After he recovered his Mechanical Army, he would even be on par with Calamity Grade Supers who were three to four thousand Energy Rank above him.

The strength differences between Calamity Grades were exceptionally large. Han Xiao had only just stepped into this territory, so there were still many who were a threat to him. Such as those above Level 200 who could overpower him. However, given how tanky he was, he would still be quite a pain to deal with.

Comparatively, opponents who used psychic attacks were a bigger threat to him. Psychic attacks were not included in the damage types that could be absorbed by [Intermediate Energy Absorption]; only attacks that landed on his physical body would be turned into energy. Psychic attacks could break his 'health-energy cycle'.

Some Mages would be quite difficult to deal with as well, such as those who excelled in Curse magic and abilities that could suppress life regeneration of sorts, also Espers that had psychic abilities like Hila.

There are countless abilities in the universe. I am far from the top of Grade A.

He was very self-aware of his strength, so there was no way he would get arrogant.

Seeing that Degulish did not have the will to fight anymore, Han Xiao said, "Anur had a stronger spine than you. I thought you would fight me to death."

Degulish clenched his teeth and said, "Black Star, don't get ahead of yourself. You've not won yet!"

He still had one final shred of hope—the DarkStar army had been annihilated, but the superiors were not all caught. The DarkStar leader had yet to return and was not in Garton Star System. This was his hope; as long as the leader was still alive, DarkStar was not completely obliterated.

Therefore, he had chosen to surrender. He wanted to keep himself alive and useful, even if it meant that he would be sent to Rainbow Prison, so that he could wait for his leader to come and save him, to give himself to the cause once again, rising for his leader.

"DarkStar's leader..."

The DarkStar leader was a very remarkable man. He had avoided this disaster out of luck. However, even if he wanted to start all over, he would have to keep an exceptionally low profile for a long time in order to escape from the Godorans. Hence, he would not be much of a problem any time soon.

Furthermore, Godora wanted to kill the DarkStar leader more than he did, so there was no point worrying about it.

...

Dragging Degulish along, Han Xiao returned to where the others were. Seeing the corpses that were piled up and scattered across the ground, he nodded with approval.

The players did very well; the effect that he wanted had been achieved.

Shortly after, the mercenaries and the Godorans landed together. The DarkStar captives were handed to the Godorans. Degulish was escorted onto the ship by two Calamity Grade Godoran government officials, heading to the dreamy life of free housing for the rest of his life in the marvelous cell of Rainbow Prison.

Risda completed his mission and returned to the BlackLight Stealth, pushing Phillip out.

This DarkStar mothership was handed to Godora as part of the deal that had been discussed with the Godoran War Bureau.

The notification of two missions in [Godora's Ally] being completed popped up on the interface.

[Deputy Leader - Degulish] complete.

You have received 24,200,000 Experience, 1500 Godoran Civilization Favorability, [Character Summon Card - Degulish]

[Seize Mothership] complete.

You have received 30,000,000 Experience and 1800 Godoran Civilization Favorability.

Other than that, [Operation Hodellas - War Hire] was shown to be completed as well, despite him not doing much. Nonetheless, after Han Xiao thought about it and realized that in order to even receive these benefits, he had to be qualified for it. After all, Godora would not hire just anyone for this. Furthermore, Risda had played a rather large part in it, so it was counted toward his contribution.

The initial reason that Godora hired him back then was to let him control the mothership; capturing Degulish and others was a pleasant surprise.

These three missions brought Han Xiao more than 70 million experience. Although it was not comparable to harvesting the players, it was still quite profitable.

Hence, despite the players' mission being the shrunk version, they still made quite a fortune.

The players were happy, and Han Xiao was happier.

Sadly, the players did not have the [Godora's Ally] mission and could not receive the other two rewards.

Shame.

With the boost of three continuous missions, Han Xiao's Godora Favorability rocketed past 6,000 and reached the highest relationship status—[Reverence].

It was well deserved. He had provided intelligence to Godora to counterattack, captured deputy leader Degulish alive, and seized a mothership. If he was a civil servant in Godora, he would have been promoted more than ten times. Hell, he might even have become a candidate for top positions in the War Bureau.

As Han Xiao was about to have a conversation with the Godora superiors, Gureja, Underworld Feather, Justin, and the other Army Commanders stared directly at Black Star Army that were cleaning up the battlefield.

Defeating tens of thousands of DarkStar warriors was an easy feat; their army could do it too. However, they would never have achieved the result that Black Star Army had!

Almost zero casualties!

Their speculations about Black Star Army had become a reality.

Those Army Commanders knew full well that as soon as word about this spread, Black Star Army's name in the mercenary world would shoot up into the skies, completely overturning their past image and officially becoming one of the top mercenary groups.

...

"Other than this seized one, all the other DarkStar motherships were destroyed. Very few escaped, and their identities are yet to be verified." In the communicator image, the War Bureau superior explained the situation.

"Is that so?" Han Xiao contemplated.

DarkStar did not have a fixed base—the motherships were their base. Now that these had been destroyed, it was basically the end for them. The 'DarkStar' organization was no more. What Han Xiao cared more about was if Ember was alive.

Ember's Esper ability was very destructive, and he had immense hatred for him. Plus, his brain was the most developed. If he escaped, there would be quite a problem.

Maybe he could use the Destiny's Child card to foresee Ember's whereabouts?

The Destiny's Child Character Summon Card only had two more uses left, and Han Xiao had yet to decide whether to use one of it here.

This time, the War Bureau superior said, "After some time, Godora will announce this victory to all of the Star System. Following your request, Serbia the Fifth will publicize your achievements personally, telling everyone that you're the hero of DarkStar's destruction and that you're a valued ally of Godora."

DarkStar had threatened the Garton Star System for many years, causing countless disasters. Now that they had finally been dealt with, Godora would certainly make an official announcement, streaming to all the channels in the entire Star System, listing DarkStar's sins and promoting their profound victory. That would boost the confidence of their people, making it known that DarkStar no longer existed, that they had saved the world, and so on.

Back then when Han Xiao sold his intelligence, one of the requirements was to publicize his contributions after the plan succeeded. This was to tremendously increase his fame.

For such an enormous feat, it was almost a definite that he would receive Star System level Legendary Points.

"By the way, you will be needed at the scene. Serbia the Fifth will personally give you the honors, and you will be a friend of Godora forever. After the ceremony ends, we will pay you the rest of the reward as discussed. Fifty medium battleships and one large main ship, the remaining fifteen million payment, and some Super Knowledges."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Finally, he was about to receive the remaining payment, but receiving the honors was unexpected.

Godora was very generous, so being honored by the leader of the nation was a huge honor. This was not his request but Godora's decision.

With some thought, Han Xiao roughly knew what Godora was thinking. Their appreciation was indeed sincere, as were his achievements, but a part of it was definitely because he was part of Floating Dragon. Thus, they wanted to improve their relationship with the Floating Dragon.

If Floating Dragon's Field Team Officer was Godora's honored hero, their relationship would be closer.

This had no negative impact on him, so of course, Han Xiao would not reject it.

"Before bringing the players to Base One to officially start their mercenary career, showing them a 'cut scene' of me being honored is very beneficial for my personal image. This will all increase my reputation. Marvelous!"

Han Xiao was very content.

When Han Xiao ended the communication, the battlefield had almost all been cleaned up. The Godoran fleet dragged the DarkStar mothership from the ground like pulling up a carrot. They then moved it outside the atmosphere and were planning to take it back.

On the galactical battlefield on the other side, there were also many Godoran spaceships cleaning up the wreckages of DarkStar fleets.

This was an overwhelming victory; joy was on the face of every Godoran soldier.

Not only Han Xiao, but all the mercenary groups were also invited to Godora's Mother Planet to attend the government ceremony not long after. Showing their faces was a free advertisement, so no one rejected the offer.

The Black Star Army and Alliance Fleet took off and headed toward Godora's Mother Planet together.

After just experiencing a war, all the players were excited. All kinds of screenshots and recordings were being posted to the forums.

Herlous was extremely excited. Han Xiao had promised to get rid of DarkStar, and he had always thought that there was little hope. He had stood behind Han Xiao and watched his every step. He had never thought this promise would be fulfilled in just a few years. At this point, Black Star's promise only had one outstanding condition—sending hundreds of thousands of Supers to deal with the problem on Planet Sunil. Even though DarkStar was destroyed, Black Star would definitely not go back on his word on this one. The highly risky bet that he placed on trusting an unknown mercenary back then had paid off!

Inside the BlackLight Stealth cockpit, Han Xiao did not pay attention to the players' actions as he would usually. After a long consideration, he had made a decision—he would foresee Ember's whereabouts. Although he might waste one use of the Character Summon Card, he wanted to be mentally prepared in case Ember was still alive.

You have used [Character Summon Card: Destiny's Child]

Usages: 4/5

The familiar fog covered his vision once again. Passing through the fog, a blurry image appeared before his eyes.

...

A mini DarkStar assault ship was speeding through the universe, escaping.

Ember was the only one on the ship.

Long before the ambush, he had felt uneasy and kept his alert up. When it happened, his reactions were the quickest. Realizing that there was no possibility of winning, he had abandoned the mothership, taking a small, fast assault ship. With a bit of luck and all his might, he had successfully escaped.

Hundreds of assault ships had tried to escape, but he was the only one that had succeeded. Ember had seen the mothership shattering into pieces under the barrage with his own eyes, and countless DarkStar warriors had turned to ash, floating in the cold universe.

DarkStar was finished, and Ember realized that.

Where should he go?

Piloting the spaceship, the dim light from the star map illuminated Ember's face. He was lost without purpose.

As a wanted man who had slaughtered tens of millions of Godorans, Godora would never give up chasing him.

It seemed like there was only one path ahead of him—leave Garton Star System, or even Colton Star Cluster, go to another Star Cluster in the Shattered Star Ring, hide his name, and start a new life.

Thinking about this, veins filled his eyes.

He did not want to escape anymore.

DarkStar still had him; it was not the end for DarkStar!

"I am destined to become Godora's nightmare. With slaughter, I will make them reflect on their traditions that are countless years behind. The bloodline belief they have is against the nature of reproduction. This twisted mindset is exactly what created us. After their confession, I will make them swallow the fruit of their thousands of years of the pureblood belief. DarkStar will build a new Godora above their ruins!

"Then, there will be no more pureblood; no one will feel superior for their blood. Discrimination will no longer exist; no one will be born lower than another!"

Those were the DarkStar leader's hopes for him when he was young, and he had always remembered them in his heart and made them his faith.

"Godora will definitely host a ceremony to announce to the entire Star System that they have defeated DarkStar and that the purebloods' reign is still strong..." Ember clenched his teeth. "When you people think that everything has ended and are celebrating your victory, I will tell the entire Star System that DarkStar has yet to disappear."

He decided to go to Godora's Mother Planet.

When Godora was holding their ceremony and was watched by the whole Star System, he would use his Esper ability and start a slaughter, destroying Godora's victory announcement.

However, Godora Mother Planet was very dangerous, so he had yet to figure out a way to get in. There would definitely be a lot of Calamity Grade Godoran government officials at the ceremony as guards, so him doing so might cost his life.

As Ember was having a thousand thoughts and was about to make a decision, his communicator suddenly rang. It was a communication request from the DarkStar leader.

That's right, the leader is still alive!

He came up with a better idea!

Ember's mind recovered, and he was overjoyed that he had found someone whom he could rely on.

Chapter 585: Mastermind

"Ember, are you the only one who escaped? What's the situation now?"

The projection of the DarkStar leader appeared. Not too long ago, he had received many emergency messages from the upper echelons of DarkStar and found out that all the DarkStar motherships were being ambushed by Godora.

If Godora was able to lock onto their coordinates through some unknown means, DarkStar would not have anything to rely on anymore, and the situation would definitely be grave. He had tried contacting the various upper echelons to find out the news of the battle, but many of their numbers did not even respond.

After waiting for a long time, the DarkStar leader finally managed to contact Ember and immediately asked about the situation.

"All the motherships have been destroyed, and only a small number of people managed to escape. Our fleet is already gone..." Ember described the situation honestly with his fists clenched tightly and his teeth clenched.

The DarkStar leader fell silent before letting out a long sigh.

Their organization did not have any territory to their name, and those motherships were DarkStar's moving bases. All their production, research, and training capabilities were concentrated within those motherships. Their many years of accumulation had been destroyed in a single battle. Their losses were incomparably heavy, and their foundations were completely destroyed.

Their entire organization no longer had any armed forces and was only left with the leader and a few escapees.

When the Mutation Disaster was resolved before the expected timing and they were forced to make a change in their plans, the entire plan was no longer within their grasp. Even if their plan was stopped midway, Godora would still be the loser, but now, Godora had actually managed to turn the tables around and launch an all-out attack to thoroughly destroy them.

As such, Godora's losses had not been suffered in vain, and they had become the outright winner.

Who would have thought that the Mutation Source plan would become the final plan of their organization?

After pausing for a while, the DarkStar leader asked, "What are your plans?"

Ember hesitated for a moment before saying that he wanted to unleash a massacre at the Godoran ceremony.

"Ridiculous." The DarkStar leader immediately rejected this plan. "With our fleet completely wiped out, we have to make further plans. Leave the Garton Star System first and meet up with me."

Does this mean that I have to escape?

"Alright then."

Ember was reluctant in his heart but could only swallow that feeling. He adjusted the course of his spaceship and set course to the nearest planet on the border of the Garton Star System.

As long as the leader is still around, we have a chance to rise up again.

...

In the Colton Star Cluster, in some Star System, the spaceship of the DarkStar leader was currently drifting in space.

After getting off the line with Ember, the DarkStar leader tapped on the spaceship's control panel in deep thought.

After pondering for a long time, he stood up and left the control room. He then came to another walkway that was made from an alloy. When he walked to a specific location of the walkway, he knocked a few times on the wall. The spot that he knocked on did not seem any different from the wall around it.

Ka-cha.

The alloy panel slid open and revealed a secret chamber. An odd-shaped communicator was located within it.

An ordinary Galactic Communicator had many different designs. They could be worn or the wrist or even shaped in the form of glasses. There were some that were extremely simple spherical designs, and others followed civilian wristwatch designs. However, the communicator in the secret chamber was an old-fashioned design from many years back that seemed bulky and unwieldy.

Upon activating the communicator, lines of complicated encryption could be seen on the screen. The DarkStar leader keyed in many different passwords and confirmed his DNA before he could turn on the communicator. However, it seemed as though all the functions of the communicator were blocked, and he could only dial a single number.

Di di di...

The time spent waiting for the transmission to go through seemed extremely long.

Du...

The screen of the communicator then turned black, and a hazy, mosaicked face appeared on the screen.

The other party remained silent, and the DarkStar leader was the first to speak.

"Godora destroyed my fleet, and all my subordinates are dead. Only Ember is confirmed to be alive."

The hazy figure on the screen moved, and a mechanical voice sounded from the communicator. "Got it."

"I need a sum of money to build a new fleet," the DarkStar leader said with a deep voice.

"This isn't the time. Since you have failed, lie low for a while. You haven't been caught yet, so Godora will be on guard against you. You cannot restore DarkStar to its former heights any time soon. If not, there will be a risk of exposing the source of your funds."

"How long will I have to wait for?"

"The day Godora forgets the name of DarkStar will be the day for you to make a comeback."

"I do not wish to continue waiting," the DarkStar leader said in a depressed tone. "I have already been under your control for a very long time. When will it end? All of you are extremely clear that I can only create destruction and cannot truly destroy Godora entirely. Just when will all of you be satisfied?"

"You will know when the time comes."

"Humph, you guys provided me with resources very willingly in the past. Now that my organization has almost been wiped out, you are starting to shrink back. Do you think that I have lost my value and wish to go back on our agreement‽" The DarkStar leader raised his voice slightly.

"Are you threatening us?" The hazy figure fell silent. "I think that you are getting your target wrong."

The face of the DarkStar leader changed slightly, and he said humbly with his head lowered, "My apologies, I spoke wrongly."

"We will evaluate whether or not the transaction has been completed. Do not rush us. Remember, you were the one who chose to make this agreement with us; we did not choose you," the hazy figure said. "Even without you, we can have a second DarkStar. At that time, the agreement will naturally be cancelled.

"So, you'd better watch your attitude...

"You'd better wait if we tell you to."

"I understand," the DarkStar leader said with a soft tone.

The hazy figure paused for a moment before saying, "In any case, this isn't the time for us to make an appearance. You should leave the Shattered Star Ring and rebuild your forces in other Star Fields."

The DarkStar leader nodded.

"Hmm... we can introduce you to another big shot in a different Star Field. If you can gain his aid, you may not need to lie low for too long. However, you have to prepare a sacrificial offering for him."

"Sacrificial offering?"

"A Super who has a sufficiently powerful Esper ability," the hazy figure said slowly. "You should understand what I mean, right?"

The DarkStar leader was startled.

He understood what a sacrificial offering meant. At the same time, he could also faintly guess the identity of that 'big shot'.

I heard that he is a crazy man who wants to form the 'Super High Risk Esper Ability Restriction Treaty'.

"There are some rumors that the Crimson Empire is dissatisfied with the peace treaty," the hazy figure said. "While they are located far away, if trouble really breaks out in the Crimson Empire, the Shattered Star Ring will be affected as well. That may be the best opportunity for you to stage a comeback and also a chance for us to complete our agreement. You will only be able to complete your side of the agreement if the situation is sufficiently chaotic."

The eyes of the DarkStar leader lit up. While this might only be an excuse from the other party to console him, he did indeed regain some confidence.

"Don't contact us again before you are prepared."

After cutting off the communication, the DarkStar leader closed the secret chamber and returned to his room. Every time he contacted the other party, he would feel a sense of pressure that came from the other party's strength, status, and authority.

I hope that they will fulfill their end of the deal...

The DarkStar leader shook his head. What he was doing was no different from making a deal with tigers.

However, even if he was worried, he could only choose to make a transaction with the other party. The DarkStar leader had stepped onto this path very early on. No one in DarkStar was aware about this matter. In his eyes, this was the only hope for the mixed bloods.

Many years ago, he had come to understand that it was no more than a pipe dream if he wanted to overthrow the rule of the purebloods and create a new Godora for the mixed bloods. While it seemed to be an extremely moving slogan, it was not a practical reality. The discrimination toward the mixed bloods would never disappear.

Regardless of the policies that the regime attempted to push forward, the long scales or tails of the mixed bloods were things that the purebloods just could not accept. Regardless of how good an upbringing they had, as long as the differences existed, the deep-rooted discrimination would never disappear. With the purebloods forming the middle and upper ranks of society, the outcome of this discrimination was not that simple.

The future of the mixed bloods was not in Godora.

If DarkStar was not the terror organization that it was but a kind organization that took in the mixed bloods to build an empire of mixed bloods...

He would only die a faster death.

Without a sufficiently powerful backer, they would not only have to face the Godoran army but also the alliance of different regimes.

Their only way out would be to gain support from an even higher place. Just DarkStar alone would not be enough to accomplish all that.

Right at that moment, these individuals had come up to him with an irresistible offer that gave him hope.

In the end, the leader of DarkStar had become a pawn for the other party to fight for another opportunity.

The DarkStar leader had once asked the other party why they chose him. The other party had said that just creating destruction and a systematic plan of destruction were two entirely different affairs. In most cases, only the latter was a threat. Thus, they had chosen DarkStar.

The initial goal of an organization would always initially be clear, but as time went on, their path slowly strayed from their original one. The focus of the DarkStar leader had already shifted to how they could create more destruction for Godora and incite hatred between the purebloods and mixed bloods. By pushing the mixed bloods to stand against Godora, it created disharmony within Godora and supplied him with fresh troops.

DarkStar had already become a blade in the hands of others. However, the entire organization apart from himself was unaware of this.

However, the DarkStar leader believed that this was the only path that would give him a chance of building a homeland for the mixed bloods. If he wanted to reap the rewards, he would have to first pay the price.

...

The mother planet of Godora was a gigantic planet. Even outside the atmosphere, traces of modifications could be seen. The more developed a civilization was, the greater the modification to their mother planet.

Spaceship after spaceship docked at the various ports of the planet, and the mercenaries all disembarked from their spaceships. The Black Star Army was mixed among the people with the players forming the largest group. The officers following behind Han Xiao looked around curiously as though they were tourists. The only thing that they were lacking was a tour guide at the front hoisting up a flag.

Han Xiao walked at the very front and was chatting away merrily with the other Army Commanders. All of them were invited to participate in the victory ceremony, and the officials of Godora were already waiting by the dock.

Chapter 586: Payment in Hand

Godora sent out one of their leaders, who said with respect, "I welcome all the Army Commanders on behalf of Godora to participate in this celebration ceremony. The ceremony is currently in preparation, and we will be in charge of all of your lodgings and needs during this period. Please feel free to inform us if you have any requests. Everyone, follow me. We have already arranged your lodgings."

The millions of mercenaries made a majestic appearance. If not for Godora being a Star System level civilization, they would not have been able to make proper arrangements for all the mercenaries easily.

They needed a few days to prepare the celebration ceremony, and the mercenaries could only wait for the ceremony to begin on the mother planet.

The ceremony was being held in the capital, and everyone's lodging was also arranged in the capital. All the Army Commanders stayed in the same place, but their subordinates were to stay in a separate location. Furthermore, only the Army Commanders were invited to participate in the ceremony, and their subordinates could only watch the live broadcast on screen.

The players who were scattered all around the capital definitely would not stay in their rooms obediently. Furthermore, Han Xiao did not intend on restricting their freedom. The players would not feel a sense of belonging to a faction that tried to restrict their movements. The only way to go was using benefits to entice them, which was what he had been doing.

The treatment of the players was like the other mercenaries. They were free to do whatever they wanted when there were no missions, as long as they did not break the law.

Besides, the only way to create a warm sense of belonging for the players was to expose them to the prices of the galaxy.

...

Han Xiao was split up from his Officers and followed the other Army Commanders to a government guest house. This guest house was used to host visitors and was not open to civilians.

Along the way, Han Xiao chatted with the different Army Commanders, and the few like Justin who were not in cooperation with the Black Star Army took the initiative to form an alliance with him.

Han Xiao enjoyed Godora's scenery as they travelled. The sky was a beautiful shade of dark blue, and the pedestrians who were making use of their flight devices stuck closely to the prescribed flying routes. They formed a long human bridge that extended up into the skies. Every building had a landing point at the top of the building, which made it look as though the crowd was being sucked in. This scenery was exactly like how he remembered it to be.

The luxurious government guest house was located on top of the mountain, and their guide led Han Xiao and the others to their rooms. Every room had identical designs, and they were two story rooms, with huge, full-length windows and a balcony. The view on the outside covered half the capital, and the air was extremely fresh.

When Han Xiao got into his own room, the guide left and did not disturb him further.

"This is truly luxurious."

Han Xiao looked around the place and opened up the fridge to take a look. The fridge was lined with all of Godora's specialties as well as many different kinds of drinks.

Having picked out a frozen piece of red meat, Han Xiao placed it into a simple reheating machine that looked like an oven. He then set the flavor to 'Godora's traditional taste' before turning the machine on.

After a short while, a plate of steaming hot diced meat was served. It was topped with thick golden gravy that looked like honey and gave out an irresistible aroma.

"I can finally save my taste buds, which crave nutritious and high energy food."

Han Xiao took a deep breath of the aroma, and his appetite was whetted. He then ate the diced meat as though he was snacking. The sweet, juicy meat bounced around in his teeth as though he was eating jelly.

Godora was a magical civilization, and its mother planet had once had countless magical beasts roaming the planet. Now, all those beasts were locked up in zoos for exhibition with a portion of them being turned into everyday delicacies. After all, beasts who had magic in their bodies usually had extremely fragrant meat.

Han Xiao grabbed a red fruit that looked like a baboon's ass and a light gold liquor that had not been opened yet. He then walked to the balcony and sat down in the deck chair, enjoying Godora's beautiful scenery while enjoying the fruit and wine in his hand.

In his past life, DarkStar had bothered Godora for a long time, but DarkStar had been destroyed much earlier in this life. The billions of lives that would have been harmed by DarkStar had been saved.

The greatest threat to him had already been wiped out, and Han Xiao no longer had an enemy to be wary of. A period of peace would follow this, and Han Xiao could finally develop his Black Star Army in peace. Before the release of the next version, there should not be much danger. Since the danger was already over, it should be alright for him to relax for a moment, right?

Not too long ago, Han Xiao had used the Destiny's Child Card to prophesize about Ember's situation. Ember was indeed still alive, but the outcome of the prophecy was actually Ember's death. Ordinarily speaking, the prophecy should have been about how Ember would bring him a bloody calamity in the future...

A prophecy could also fail, but it was a pity that he was not able to determine Ember's location and give chase.

While he was not able to personally get rid of Ember, it seemed like Ember would not have a good ending. Han Xiao was truly curious about what kind of dangers Ember would meet. The most likely scenario would be him being chased by Godora and being beaten to death. However, it was a pity that the prophecy had been too hazy, and Han Xiao could only make a wild guess.

"The DarkStar storyline has been changed by me, and all future events will no longer happen. The fate of these DarkStar members will also be different," Han Xiao mused to himself.

From Version 1.0, the main boss of the Garton Star System had been DarkStar. Now that DarkStar was no more, there would not be another enemy capable of threatening him in the Garton Star System any time soon. Together with the fact that he had a good relationship with Godora, his main camp would be more or less safe.

Thus, Han Xiao was in a pleasant mood and felt that the sun was warm and the flowers red.

"I have been in the galaxy for a few years now..."

As he sipped his wine, Han Xiao could not help but reminisce about his experiences in the galaxy.

He had set up the Black Star Mercenary Group and completed missions all around. He had become a subordinate of the Dragon Emperor and made use of her as a backer to build ties with the various organizations. He had begun his accumulation since Version 1.0 and returned to Planet Aquamarine after Version 2.0 was launched. He had carried out his plan to recruit players and initiated deeper cooperation with Godora. He had resolved the Mutation Disaster and caused the destruction of DarkStar...

Now, he had finally accumulated enough strength to stand his ground in the galaxy.

"The next step will be my uprising."

Han Xiao swallowed a large mouthful of wine as many ideas sprouted out in his head.

...

After a short rest, an upper echelon of the War Bureau arrived at the guest house and invited all the Army Commanders for a meeting.

Han Xiao also received the notice and made sure that his hair was done nicely before walking to the conference room while singing. He saw Underworld Feather and Gureja the moment he entered the conference room.

He then sat down and made some idle chatter with the two of them. Gureja liked to touch his own thighs when talking, and Underworld Feather liked to eat nonstop. After talking for a short while, the other Army Commanders also arrived.

When everyone was present, a Godoran dressed in old-fashioned attire walked into the room. He was an upper echelon of the War Bureau, and Han Xiao had talked to him through the communicator before.

The War Bureau upper echelon then began his speech about how he was grateful to everyone present before moving onto the things that they should take note of during the ceremony. The majority of the upper echelons of Godora would appear during the ceremony, including the current highest leader, Serbia the Fifth. The ceremony was an official event, and there were many rules that needed to be followed.

The ten or so Army Commanders seated in the room were all local tyrants of their respective regions. However, this was also their first time attending an official galactic civilization ceremony. Despite their strength and unbridled nature, they did not dare do as they pleased in such an official event.

The meeting ended very quickly, and the various Army Commanders stood up to take their leave.

Right at that moment, the upper echelon of the War Bureau called out to Han Xiao.

"Black Star, follow me. Serbia the Fifth invites you to meet him."

Pa!

All the Army Commanders froze on the spot and looked back at Han Xiao in shock.

The highest leader of Godora was the leader of a Star System level civilization and was a true big figure. His status and influence were not something that they could match. They would only be able to encounter Serbia the Fifth during the actual ceremony!

However, such a figure was about to meet Black Star in private‽

We are all Army Commanders here. Why are you the only one getting special treatment?

Han Xiao's brows were raised, and he did not think that this was anything strange. Nodding, he said, "Alright, let's go."

The Army Commanders looked at their departing backs before looking at each other with puzzled looks.

There was definitely something behind this!

Godora had not made an official announcement, and the Army Commanders did not know that Han Xiao was their true key to victory. The merit that he rendered was on a completely different level from theirs.

...

After taking a long and winding path, they entered the core building of the regime. They then went through many different security checks before finally arriving at the office of the highest leader.

Serbia the Fifth took the initiative to stand up and extended his hand. "Black Star, how is your rest?"

"Pretty good." Han Xiao shook his hand, and the two of them began exchanging pleasantries.

The three of them then had a casual conversation for a while before finally broaching the main topic.

"Black Star, your intelligence helped us to wipe DarkStar out." Serbia The Fifth did not display a lofty attitude and spoke with a solemn expression. "I thank you on behalf of the Godoran citizens. Godora will always remember what you have done."

"As a citizen of the Garton Star System, this is something that I should do. It is just a small matter," Han Xiao said humbly.

"Your award ceremony would be grander, and we are going to award you with the 'Golden Gal Badge'. This is Godora's highest honor, and only thirty-two badges have been given out to date."

"I am truly overwhelmed," Han Xiao replied.

"This is something you deserve. We have already prepared the conditions that you have requested."

The moment Serbia The Fifth completed his sentence, the War Bureau upper echelon beside him took out his communicator and flashed the image of two different spaceships.

"Fifty Violent Falcon grade battleships that have the ability to attack and defend. One Fortress grade flagship that is made from a powerful alloy. These fifty-one battleships are brand new, and they are currently being stored in the army's warehouse. They can be handed over to you at any time."

According to his request, those battleships were in their base form and not special Godoran variations.

Together with this batch of battleships, his fleet now had about seventy battleships.

Han Xiao looked through the data of the spaceships and nodded in satisfaction. Godora did not go back on their word and try to toy with him. Those two spaceships were truly decent. Especially the Fortress grade flagship, which had a selling price of over 10,000,000 Enas and cost price of a few million. Of all the different spaceships, flagships and motherships were the most expensive kind.

Just these fifty-one battleships would be a hefty price.

After confirming that there was no problem with the spaceships, the War Bureau upper echelon continued.

"15,000,000 Enas have been deposited into your account. Please take a look."

A bank transfer message had indeed appeared on his communicator. After taking a glance, Han Xiao needed to exercise all his willpower to ensure that his face did not break out in a wide smile.

Together with the 3,400,000 Enas from being hired in the war, Han Xiao now had over 28,000,000 Enas in his account!

He was truly a wealthy tycoon!

"As for the Super knowledge that you have requested, we can provide five. This is the list."

As Han Xiao took a glance, the Super knowledge that a civilization had was indeed more complete than the black market. There were even some that could not be found on the black market. Now that they were being placed before him for him to choose, it saved him a great deal of time. However, the highest-grade knowledge on the list was only a High-End Knowledge.

Without any hesitation, Han Xiao immediately chose to learn the Mechanic High-End Knowledge that he had not learned.

_____________________

Armed Branch: [High-End Material Technology]. Core Mechanic knowledge to research materials with high resistance. The most obvious result would be an increase in Armor for all machines.

Energy Branch: [Super Nanometer Force]. Strengthens the basic attributes of all armor and machines. When used in tandem with [Super Nanotechnology], high grade memory alloys that have the ability to automatically restore Armor can be researched. If the blueprint for Nano Robots is learned, machines may even have the ability to transform!

Energy Branch: [High Energy Weapon Control]. When used together with [High Class Energy Control], many different powerful weapons can be created.

Control Branch: [Interstellar Navigation Technology]. Prerequisite knowledge to building a spaceship.

Control Branch: [Advanced Applications for Quantum Entanglement]. Greatly increase the transmission range of energy and messages. Increases the range and efficiency for virtual intrusion.

_____________________

The upper echelon immediately brought up the data from the knowledge bank and sent it to Han Xiao's communicator.

Han Xiao suppressed the urge to throw in his Potential Points immediately.

The benefits from the trade had basically been obtained by him, and the only thing left would be for Godora to announce his contributions at the ceremony and increase his Renown.

It could be said that this was truly a happy ending for their cooperation.

After a short conversation, Han Xiao stood up to take his leave. Right at that moment, an idea suddenly came to him, and Han Xiao threw an [Observer's Mark] on Serbia the Fifth.

The highest leader of Godora would come into contact with top secret information every day, and he could obtain some unexpected intelligence from spying on Serbia the Fifth.

It definitely was not because he wanted to spy on the lifestyle of the highest leader!

...

The next day, Han Xiao rented out a machinery modification room.

Since he was currently on the mother planet of Godora, the time taken for shipping would be negligible. He immediately bought the core materials required for his new mechanical suit.

Despite Godora only charging him the cost price of those three materials, he spent more than 100,000 Enas.

At the same time, of the five new knowledges that he acquired from Godora, [High-End Material Technology], [Super Nanometer Force], and [Advanced Applications for Quantum Entanglement] were raised to the max level, which cost him a total of fifty-one Potential Points.

Han Xiao could finally feel a lack of Potential Points. The moment he started to level up his knowledge, his Potential Points would also be expended rapidly.

Han Xiao made use of his new knowledge to complete his mechanical suit blueprint and also increased the blueprint up to level ten. This was to ensure that he could create the most perfect mechanical suit.

This time, Han Xiao was prepared to create a mechanical suit that could keep up with his new Grade A strength!

Chapter 587: Berserk Ape

In the machinery modification room...

"The core module is complete. Running an automatic scan... Automatic scan complete. Everything is in working order. Assembling the periphery modules..."

Ten or so mechanical arms quickly assembled the various parts of the mechanical suit, and a holographic screen displayed the various stats of the mechanical suit.

Phillip played the role of an assistant throughout the entire assembly process and used his superior processing speed to oversee the entire process. He detected all the microscopic defects within the various parts so that Han Xiao could make continuous adjustments and ensure perfection to raise the grade of the product.

Above the purple grade was the pink rare grade. The higher the quality of a machine, the more difficult it was to increase its grade. However, a problem that could be solved by money was not a problem at all.

Han Xiao spent more than 100,000 Enas on the core materials, and he had even made use of the pink grade void dragon bone in the mechanical suit. With so many rare materials being used, it was extremely simple to increase the grade of the final product. When comparing two different equipment of the same level, the difference between the pink and purple grade was not small at all.

Now that he was in the Calamity Grade, he had abundant Mechanical Force, and his Machinery Affinity was also raised. Together with the aid of all his talents and skills, Han Xiao's construction efficiency was increased a great deal. Even if he was constructing a high-grade mechanical suit, it did not take him too much time.

Whoosh!

The mechanical arms quickly assembled the remaining modules of the mechanical suit, and after the assembly was complete, the mechanical arm sprayed out a chilly gas that had the ability to cool down and combine the modules. This was the final step.

The white cool gas dissipated in all directions, and a black and gold mechanical suit was displayed before Han Xiao.

Han Xiao then pressed his finger on the chest portion of the mechanical suit and released a trace of Mechanical Force to activate the suit.

Suddenly, waves seemed to have appeared on the surface of the mechanical suit, and countless black Nano Robots sprung to action. The various modules of the thin mechanical suit began to surface, and the mechanical suit bulged out as though it had put on a great deal of muscle.

Han Xiao made use of the [Super Nanometer Force] on the new mechanical suit, and there were many nano machines in the mechanical suit that had the properties of a memory alloy. The information of the various weapon modules were programmed into these nano machines, and these nano machines could transform into different weapons at any time. While the design of the mechanical suit seemed simple, it was actually filled with weapons all over and had many different functions.

Apart from that, these nano machines had the ability to self-repair, produce energy, and many other functions.

"This mechanical suit is much more powerful than Void Dragon and is the most powerful mechanical suit that I have created to date..."

Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at the attributes of the mechanical suit.

[Berserk Ape]

Type: Nano Transforming Mechanical Suit

Grade: Pink

Requirements: Lv.135, Mechanic Class, >10,000 Energy

Basic Attributes:

- Armor: 86,000/86,000

- Defense: 580

- Power Level: 3,400

- Energy: 27,500

- Height: 1.96m

- Weight: 260 Pounds

Control Method: Middle Grade Artificial Intelligence assistance + Nerves Connection (+10% to all attributes)

Power Source: Mini Concentrated Nuclear Reactor - Self Charge. Recovers Energy at 480/min. Energy conversion rate from user: 40:90

Stationary Mode Energy Usage: 45/min

Combat Mode Energy Usage: 110/min

Core Power Capacity: 2,375/2,700

Skeleton Module: PR-909 Super Nano Polymer Fiber (Dark Purple) + Nanoparticle Array. Largely increases the attributes of the mechanical suit.

+125 STR, +131 DEX, Power Usage: 350.

Nanoparticles can be activated to provide additional attributes. Energy cost: 50/min, all attributes +45%.

Armor Plating Module: Kyle Alloy (Dark Purple) + Void Dragon bone (Pink) + Refined Overga Metal (Purple).

Weapon Module: Transforming Nanoparticle weapons. [Expand/Collapse]. Power Usage: 725

Thrusters Module: Anti-Gravity Electromagnetic Engine + Elementary Grade Galactic Thrusters. Power Usage: 500

Shield Module: Super Tough Electromagnetic Shield. Provides 18,000 shield durability, 150 defense. Energy cost: 150/min. Recovers 600 shield durability/s. Shield can only be used again after 8s if it breaks. Power Usage: 300.

...

Additional Ability: Nanoparticle Repair. Nanoparticles have the ability to repair independently. Energy cost: 200/min, 5% Armor repaired/min. The effects will be multiplied if out of battle.

Additional Ability: Berserk Throw. With the boost from the Concentrated Nuclear Reactor and Nanoparticles, +80 STR during the throw. Throws the target away, and damage is broken down into parts.

Damage calculation is determined by total STR. Point of throw will be first damage taken, and point of contact with the ground will be the last. Every time the target collides into an object along the way, a new round of damage will be taken. The collision damage will be calculated by the size and hardness of the object. If the collision object is a living being, the living being will also suffer collision damage.

Energy cost: 60

Cooldown: 15s

Additional Ability: Power Detonation. 1,000 Energy would be immediately used up and channeled into the next attack.

If the attack is a long ranged one, +320% – 360% power, AOE effect and sustained damage, +300% shooting range.

If the attack is a close-ranged one, +650% – 700% damage, power detonation damage and sputtering damage. 65% chance of critical damage. Able to inflict status effects like knock up, knock back, suppression, and dizziness.

Cooldown: 90s

Special Ability: Nano Transformation, three different forms

Giant Ape Form: Transform into a heavy armor form between 4m to 8m tall. A portion of the weapons will be unusable. In this form, +150 STR, -100 DEX, +130 Defense, +20,000 Armor, close range attacks have an additional 16% vibration damage. +20% Damage from [Berserk Throw].

Shuttle Form: Transform into a space shuttle. Unable to use any close ranged attacks. Speed is largely increased in this form and capable of flying in space.

Berserk Overload Form: Energy core will enter an overload state. Energy cost: 2,000/min. -25% Armor, +180% damage to all weapons, +30% to all attributes, -40% cooldown for [Power Detonation] and [Berserk Throw].

Remark: It would be suicide for a weak Super to put this suit on.

Compared to his previous mechanical suits, the greatest difference would be the different class of the suit. In the past, the snake and dragon series belonged to the 'Light Battle Mechanical Suit' class, but the Berserk Ape belonged to the 'Nano Transforming Mechanical Suit' class. It had the ability to transform and did not need additional components to be mounted.

In fact, many of the transforming mechanical suits were of the ape series. Could it be that the origins of this suit were the Saiyan ape?

The new mechanical suit was extremely powerful, and it met Han Xiao's expectations. His mechanical suit was finally stronger than his own body, and its damage was also powerful. Furthermore, with the intergalactic engine that he had built into it, it was akin to a one-man spaceship. He would be able to attack battleships in an intergalactic battle. It was an extremely useful function.

Compressing the Berserk Ape into a compressed orb, Han Xiao hung it around his neck. He could not help but feel his hands turn itchy, and he was looking forward to finding someone to spar with.

However, his own Officers would only be bullied by him one-sidedly, and it would not be too convenient for him to find the other Army Commanders or Godora.

"The ceremony is about to begin, so I'd better not create any trouble. There will be chances in the future."

Han Xiao temporarily suppressed that urge. The new mechanical suit was only a part of his plan to upgrade his equipment. There were still various new weapons and machines that he needed to construct. When he built up his new Mechanical Army again, his combat capabilities would then reach the peak.

...

The date of the ceremony was finally decided.

Before the ceremony, Godora revealed the news of DarkStar being destroyed, and the entire Star System was shaken.

DarkStar was infamous in the Shattered Star Ring, and it had actually been destroyed! This was truly earth-shattering news!

Numerous galactic residents were completely dumbfounded. After so many years of no progress in eradicating DarkStar, Godora was actually able to get rid of DarkStar in such a secretive and thorough manner. This was truly too sudden.

Many organizations had still been guessing what kind of a storm DarkStar would kick up next and were shocked by the news.

Godora only revealed a simple report of the process and would only announce the entire process in detail during the ceremony. It was akin to a media press conference. As such, all the citizens of the Shattered Star Ring focused their attention on Godora's ceremony.

The galactic reporters were like sharks who smelled blood and all swarmed toward the mother planet of Godora, anxiously waiting for the beginning of the ceremony.

The galactic media agencies came to an agreement with Godora and would broadcast the entire ceremony.

As the date of the ceremony drew near, countless galactic residents became even more eager for the ceremony to begin. They truly wanted to know exactly how Godora destroyed DarkStar!

In the midst of anticipation and eagerness, the day of the ceremony finally arrived.

Chapter 588: Award Ceremony

Boom!

The guard of honor squad opened fire toward the sky, and ceremonial fireworks burst open.

In the capital of the Godoran mother planet, the plaza in the center of the city was filled with splendor.

This was the most prominent landmark of the capital. The plaza was large and grand with the statues of various historical figures in the center of the plaza. Those statues were enchanted with magic to make the statues glow with a golden light. Many large scale Godoran events would be held in this plaza.

At that moment, the sky above the plaza was a no-fly zone, with many Godoran patrols making the rounds. On the ground, the center of the plaza was cordoned off, and only those who were granted access could enter. A large platform was situated at the center of the plaza with seats being placed on the platform. These were the seats for the upper echelons of Godora. At that moment, the various leaders were there yet, and their seats were still empty.

Below the platform were rows of neatly arranged seats that were there for the various members of society invited to participate in the ceremony. At that moment, the seats were already filled up.

Outside the plaza, golden-skinned individuals were packed like sardines as they watched the ceremony from afar. In truth, they did not need to be present physically to watch the ceremony as Godora would project the entire ceremony into the sky. A holographic screen was currently floating in the sky of the capital, and they only needed to raise their heads to be able to watch it.

Everyone in the streets and alleys of the capital stopped and looked up at the screen as they waited for the ceremony to begin.

"The screen in the sky looks like a gigantic theatre. This effect is truly stunning."

Many of the players also went onto the streets, and this sight was truly a fresh one for them.

Over the past few days, all the players had been freely exploring the capital, and they could experience a new culture of a different race. This fresh experience was like tasty candy for them all.

Apart from the prices of goods being frighteningly high, everything else was extremely interesting to them.

The players who had followed Han Xiao into space in the previous version were used to the various sights in the galaxy. Frenzied Sword and the others could not help but describe the significance of being brought to Godora's mother planet to others. According to their experience, their Black Star Army being on the mother planet was significant.

Maple Moon made a conjecture. "I think that a new Storyline may be waiting for us here. Think about it, the Mutation Disaster has just ended, and the organization behind it has also been wiped out. The players are starting to enter the galaxy on a large scale, and I think that there will be a new goal for us."

Frenzied Sword shook his head and said, "No. I think that the Black Star Army itself is a Main Storyline Mission. Don't forget that we accepted many different missions previously and went to many different planets with different races. Every planet had their own storyline, so the next Main Storyline Mission should be an exploration one. With the Black Star Army as the guide, we will be able to encounter more planets and races to allow the players to get used to the galaxy."

"Makes sense. If the Black Star Army is the next Main Storyline Mission of Version 2.0, then the significance of this ceremony is to create an impactful beginning."

"This is the smell of wonderful material!" Bun-Hit-Dog's eyes lit up.

A military aircraft stopped outside the guest house, and this was the vehicle that was going to take all the Army Commanders to the ceremony.

Everyone got onto the aircraft, and Han Xiao picked a random spot to sit in.

"It is finally time for the ceremony to begin."

None of the Army Commanders were too excited about the ceremony. They had personally participated in the war and were extremely clear about what had happened. The ceremony would just be for Godora to announce the process of how they ambushed all of DarkStar's motherships and defeated DarkStar in one fell swoop.

This would definitely result in people questioning how Godora locked onto DarkStar's location. However, this had come from one of Godora's top secret sources, and it was impossible for them to reveal it.

All the Army Commanders understood this, so the ceremony did not interest them greatly. All of them only intended to make use of the ceremony to spread the fame of their Army.

All of them chatted casually, and while they had intentionally restrained their aura, the pilot who was in the same aircraft as ten or so Calamity Grade Supers had a pale complexion with his entire back covered in sweat.

Although he had known that this was an aircraft full of bigshots in advance, it was still frightening!

Underworld Feather sat beside the pilot and asked in a gentle tone, "Are you afraid?"

The pilot gulped hard and stammered, "No... not at all."

"Don't be nervous, eat something." Underworld Feather took out some suspicious looking dried meat and fed it to the pilot with a friendly look.

The pilot gritted his teeth and ate the piece of dried meat and was surprised to find out that it was actually pretty tasty. He thus asked curiously, "What kind of meat is this?"

Just when Underworld Feather was about to reply, Han Xiao interrupted helplessly. "Don't ask if you don't want to puke."

Over the past few days, he had come to understand Underworld Feather's personality.

She would pretend to share her snacks warmly but intentionally fed people strange items so as to satisfy her sadistic urges. This little lass was still extremely good at feigning innocence.

"Tsk." Underworld Feather turned around.

Han Xiao and the others arrived at the ceremony grounds and sat in their seats. Their arrival immediately resulted in a huge wave of commotion from the galactic reporters.

"They seem to be the captains of the various large-sized mercenary groups, right?"

"That's right. They are all famous mercenaries. They should have joined the war as well."

Below the platform, the reporters chatted among themselves.

After a short while, a couple of aircrafts flew over from the direction of the government buildings. The leaders of Godora were finally there, and they all got into their seats.

Serbia the Fifth was the last to appear, and the moment he made his appearance, the entire crowd burst into loud cheers with the citizens watching from afar also cheering at the top of their lungs.

Han Xiao casually glanced at the VIP seats below the platform. Apart from the reporters, those in the VIP seats were the various leaders of the Godoran planets. Almost all of them were purebloods, and even the few mixed bloods were not too different in appearance.

Serbia the Fifth raised his hand, and the entire crowd became silent. He then began his speech, which was projected far and wide by the magical loudspeaker.

This was the official beginning of the ceremony, and it was broadcast live.

The ceremony would naturally begin with some usual pleasantries like thanking the citizens of the various planets for their contribution, emphasizing on the efforts of the government, and so on.

After a long speech, the Godorans were still sat up straight as they listened with seriousness. However, Han Xiao did not have the same patriotism as the Godorans and almost fell asleep from that long speech. At this moment, Serbia the Fifth finally changed the topic and got to the main point.

"I have something important to announce. DarkStar was a terrorist organization that made use of discrimination as an excuse to create chaos and destruction. For years, DarkStar committed many atrocities, and their hands were covered with blood! We will never be afraid of any provocation and have always done our best to stop DarkStar. Thirteen days ago, we finally made a huge breakthrough and wiped DarkStar out!"

Boom!

Despite Godora releasing a simple report of the matter before this, the Godoran citizens still could not hold in their excitement upon hearing it from Serbia the Fifth personally. The Godoran citizens burst out with excitement upon hearing the news.

The cheers were deafening to the point one could not help but feel one's body shake.

Right at that moment in the VIP location of the platform, Underworld Feather looked at Han Xiao and softly said, "Can you hear me?"

Han Xiao turned around and replied, "Yes I can. What's the matter?"

"I am just making sure that you aren't deaf," Underworld Feather said expressionlessly.

Han Xiao's mouth cramped up. Underworld Feather then ignored the cameras around her and took out a bag of melon seeds to munch on. She even shot out the shells of the melon seeds onto his back like a machine gun. Han Xiao's mouth could not help but cramp up even more.

The Dark Elves truly are a petty bunch...

After cheering for a long time, the Godorans gradually quieted down. The reporters knew that it was time for Godora to announce the process of the raid. They all became extremely attentive and focused their attention on Serbia the Fifth. Their pens were gripped tightly in their hands, and they were prepared to write down everything that he said.

"This time, we received help from a key individual and locked onto the location of DarkStar, thus allowing us to deal with the DarkStar fleet in one fell swoop..."

Serbia the Fifth described the battle slowly. The content of his speech was as the mercenaries had expected. He briefly narrated what had happened and emphasized greatly on their victory.

All the Godorans listened carefully, and the reporters jotted down the details in their notebooks. When this speech was broadcast across the Shattered Star Ring, many galactic residents were extremely curious about this 'key individual' that Serbia the Fifth talked about.

This 'key individual' should probably be their intelligence source!

After Serbia the Fifth finished his speech, he indicated that he would take questions. The hands of the galactic reporters all shot up extremely quickly.

One of the reporters was then chosen, and he said, "Your Majesty, I would like to ask if the identity of this key individual can be revealed."

Upon hearing that, viewers across the Star System all rolled their eyes. While they were also interested in the source of the intelligence, this was obviously top secret, and Godora definitely would not be willing to reveal it.

At that moment, Serbia the Fifth smiled and suddenly changed topics. "In truth, there is another major event planned for the ceremony. I will be performing an award ceremony for an individual to award him with the Golden Gal Badge!"

Golden Gal Badge‽

The Godorans and the majority of the reporters present were completely dumbfounded. Their minds blanked out from this piece of news.

Compared to those from other Star Systems, who were puzzled by this announcement, they understood the significance of the Golden Gal Badge.

The Golden Gal Badge was the badge of highest honor in Godora, and it had only been given out a total of thirty-two times. This was despite the millions of years of Godora's history! This badge was extremely rare!

Only those who made a significant contribution—such as world-renowned scientists, triumphant generals, or wise and peerless rulers—would be able to receive this badge. All the recipients of the badge could be called heroes.

Furthermore, at least half of the recipients had only received the badge after they passed away.

It had been an extremely long time since the badge was last given out. Who would have thought that someone would receive the badge of utmost honor again that day?

This was truly earth-shattering news!

All the reporters regained their cool, and their faces were flushed red from excitement.

Serbia the Fifth turned and looked at the VIP area, and many heads turned to follow his vision.

Han Xiao's mouth twitched, and he had no choice but to stand up. In the face of Serbia the Fifth's friendly gaze, he gritted his teeth and walked over.

It was not because he was nervous.

But because his back was still covered with the shells of melon seeds...

"Let me introduce to all of you the recipient of the Golden Gal Badge, Black Star!"

All of a sudden, everyone took a deep breath.

Everyone was stunned!

All the Army Commanders were completely dumbfounded, and Underworld Feather was shocked to the point her jaw dropped.

The players that were watching the live broadcast were dumbfounded.

The Black Star Army Officers who were playing cards while they watched the broadcast were also dumbfounded, with many of them dropping the cards in their hands.

In fact, there were many Godoran officials who had not been made aware of this matter who also revealed looks of shock.

This was the Golden Gal Badge! This was the first time that it was to be awarded to an outsider who was not a Godoran!

Chapter 589: Recorded in History

"How come Black Star is able to obtain the Golden Gal Badge‽"

At this moment, countless galactic residents were shocked, their faces full of doubts.

The intelligence that Han Xiao had provided had not been disclosed yet. Furthermore, many people still remembered Han Xiao's identity as well as his deeds. If the medal was issued to an unknown character, most people would only have felt that the person was mysterious and be curious about them. However, giving the medal to someone who had already formed an impression in their hearts instead resulted in a great amount of shock for the community!

Pairs of dumbfounded eyes stared at Han Xiao, only to see him walk to stand side by side with the leader of Godora, Serbia the Fifth.

Serbia the Fifth changed to a solemn tone as he proclaimed, "Black Star is the key person who provided the coordinates of the DarkStar motherships. He is the biggest contributor to the elimination of DarkStar! His boldness and caution allowed him to infiltrate and crack the stealth system of DarkStar, foiling their survival efforts and allowing us to monitor their movements. Without him, we would not have been able to obtain victory!"

Black Star was the linchpin that provided the intelligence‽

Hearing this news, everyone present came to their senses.

The skepticism in the Godorans' eyes was immediately replaced by surprise, admiration, gratitude, and even reverence.

The various Army Commanders suddenly burst out into conversation. It was no wonder Black Star was favored by Godora. Everything could be explained now.

It turned out, this war employment of theirs was actually a deal facilitated by Black Star himself! Their armies were just the party enjoying the benefits!

Justin blushed, feeling that he had become a laughingstock.

That time, he had asked Black Star if he was worthy. Most likely, he would be mocked till he could not show his face.

On the other side, the various reporters froze for a moment, realizing the key issue here.

DarkStar was ephemeral, coming and going like ghosts, but Black Star was actually able to track their coordinates. In truth, he was the root cause of DarkStar's demise!

He single-handedly supported the war! He rewrote the power structure of the Garton Star System!

Rather than saying that Godora had borrowed the intelligence of Black Star to defeat DarkStar, it could even be seen as Black Star borrowing the knife that was Godora to kill the villains who destroyed his hometown, DarkStar!

Such a character... how scary!

Many of them were struck by inspiration. The reporters were in a frenzy, burying their heads and scribbling hastily.

Han Xiao accepted the stares as he stood on the stage. The camera broadcast his handsome face onto the virtual screens of every Godoran family.

The impact caused by this news further propelled the reaction that the residents had toward Han Xiao repelling the DarkStar elites a while ago. The effect could only be described as sensational. Han Xiao's appearance and deeds had been imprinted on the hearts of the countless viewers, and they could not forget him even if they wanted to.

It was a pity that the award ceremony did not arrange for him to give a speech, or else he would have been able to utilize his skills. Right now, he could only be a mascot to receive praise on stage.

The ceremony of awarding the title had a grand and formal process. After going through the ceremony, Serbia the Fifth received a golden medal from the attendant beside him. The medal had an image of God Gal carved on it.

He personally awarded the medal, pinning it solemnly on Han Xiao's chest.

"I represent Godora in thanking you for your contribution."

Han Xiao suddenly had the impression that he was an Olympic champion being bestowed the gold medal. He reached out to touch the Golden Gal Badge and had an urge to bring it up to bite on it, to check if it was real gold.

After receiving the highest honor of Godora, he could not just remain passive. In theory, it was time for him to state a phrase of thanks to Godora. However, Han Xiao thought about it before stretching out his hand and giving a firm handshake to Serbia the Fifth before putting on a 'sincere' smile on his face.

"It was a great cooperation. Our Black Star Army will accept all legal employment, and we operate with integrity. Please, do not hesitate to choose the Black Star Army, and you can rest assured... oh, and I hope that the friendship between us will continue."

In Han Xiao's mind, the bigger the occasion, the more suitable it was to advertise. Since they were not subordinates of Godora, just giving out pleasantries of thanking each other would be too boring for the viewers. As the saying goes, as long as one has the guts, even wheat can have a yield of 18,000 kilograms per acre of land[1]!

Besides, could Godora still take back the medal in front of everyone watching?

F*ck me, at such a grand and formal occasion, you actually came out with an advertisement... The smile on Serbia the Fifth's face instantly froze, the phrase 'MMP[2]' almost coming out from his throat. He forcefully swallowed it and maintained his slight smile with difficulty.

I am the leader of the Godorans. I cannot be seen uttering any profanities...

Pa!

The various Army Commanders facepalmed on the spot. We're all colleagues, but to dare use such a venue to make an advertisement, your courage surpasses all of us here.

"Truly my teacher, even his shameless mannerisms are still so handsome!" Sylvia was staring with sparkling eyes.

Hila suddenly had a sense of relief. This guy indeed had not changed and still had that nasty streak within him!

Kacha!

Countless cameras captured the moment of the duo shaking hands, as though carving this memory into the river of time.

In the eyes of the players, this scene seemed to have a significance on par with an epic tale. Looking at Han Xiao, who had mentioned the Black Star Army, many players suddenly felt inexplicable excitement and pride, as though it was their honor.

Galaxy Calendar, Year 692, the 25th day of the 5th Month.

Godora had launched a comprehensive counterattack on DarkStar, annihilating them. Black Star was revealed as their key source of intelligence, and his actions had practically rewritten the power structure of the Garton Star System. The Black Star Army had also participated in the counterattack, codenamed [Operation Hodellas].

In the 6th Month of the same year, Black Star was awarded the Golden Gal Badge by Godora's Supreme Leader, Serbia the Fifth. He became the first non-Godoran to have received this honor in history.

Time seemed to stand still as all the events were written into history.

The Shattered Star Ring was thrown into chaos!

After the formal ceremony was a celebration for the civilization. The people applauded and cheered for the destruction of DarkStar.

At the end of the ceremony, Han Xiao, under the aggrieved stare of Serbia the Fifth, took the official hovercraft for the reception and returned to the guest house with the other Army Commanders.

On the way, Gureja, Underworld Feather, and the other Army Commanders were all cozying up to Han Xiao.

After the award presentation, everyone knew in their hearts that the Black Star Army was the one that had benefitted the most and had successfully made a name for themselves. They would obtain a continuous flow of tasks in the future, so Han Xiao's position in their hearts had gone up a few notches. The moment they had the opportunity, they would try to connect more with him.

When the hovercraft stopped at the guest house, Han Xiao, who was already frustrated from all the talking, hurriedly pried himself away from everyone, returning to his room.

Once he closed the door, Han Xiao drank some water and caught his breath. Only then did he take out the Golden Gal Badge, holding it in front of his eyes to analyze.

An introduction popped out on his interface.

Golden Gal Badge: Highest level of honor awarded by Godora—Your relationship with the Godoran Civilization is fixed at [Reverence]. If Faction Favorability falls to a negative level, the relationship will change. The favorability of all citizens toward you is at [Respect], and the relationship with all of Godora's allies will reach [Friendly].

Remark: When a small piece of metal that costs less than 1 Ena has the meaning of honor attached to it, its perceived value rises tens of thousands of times in the eyes' of some people.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

This medal has changed my Favorability levels so much, probably saving me at least four or five years of time.

The improvement of his relationships meant that people would show him more respect, and the Black Star Army would receive more employment, allowing them to expand their business.

The default model of his Black Star Army would require a lot of resources, and the thing that he needed most would be NPC provided resources. With the increase in faction favorability provided by the medal, it would help him to save a lot of energy.

Looking at the interface, in addition to the effects provided by the medal, there were more notifications. With the official announcement of DarkStar being annihilated being broadcast, the interface had also sent out a popup showing that the mission [Godora's Ally] had been completed.

Mission [Godora's Ally] has ended. The objectives completed consist of: [Deputy Chief - Degulish], [Wind Demon - Anur], [Captured Mothership], [Assault Ship Destroyer]...

Mission rating: Unbelievable

You have been awarded 75,000,000 experience, 3000 Godora Favorability, 2 Potential Points, 4 Free Attribute Points, 1 Random Reward, and 4 Special Items.

This was a Grade A main storyline, and one of the four special items was a Medal of Honor. However, Han Xiao had already obtained three and combined them to obtain the special medal that would give a twelve-percent bonus to all Attributes. This item was a one-of-a-kind, so there was no need for his newly obtained Medal of Honor. He gazed at the other three special items instead.

Character Summon Card—DarkStar Leader: [Heart Malediction—Collapse] - Causes the effect of [Mind Collapse] on a single target. If successful, the target will lose control of their body and will not be able to perform any actions. Effect and Duration will be determined based on the MYS attribute.

Number of times used: 0/2

Character Summon Card—Ember: [Carbon Deconstruction—Intermediate Damage] - Inflicts a large amount of True Damage to all enemy targets within 400m. Specific damage value is based on the difference in Level between the targets and user. The larger the value, the higher the damage, and the higher the probability of inflicting serious injuries, disabilities, internal bleeding, and other negative statuses.

Number of times used: 0/3

Character Summon Card—Nagakin: [Secret Skill—Muscle Is Truth] - +250 STR, +40% Damage to Melee Attacks. Lasts 3 minutes.

Number of times used: 0/7

Muscle is truth? What a weird skill name. Han Xiao's mouth twitched. What sort of philosophical ideology is this? You might as well have put 'Whoever has the strongest fist dictates the truth'.

He left his random reward untouched. Without reaching a certain amount, he did not wish to draw them. Moreover, he did not have any problems that required the testing of his luck.

Following which, Han Xiao scrolled down the interface. By completing the Mission Rating with a high Mission Rating, he had produced a new Dungeon Crystal.

[Godora vs. DarkStar]!

The new Dungeon Crystal was the same as the previous [Six Nations and Germinal Organization]. It comprised all the main storyline battle episodes and condensed them to form the dungeon crystal. It would basically just be parts of the mission of [Godora's Ally], sending out enemies to challenge the players. Weakened copies of Anur, Degulish, and a fixed number of DarkStar warriors and elite warriors would appear, along with the assault ships.

The number of copies present would almost be equivalent to the number of enemies in DarkStar that he had defeated.

However, the players now would only be abused if they used the dungeon crystal, so they would not be able to utilize it.

His gains this time were still good.

After sorting out his rewards, Han Xiao then looked toward his other notification prompts.

Unsurprisingly, this sensational ceremony had awarded him with new Legendary Points.

Not one, but two points!

Galactic Legendary Point (Garton Star System): Destroyer of DarkStar—DarkStar was the nemesis of Godora, a terrorist organization that did whatever they liked. The two have clashed for many years, but you have managed to bring about an opportunity, rewriting the power structure. Because of your help, Godora managed to annihilate DarkStar. DarkStar has become part of history, and your legends will exclaim and astound everyone. The world will respect you, and those who are against you will fear you.

Galactic Legendary Point (Garton Star System): Godora's Ally—You have made a huge contribution to Godora and have been conferred the highest honor, the Golden Gal Badge. Your achievements will be recorded in the history of Godora, remembered by all its people!

"What an unexpected surprise." Han Xiao rubbed his hands in glee.

Legendary Points were hard to obtain. He initially only had one point. To think that he got two points in one go, which, if converted, would give him a bonus of twenty-four percent when receiving rewards. The improvement was considerable, and this showed the potential benefit of obtaining Legendary Points.

'Destroyer of DarkStar' title naturally came from annihilating DarkStar, and 'Godora's Ally' was obtained because of the Golden Gal Badge and the [Godora's Ally] mission. They were divided into separate titles.

"After another few days of 'fermentation' in the media, my renown will skyrocket. The Black Star Army will see its reputation rise to a scarily high level. People will flock toward me, be it employers with or without money."

Han Xiao was quite satisfied.

He had obtained explosive fame in the Garton Star System and could probably roam unhindered through this part of the galaxy.

His next goal would be to consolidate his reputation while expanding his mercenary group, allowing the players to officially start their mercenary careers.

"Since the ceremony has already ended, there's no need to stay on the Godora mother star any longer. After a night's rest, I'll receive the fifty-one spaceships and take the players over to Planet Golden Gate, our first base."

Han Xiao set down the plans in his mind.

At the edge of the Shattered Star Ring, on an unmanned, desolate planet, a spaceship was suspended in the air, collecting gaseous fuel from the planet. There were only two people on board, the DarkStar leader and Ember.

At that moment, in the cockpit where they were seated, the virtual screen in front of them had just finished broadcasting the celebration of Godora. Han Xiao's award ceremony had also been taken in by the eyes of them both.

There was a deathly silence.

The expressions of the DarkStar leader and Ember were stiff as they finally understood why they had lost so miserably.

[1] This might sound a little iffy, but supposedly this amount of wheat yield was only possible back in the 1950s, when they did not care about preserving land fertility I suppose. The normal yield of wheat is believed to be around 800 – 900 kg per acre. Back

[2] MMP is a slang vulgarity commonly used in Sichuan areas. Back

Chapter 590: Influence

"I did not lose to Godora; I lost to him..." The DarkStar leader had a complicated expression on his face.

Back when Black Star first entered his sights, he had still been a small-time mercenary. After Black Star killed Anur, only then did he take him seriously. He had never expected Black Star to rise like a rocket, making three Calamity Grade officers swallow a shameful failure. In the end, DarkStar had become a stepping stone for Black Star.

"Terrifying person..." The DarkStar leader did not feel angry but helpless.

Why did we mess with this guy at the start?

Ember was sulking.

A few years ago, when he first fought Black Star, he would never have thought Black Star would become the one to destroy DarkStar.

Black Star had almost become his nightmare.

Although he had taken Black Star's potential much more seriously than his colleagues, it was too late. The DarkStar leader was about to take him away from Shattered Star Ring to find someone to rely on in another Star Field.

Ember believed in the leader's judgment. Hence, even at this time, despite knowing that Black Star was the mastermind behind everything, they were not going to turn around and deal with him. Furthermore, troops that were after them were everywhere in the Garton Star System, so going back was basically giving themselves up.

Nonetheless, Ember was frustrated.

The DarkStar leader glanced at him and said indifferently, "Don't think too much. A loss is a loss. Before we recover our forces, we have no ability to get revenge."

"I know. The matter of the utmost importance now is to look for the person you said we could rely on." Ember nodded solemnly and suppressed his anger and frustration deep within his heart. He knew that before they had the ability to, revenge was just an empty dream. He paused and asked, "Who is this person you're talking about?"

"A Beyond Grade A, you will know by then."

Joy appeared on Ember's face. "You managed to find a Beyond Grade A? That's amazing. This way, we won't have to hold back because of Floating Dragon."

The DarkStar leader glanced at Ember and suddenly asked, "Ember, what do you think the best future for hybrids is?"

"Best future? Overthrowing the reign of the purebloods and becoming the new Godora, of course," Ember replied without hesitation.

The DarkStar leader expressed neither approval nor denial. "And what does it mean to have overthrown the reign of the pureblood? All the government officials becoming hybrids? Killing all purebloods? If we successfully control the government, the fixed bloodline society levels can't be changed overnight. Even if the government is overthrown, the remaining Godora purebloods will request help from the ally civilizations. By then, there will both be exterior and interior problems. Even if we overthrow the reign of the purebloods, it might not last for long. Furthermore, the Colton Star Cluster's Star Cluster Civilization will not approve of our legal position."

Ember frowned. "Despite the obstacles, there will be a chance."

"What if there's a better way? Where the hybrids leave Godora, get away from the rule of the purebloods. We build a home belonging to the hybrids in another Star System, where everyone is a hybrid. There will not be the problem of bloodline anymore; we will rule ourselves, free of Godora's label, becoming a new civilization, a new race."

Thinking of that image, longing appeared in Ember's eyes. He then shook his head—he had thought of this before.

"If we openly split from Godora, we will have nowhere to hide. Godora will attack us immediately. Furthermore, in order to create a new civilization, there are way too many difficulties: territory, diplomacy, manpower, production, population, and many more. Plus, the obstacle in the political aspect is too strong. The other Star System civilizations or even Star Cluster civilizations will not sit and watch us create a civilization without doing anything. We will have almost no support at all."

"Yes, no civilization will support us, unless a higher power interferes." The DarkStar leader stopped this conversation and changed the topic. "You pilot the spaceship; I have something important to deal with."

The DarkStar leader then left the communicator, took out the hidden communicator, and sent a communication request.

The blurry image appeared once again.

"We will be able to leave Shattered Star Ring very soon. Everything is prepared."

"Alright, we have introduced you to that person already. He's very interested in your offering and is waiting for you."

The DarkStar leader nodded and said, "One more thing, about Black Star... he's an obstacle."

"You don't have to worry about Black Star. If needed, we will find someone to provide him with a mission at a price he cannot refuse." The blurry shadow faintly smiled. "After all, he's a mercenary. Being killed on a mission is the most common way for mercenaries to die."

After a few more words, the DarkStar leader hung up the communication and returned to the cockpit.

The spaceship continued on its journey after harvesting fuel, heading toward outside of Shattered Star Ring, turning into a stream of light, and disappearing into the universe.

...

On Floating Dragon Island...

"Black Star is probably Floating Dragon's strongest officer."

"Ames really found a treasure."

"Did you guys know that I once fought Black Star on Floating Dragon Island?"

"You were the one being beaten up, right?"

The Godoran ceremony had been broadcasted there too. The numerous scavengers and galactic pirates chatted at the dock.

At this time, a small gray metal spaceship slowly landed. On its body was a special mark—crossed arms on top of a cross, surrounded by a ring made up of different shapes.

Upon noticing this spaceship, the volume of these galactic pirates suddenly softened. Their faces turned horrified.

This mark represented another Beyond Grade A force in Shattered Star Ring—Bloodshed Land.

'Tyrant' Heber, a person who had achieved Beyond Grade A on the path of the Pugilist. He was known as 'The Walking Fixed Star', 'The One Who Stepped into the Forbidden Zone of Life'.

Unlike Ames who was neutral, he was a VIP of a Star Cluster Civilization. The Bloodshed Land under his command was an enormous organization that ruled an area. Compared to the size of Floating Dragon, it was like the difference between an adult and an infant.

A group of people disembarked from the spaceship, led by a tall, muscular man wearing heavy plate armor without a helmet, showing his face with the features of the Demon race.

His skin was red. A pair of curved horns extended from his forehead, and half of one was missing. His pupils were white, and two dark black lines slashed across his face from his forehead all the way down to his jaw, giving off a strong feeling of hostility.

With every step he took, he left a shallow footstep on the ground behind him, showing the tremendous weight he carried with him.

"That's one of the Bloodshed Land's Eight Frontiersmen, a core officer, 'Broken Horn' Malekith."

"Bloodshed Land's men coming to Floating Dragon? Could these two Beyond Grade A Supers have some plan?"

The people on the dock held their breath and whispered. Malekith from Bloodshed Land told his subordinates to standby and ran toward the palace in the middle of Floating Dragon alone, disappearing from everyone's sight.

Not long after, a stream of light suddenly rose from the palace, drawing a parabola in the sky over the entire city area extremely fast, and fell right near the dock.

Boom!

Like a meteor, a deep crater formed on the ground.

The galactic pirates around were startled and hastily looked over.

In between the dust created by the impact, Malekith climbed up from the deep crater and dusted off the soil from his body.

The Dragon Emperor had always been hostile toward Bloodshed Land's people. When he met Ames, he was thrown out by her Force Field before he could say much. However, Malekith was unhurt despite what had happened.

"The invitation letter has been delivered, let's go."

With an indifferent face, Malekith ordered his subordinates to board the spaceship. The spaceship took off and disappeared into space.

...

On Planet Aquamarine, in the middle of the reconstruction after the disaster, the Sanctuary and the Six Nations were visited by uninvited guests.

Spaceship fleets landed on Planet Aquamarine one after another, these people were all from the financial groups operating in the Garton Star System.

After Bennett discussed with the Six Nations leader, they decided to use the base that Black Star had left on Planet Aquamarine as a landing spot to meet all visitors from space.

The personnel of the various financial groups gathered and conversed with Bennett and the Six Nations leader together.

"Why are all of you here?"

With the instructions that Han Xiao had left behind to communicate with visitors from outer space, Bennett and the Six Nations' superiors were much calmer.

"Hi, government authorities of Planet Aquamarine, I'm the senior director of Lauren Financial Group..."

"I'm Shine Financial Group's manager..."

The financial group personnel introduced themselves one after another, followed by their purpose.

"We hope to sign commercial partnership treaties with you, to invest in Planet Aquamarine. Simply put, we will pay the money to modify Planet Aquamarine for you in exchange for business licenses and permission to build businesses here."

With the background of Floating Dragon in addition to the sensational Golden Gal Badge event recently, Planet Aquamarine became a hot target for many galactic financial groups. Not only were there commercial opportunities, but there was also a chance to get on the good side of Floating Dragon. The return was very valuable.

Hence, many financial groups decided to invest in Planet Aquamarine's development.

Usually, advanced civilizations were not allowed to interfere with the developments of lower civilization. However, what would be considered 'interference' was very blurry. The investments from galactic financial groups hardly had anything to do with advanced civilizations. Furthermore, whether or not any advanced civilizations were behind this was even more difficult to clarify.

Also, this was Shattered Star Ring, the edge of the known universe, far from the authorities.

Bennett and the Six Nations superiors were overjoyed. What they dreamt of was indeed to become a galactic civilization from a surface civilization. Although the path they took was not exactly the same, it was an effective path.

All of this was brought about by Black Star. Having someone on the same planet doing so exceptionally well in the universe was a blessing for Planet Aquamarine.

Relying on Han Xiao was indeed proven to be better than relying on Godora.

After agreeing on the idea, the authorities of Planet Aquamarine discussed the partnership with the galactic financial groups for the very first time in history.

This planet was gradually taking steps toward the universe.

Planet Aquamarine's galactic era had begun.

...

The day after the award ceremony, Han Xiao bade farewell to the Godoran superiors and the army commanders. He received fifty Violent Falcon battleships and a Fortress Grade flagship. The improved fleet carried all the members of the Black Star Army and left the Godora Mother Planet.

This was a remarkably profitable trip. With the size of their fleet, it was more than enough to even fight a small-scale galactic war.

After many days, Planet Golden Gate finally appeared in their sights.

"Finally, we've reached the headquarters."

Inside the BlackLight Stealth cockpit, Han Xiao looked at the outline of Planet Golden Gate and smiled.

Chapter 591: Changing Main Cities

After informing them of his identity, the attitude of the Planet Golden Gate guards became immensely respectful, and they were immediately allowed to proceed. With the Golden Gal Badge, he had a transcendent status in the eyes of the Godorans and could move almost unobstructed through the Garton Star System.

Countless players swarmed to the portholes, taking in the grand appearance of the Base No.1.

The Base No.1 that had taken a whole year to build resembled a castle coated in alloys. Han Xiao was deeply aware that this was an era where looks mattered, so he had made the exterior especially beautiful, full of technological impressions.

If not for the fact that it would result in him being judged by the players as narcissistic, he would even have liked to paint a portrait of himself on the castle walls.

The fleet successfully landed in Base No.1. During its construction, Han Xiao's blueprint had reserved a huge section of space to serve as a hangar, which would be more than enough to accommodate sixty to seventy individual spaceships. Even the largest flagship level spaceship had a personalized hangar for it.

The air vents sounded as the ships were depressurized. The doors of the cabins slid open, and tens of thousands of players stepped into the hangar, curiously looking around. They were packed closely together, looking like a sea of bobbing heads.

At this point, Phillip's voice sounded in the hangar area, cutting through the hubbub of noises as it was clearly transmitted into everybody's ears.

"Welcome to Base No.1, hum... I would like to ask the new mercenaries to open their communicators and manually accept the verification procedures, hum..."

As he spoke, the communicators of the players suddenly rang all at once.

Frenzied Sword took his out, only to see that there had been new programs added to the communicator. After opening it, he found out that it was the mercenaries identity verification program for the Black Star Army. There were additional functions, such as searching for a particular area of the base, database query information, and so on...

Basically, it was a guide meant to simulate an AI in certain ways.

This was a sub-program made by Han Xiao for Phillip. The players would be able to find out about their own tasks and credits within the Black Star Army through this program. Since the players were also free mercenaries, there had to be a separate account for their accumulated credit, so it would be convenient for management and overall planning. This would also make it convenient for players to check their current accomplishments.

To enhance the sense of accomplishment within the players, there was a need to allow them to see that each task they completed would be reflected real-time in the records of the Black Star Army. There would be no underhanded moves, and everything was transparent and open.

Because the players obtained rewards through the [Operation Hodellas - War Employment] mission, they had all bought their own communicators during their trip to the Godoran mother planet.

Because the market price for such communicators was dirt cheap, there was no way for Han Xiao to earn by being the middleman, so he did not even bother to dabble in this business.

Base No.1 had been built after Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, King Admiral, and the rest left during the patch from Version 1.0 to 2.0, so they only received the subprogram at this point.

"So, this is the base of our Black Star Army. Pretty cool!"

"Strange, in the last version of your video, there wasn't such a huge base!" Someone stared at Bun-Hit-Dog, causing the latter to quickly cover his face and leave.

"Heh, it must be the change in timeline along with the update in the version. It's not the first time this type of thing has happened."

Including Frenzied Sword and the others, this was the first time any player had ever set foot on Base No.1—they were all excited.

The purpose of Base No.1 was to allow the players to treat this place as their Main City. With this faction camp, people would feel that their faction had influence and was reliable, generating a higher sense of belonging.

With the subprogram present, Han Xiao did not need to explain things personally any longer. He did not bother managing the players, allowing them to move about as they wished.

Once upon a time, these players' main city had been on Planet Aquamarine. However, they had now shifted to Base No.1, and thus, they needed to be familiar with the current main city to dispel their confusion.

...

Back in his room, Han Xiao took some time off to clear his backlog of work, such as the applications for free mercenaries to join his group, as well as some new employment invitations.

After the ceremony where he showed his face, the amount of business cases showed an exponential surge. There were even cases that invited him, a mercenary, to be their endorser for an advertisement. They had to be crazy!

However, upon closer inspection, he realized that the other party was an arms company. That made more sense.

By recruiting the tens of thousands of players, following word of mouth and his spike in popularity, Han Xiao thus decided to recruit as many free mercenaries as possible. Although the players were good, they had a restriction—the version updates. As such, he had to plan ahead.

To use players to expand his Black Star Army, improve word of mouth to attract more free mercenaries. This also worked as a chain of interest.

The backlog of employment tasks was endless. Phillip sorted them according to the difficulty, and the entire layout became clear at a glance.

The majority of the employment tasks would be provided to the players themselves. Only a few high-paid, difficult, or high-levelled tasks would require his officers or even himself to be involved.

Due to the mercenary model of borrowing chickens to obtain eggs, the players would be sent to different places throughout the galaxy to carry out their missions, which would allow them to explore the area. The place where each mission was to be completed would have their own events and plots, which could make up for the lack of knowledge the Black Star Army had, as well as giving the player some additional benefits.

Furthermore, the players had just entered the interstellar region not too long ago and required a stable flow of activities to allow them to familiarize themselves with the environment, as well as a storyline that could guide their actions.

To this end, areas with rich NPC resources such as Planet Sunil would have most of the functions that the players need, including a storyline.

If the players were seen as seeds, then the NPC resource areas would be the soil with fertilizer.

Planet Sunil was the first pilot test that Han Xiao had prepared for the players, and it was also time to complete his promise to Herlous.

Han Xiao looked deep in thought.

"From now on, the plan will enter a new chapter."

...

"Black Star, were you looking for me?"

Herlous pushed open the door before entering the room.

Compared to the past him when he had just followed Han Xiao to be a mercenary, Herlous' aura had become calmer and more stable. As a mercenary, they had no shortage of opportunities to fight, and Herlous' strength was slowly increasing with each battle.

"Herlous, I promised that I would bring tens of thousands of Supers to solve the problem of the Sunils' once and for all." Han Xiao paused and smiled. "In the name of the Black Star Army, I'll loan 200,000 mercenaries to you with the most basic remuneration. During this mission, they can be dispatched to Sunil."

Herlous paused in shock before his face showed unbridled joy.

This was why he had followed Black Star and was also the reason he had believed in Black Star's promise. The day had come!

At this moment, he was extremely touched and would gladly pull out the knife for Han Xiao.

As for what he would pull the knife out for, even he had no idea.

Reluctantly holding back his excitement, Herlous spoke quickly. "I'll inform my people immediately, allowing them to issue a formal invitation to hire the Black Star Army."

"Sure, but I have an additional condition." Han Xiao nodded.

"As long as it is within our capabilities, I'll promise you."

"It's nothing too serious. I would just like to have permission to build an offshore base of Black Star Army on Planet Sunil." Han Xiao smiled harmlessly.

Each NPC resource area was a great place to provide players with benefits. So long as there was a sub-base established in the location, it would be indirectly counted as the 'territory' of Black Star himself.

"No problem," Herlous straightforwardly replied before pausing a while and adding on, "This is good for us as well. The upper echelons will not reject your idea."

Because of the award given by Godora, Han Xiao's face was akin to a golden signboard. He estimated that if he went out to buy fruits from a stall, he would probably obtain a five percent discount.

After sending away the excited Herlous who was getting irritating, Han Xiao opened his communicator and activated Phillip's feedback interface.

All players who had installed the subprograms were immediately shown as red dots and displayed on his map in real time. With Han Xiao's expertise being in Virtual Technology, this was just simply surveillance in disguise.

It was not that he could not be assured by having players around, but he did not wish for them to mess up themselves.

Inside the map, the players had spread to every corner of Base No.1, with the majority being clustered in the store area.

Seeing the situation, the corners of Han Xiao's mouth curled up, showing a pleased smile.

"The old inventory finally has a pathway to go."

...

Base No.1 was divided into many different areas, with the store area sector allowing players to obtain products from the existing inventory. After paying the required amount, Phillip would draw out the respective item from the warehouse. This whole process was automated.

At this moment, there was a long line of players lining up in front of the stores.

Because the production of the assembly line had never stopped, it had resulted in a huge stock of equipment and machinery being stored. The machinery had all been carefully selected by Han Xiao and was very suitable for players at this stage. It would be ideal for players to replace their current equipment.

For the players other than Frenzied Sword and company that did not have the NCO Class armor, they had an even greater demand for more advanced equipment. As long as there was a demand, there would be a market. If there was no demand, he just had to create some!

Set after set of equipment was quickly sold, and the fully stocked warehouse was just like a beautiful love scammer, slowly sucking dry the players'... wallets.

This turnover has caused the Enas in Han Xiao's inventory to raise at a staggering rate. One million Enas? A mere fraction!

Although the equipment was all assembly line products, their quality was not low at all. Furthermore, because the equipment required a higher level of technical skill, the base price could not be set too low. Hence, even if the players spent all their money, they simply did not have enough to replace all their current equipment.

This was especially so for the expensive full body armor, which gnawed on the stomachs of the players like parasites.

The moment the players lacked money, the first thing that would come to their mind would be to complete more tasks!

For this, the subprogram of Phillip showcased a dazzling list of acceptable employment tasks.

Most of those missions had considerable rewards. According to the procedures set by Han Xiao, Phillip explained that this was a benefit brought by the reputation and connections of the Black Star Army. Only mercenaries who had joined the Black Star Army could enjoy such a good employment task. If it was a free mercenary, they would probably have to risk their life for a meagre reward.

The reason Han Xiao had requested that Phillip emphasize this was to ingrain in the players the benefits they could enjoy by being in the Black Star Army. Furthermore, being a growing faction, helping the Black Star Army in its missions would make it such that both parties benefitted.

"The rewards are plenty!"

"The best missions will definitely have a lot of people fighting over it. However, the failure compensation is also equally high."

The majority of players discovered the benefits of being a mercenary.

The most obvious thing was that the reward for these interstellar missions far exceeded that of the missions on Planet Aquamarine. Furthermore, they were now free to choose their missions and had great freedom in completing them, which made those players who were frustrated over triggering mission enjoy this new process.

Each employment mission could have multiple people participating, although the maximum number would vary. Players that wished to accept a mission would first have to submit an application through the subprogram, and then Phillip would operate to access their qualifications. If the player met the requirements, the application would be approved. Only then could the player be officially counted in the mission.

Because the requirements also included the difficulty of the employment missions, the difficult missions would definitely be more rewarding. Many players wanted to grab the high-paying employment missions, but all their applications were rejected.

Phillip explained all this to the players.

Han Xiao had set up a faction level system, to provide players with a way to advance within the system. With the base level as 1-Star, the higher one's level, the higher one's authority and standing. That personal level was also used as an application standard for employment missions, which served as a gauge to the difficulty they could handle. Players had to first complete enough low-difficulty tasks to raise their credibility points in order to be eligible for the more difficult tasks.

This was to protect their reputation. Han Xiao knew the players too well—they loved to fool around. If every mission ended in failure, this would hurt the reputation of his faction, and all the glory obtained thus far would be lost. Thus, such a safeguard was needed.

In addition, Han Xiao also set up another system. Players could browse the employment list anywhere, but they had to return to the base to accept a mission.

The reasoning provided was that there was a need to verify the identity of the mercenary and to prevent theft of the communicator. In actual fact, it was to prevent players from staying outside for an extended period of time, ensuring that they returned to the main city and cultivated their feelings... as well as to spend money.

If they did not come back, how could he earn money from them?

On the other side, the players whom had originally followed Black Star into space had mixed feelings.

"The way to accept missions has been changed..."

In Version 1.0, they had followed Han Xiao to perform various missions. However, they had now been given the right to freely choose the missions. The most intuitive feeling was that their faction's strength was becoming stronger and stronger.

At this moment, a new employment notice was placed on the subprogram's employment list.

Sunil Rescue Operation: Large Scale Employment Mission

Mission Introduction: Planet Sunil is plagued by catastrophes. With the suggestion of the Black Star Army Officer Herlous, Black Star has decided to issue a designated employment to the Black Star Army, recruiting a large number of mercenaries to solve their disasters once and for all.

Mission Requirements: Proceed to Planet Sunil to solve the source of the disaster.

Number of recruits: 200,000

Remark: This is a large-scale mission. Completion of this task will raise the reputation of the Black Star Army. There will be increased benefits as well as a new base.

"Wah, 200,000‽ That's almost half of our total numbers!"

"This must be a big event."

"Sunil? Catastrophe? Isn't that the storyline that Bun-Hit-Dog posted on his channel? Turns out, there's actually still a continuation."

The majority of players immediately felt curiosity.

The remuneration was not high. After all, the lives of the Sunils were not well off. They could not help but wish that every Ena they had could be split into five. Han Xiao had given them a preferential price, and thus, the other party was able to afford it. However, due to the fact that it was a large-scale employment, the experience reward was still sufficient.

The large-scale employment of 200,000 players was undoubtedly a main storyline in the eyes of the players. Many of them wanted in on the 'fun', so gathering the required amount was not difficult at all.

Among the hundreds of thousands of players, those who were casual players numbered higher. Compared to the professional players or players belonging to large guilds, the adaptability of the casual players was weaker.

The interstellar map was extremely broad, and upon seeing the large number of tasks as well as the high degree of freedom, the casual players were thrown into confusion, not knowing what was good.

The employment task of the Sunils served as a way to 'guide' these players.

Not sure what missions to take? Just follow the crowd and take up this large-scale employment. As long as there was a crowd, there would not be any problems.

Just in case, to ensure that the mission could attract a significant number of players, Han Xiao also increased the faction favorability reward, and modified the mission description to emphasize it as a task that could help the faction to grow. This served as a form of motivation for the players.

However, Han Xiao could be said to have been overly worried this time. Being awarded the medal from Godora had resulted in him getting sensationalized on the forum. The players realized that Han Xiao was already a famed person shining within the universe.

The players could be said to have watched Han Xiao grow along the way and had a sense of gratification to fight for the Black Star Army.

While the reward was not high, many of the players would not mind participating in missions that would allow the Black Star Army to grow.

After so many years of his actions, Han Xiao had gradually imprinted himself on the players' hearts.

Chapter 592: The Investment from Noriosse

On the forums, many of the players were sharing their own views. The Planet Aquamarine sector became the most happening region, and many players from the other novice planets also came over to take a look from time to time.

Some players posted about the different strange looking species of the universe and others the magnificent scenery. There were even some who posted their selfies with the various NPCs... mainly Aroshia, Feidin, and Sylvia.

Since Han Xiao made a promise to Risda, he sent the scenes of Aroshia's memories to all the players and gave them a new mission. It would naturally be more efficient to mobilize all the players to search together.

Bun-Hit-Dog and Galaxy Times closely followed the trend and released a new series. The content of the series was the first beginner planet entering the galaxy. The series introduced the Black Star Army, the various facilities of Base No.1, and the award ceremony of Black Star.

Han Xiao, who was already a famous NPC among the players, once again had his fame boosted.

There was another hot thread at the moment, which was about Planet Aquamarine's changes.

There were still tens of thousands of players trying to pass the test in Base No. 2, and they personally witnessed how the galactic financial groups aided Planet Aquamarine in its development, opening up many new opportunities in the process.

Han Xiao found out from the thread that Planet Aquamarine experienced a huge breakthrough in technology through the aid of the galactic financial groups with many new buildings shooting up from the ground. Planet Aquamarine was rapidly stepping into the galactic era.

Han Xiao was not too surprised by this outcome. When he invited the reporters to Planet Aquamarine back then, he had already expected such an occurrence.

However, the way the players felt about this phenomenon could be described with a single phrase.

A single person receiving enlightenment, the chickens and dogs rise to the heavens!

The players worked together to piece together Planet Aquamarine's history, and the change that they were witnessing before their eyes could be said to be a result of Han Xiao's actions alone.

Planet Aquamarine was able to develop so rapidly only because of Black Star's influence in the galaxy.

Bringing benefits to the billions of inhabitants on Planet Aquamarine, this alone would make Black Star the hero of the planet.

Han Xiao's charisma formed a strange sense of attraction between the players of Planet Aquamarine.

...

A few days later...

The players could be split into four general groups.

First, the ones who stayed in base and familiarize themselves with the new Main City. Finally, they would accept missions from the Black Star mercenaries.

Second, the indecisive ones who did not know what to do. They would end up remaining on the prosperous Planet Golden Gate, digging up missions from the planet.

Third, those who accept the various missions. They would follow Phillip's instructions to go on a special Black Star Army galactic tour. They would go to the various Star Zones of the Garton Star System and sightsee while completing missions.

The last group would be the 200,000 players who accepted the Sunil rescue mission. They followed the Sunil Division led by Herlous and made their majestic appearance on Planet Sunil.

Because it was the first time that they had entered the galaxy, the majority of the players chose to act with caution.

Because they were not familiar with the galaxy, it was extremely likely for them to violate different laws. Thus, the missions that Han Xiao released were limited to the Garton Star System, and Phillip would design a program such that they would be reminded of the local laws from time to time to decrease the chances of the players violating the laws.

However, there would definitely be some players who just wanted to do as they wished. After all, the players did not like to be restricted, and some of their brains were like black holes.

Han Xiao understood the players 'creativity' too much and so was not too optimistic.

Han Xiao had already drafted an emergency procedure for the worst-case scenario. He was not obsessed with controlling the players, but punishment was a must.

Of course, he was still in the honeymoon phase, and everything was still going smoothly.

The majority of players were filled with curiosity and excitement. The moment they left Base No.1, they set off on their various missions and explored the different Star Zones.

A few months after the Mutation Disaster and DarkStar incident, the Black Star Army officially began their operations.

Han Xiao gave Phillip's child program the function to purchase equipment. Players who were away from the base could view the products in the faction store and compare prices immediately. They could even make a pre-payment and collect the goods when they returned to the base.

On top of that, the players could also choose to pay an additional fee for the goods to be delivered to them with the price being calculated by distance. The goods would be accumulated before being sent in a large batch. Of course, one could spend even more money to purchase a personal delivery service, and the goods would be sent immediately.

This was another way for Han Xiao to make money. However, the players were still poor, and this service was still in the testing phase with the details being ironed out. Because of the vastness of the universe, the distribution business was extremely prosperous. With Han Xiao's current reputation, it would not be difficult for him to find a couple of distribution companies to cooperate with. In fact, he could even build up his own distribution channel.

Building up a large mercenary group was like building a large corporation. Transport, delivery, reputation, manpower, assets, treatment, and many more other factors needed to be considered. The players were like a trump card for a cooperation that held great benefits within them, capable of being harvested over and over again for a never-ending stream of benefits. Thus, Han Xiao's current job was to design the mercenary group around the players to ensure that he would be able to reap the largest benefits.

...

Herlous led the troops over to Sunil, and as a precautionary measure, Han Xiao placed an [Observer's Mark] on Herlous. This was his third mark.

A while ago, Han Xiao had experimented with the talents of the Chaos Observer race. His vision could ignore physical distance with his vision locked within a certain range of his mark. He could see Aroshia stuffing herself without a concern in the world and Serbia the Fifth working hard. Furthermore, the individual being watched would not notice a thing, and this was truly a divine ability to spy on others.

Base No.1 had immediately become much more spacious. Apart from the players who stayed behind, the only officers left behind were Aroshia and Sylvia. The other officers had taken the mercenaries out to complete some missions of middle to high difficulty.

Han Xiao also stayed behind in the base.

With over 30,000,000 Enas in his account, Han Xiao began buying large amounts of raw materials without any hesitation.

Money was the main combat force of the Army Style. Now that Han Xiao was in the Calamity Grade, he could forge more powerful machines, and he was prepared to evolve the current machines that he had. Apart from restoring the previously damaged machines, he wanted to add some new troops.

Han Xiao was prepared to go into seclusion to build up his army. Since he had plenty of motivated troops under his charge, he would have more time to do other things.

Since Ames did not rush him, he was not in a hurry to send Aurora and Hila to Floating Dragon Island.

"I still owe Noriosse 4,000,000 Enas. It has been less than two years since I borrowed the money from them, and the interest rate is only at ten percent. The interest rate will go up again at the two-year mark."

Han Xiao still remembered this debt. Now that his funds were ample, Han Xiao decided to repay the debt while the interest was not too high.

He then contacted the leader of Noriosse, and the other party's projection appeared before him.

"Black Star? Haha, it has been a long time since you last contacted me. Your fame has truly skyrocketed in recent times," Rockfess said with an amiable smile and warm tone.

Compared to his attitude when Han Xiao wanted to borrow money, his current attitude was much better.

"I actually prefer to remain low profile." Han Xiao coughed dryly before continuing. "I am contacting you to repay the 4,000,000 Enas I owe together with the interest for a total of 4,400,000."

The law governing debts was extremely strict, and Han Xiao would definitely have to pay up eventually.

Rockfess suddenly changed topics and asked, "I wonder, are you willing to accept a sponsorship?"

Han Xiao had just transferred the money over, and his heart was bleeding inside. Upon hearing those words, Han Xiao's brows shot up, and a playful look could be seen in his eyes.

A year ago, when he asked Rockfess for a sponsorship, Rockfess had rejected him and only promised him a loan. This time, Rockfess had actually taken the initiative to offer a sponsorship?

It seemed like his recent accomplishment had made Rockfess think that he was a worthy investment. Thus, Rockfess changed his mind and offered the sponsorship.

While Rockfess was an individual only motivated by benefits, Han Xiao did not think that it was anything strange and did not intend to be sarcastic. Everyone in the world only worked for benefits. He would only be able to draw investments if he displayed sufficient potential or strength. This was the ironclad law.

"Of course, I am extremely interested in this proposal." Han Xiao smiled.

Rockfess' eyes lit up.

He originally had not been too sure if Han Xiao would agree. He had worried that with Black Star already developed, he would not need any external funds. However, he would find it a waste if he lost an investment channel with huge potential.

Since Black Star was willing to accept his sponsorship, it meant that his initial investment was reaping returns.

Rockfess pondered for a while before saying, "Sir Black Star, I have decided to sponsor the Black Star Army with another 5,200,000 Enas."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and asked, "What do you want in return?"

"Haha, this is only an initial investment, and I hope to form a long-term cooperation with the Black Star Army. Our Noriosse financial group will come up with funds to support the development of the Black Star Army, including but not limited to the welfare of mercenaries, transportation, expansion of operations, and the construction of bases. We can also borrow the name of the Black Star Army to start businesses in the Garton Star System or other Star Systems as well. When we require violence to solve our problems, we hope to receive the aid of the Black Star Army at the first possible moment..."

The conditions that Rockfess gave were common ones between financial groups and armed organizations.

Under normal circumstances, the Black Star Army was the Field Team of Floating Dragon, and it would be a better option to invest in Floating Dragon Island directly. However, Black Star himself had some influence and thus became another target for investment.

Han Xiao listened to the conditions patiently and concluded that the Noriosse financial group wanted to manage the backend logistics of the Black Star Army.

The reputation of the Noriosse financial group was extremely good, and they had plenty of different businesses all around.

This was the phase where Han Xiao needed to take care of the backend logistics of the Black Star Army, and it would save him a great deal of trouble with the aid of Noriosse. Most importantly, it would save him a lot of money. The amount of money needed to develop an armed organization was truly terrifying.

What a fat sheep... Han Xiao lamented in his heart

"Sounds good. Mister Rockfess, I am willing to sign an investment agreement."

"Alright, I will get someone to prepare it and send it to you later."

Rockfess was in a brilliant mood, and a bright smile could be seen on his face.

"If the scale of the Black Star Army grows in the future, our Noriosse financial group can even help you to operate a financial market and establish a Black Star brand to launch a credit voucher and public bond."

"We can talk about this in the future..."

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

The so-called credit voucher was basically stocks. With the development of the economy, something like a credit voucher was not too surprising. Since a very long time ago, stocks and bonds had begun appearing in the universe, and many of the large financial groups had begun issuing credit vouchers. Because of the sheer size of the universe, different regions of the universe would have their own stock markets. Usually, each Star System would form a unit, and the Garton Star System had its own financial market.

Players could also purchase these credit vouchers. In his previous life, there had been some players who had made big money from the financial market and also others who had lost big time. With the environment of the galaxy, the ferocity of the financial market could easily be imagined.

Han Xiao was extremely skilled in making money through credit vouchers. In his previous life, he had plenty of experience with buying low and selling high. As for how to suppress the price of another party's credit vouchers... Hehe, he would never walk the orthodox path. Since he had already done plenty of bad deeds, another one would not hurt him.

Of course, the consequences of those actions were severe. Now that he had to take care of an organization, he naturally would not be taking the same path.

As for Rockfess' suggestion of listing a mercenary group on the stock market, it was extremely rare. After all, the operations of a mercenary group were extremely unstable with deaths and injuries being extremely common.

After signing the contract, a 'ding' sound could be heard on the communicator, and the figure on his bank account shot up by 5,200,000 Enas.

"The road ahead is very long. I hope we have a pleasant cooperation." Rockfess stretched his arm out with a bright smile.

Han Xiao also stretched his arm out to shake Rockfess' holographic hand.

"I hope we have a pleasant cooperation."

Chapter 593: Sudden Emergency

As Han Xiao was undergoing a trade with Rockfess, dozens of spaceships carrying 200,000 mercenaries sailed toward Planet Sunil.

The star map in the cockpit flickered. As it showed Planet Sunil nearing them, Herlous' mood grew all the more excited. The same rang true for the other Sunil mercenaries.

They themselves were too aware of their civilization's plight. Because of the catastrophe, the casualty rate of their young and middle aged had always remained high, and their partners lived in constant danger. Now, they finally had a ray of hope to solving this problem!

This group of warriors who would sacrifice their lives for their civilization were all extremely touched, grateful to Han Xiao to the point of wanting to cry.

"The day has finally arrived."

Herlous took a deep breath, regaining a calm mood.

Outside the porthole, Planet Sunil seemed to be beckoning them, and the fleet landed quickly on it, as though both sides had collided with each other.

The main city of Planet Sunil was still Forest City, and all the upper echelons there had long received the news, rushing out to welcome them. From all around, army troops wearing the Sunil armor stood in their formations in welcome, filling a huge patch of open space.

As the spaceships landed one after another, and the players stepped out, they saw the armored troops at a glance. The sunlight reflected off the steel from the Sunil armor, exuding an aura of silence and slaughter.

"We thank the Black Star Army for reaching out to aid us. Welcome, I am..."

One of the upper echelons of the Sunils stepped forward, preparing to give a speech, but before he could finish half of it, he saw the 200,000 mercenaries scatter. The majority of the players ran over to the aggressive armored soldiers with dumb expressions.

"Oh, this is Sunil. Indeed, the same as in the video channels!"

"Come brothers, let's take a group photo!"

Having arrived on the new planet, the players immediately started to party.

"This..."

The upper echelon of the Sunil felt his face twitch incessantly, but he did not know what to do. Turning over, he saw Herlous walk out of the spaceship. He regained his composure, rushing forward respectfully.

"It's all thanks to you, or else we would not have been able to hire the Black Star Army." The superior of the Sunils had an expression of gratitude.

"You should thank Black Star actually. If it wasn't for the fact that he asked me to follow him, Sunil would not have had this opportunity."

Herlous had a solemn expression. In this regard, he felt that he had taken too much of an advantage, and he should not claim credit for this matter.

Right now, Black Star had already been promoted to a Calamity Grade Super, with no shortage of Grade B Supers under him. Instead of saying that he was selling his life for the Black Star Army in exchange for them helping him, it was more accurate to say that it was Black Star that offered his help voluntarily to the Sunils!

After the incident with DarkStar, Herlous had gained a deeper understanding of Han Xiao. To go head on against a terrifying interstellar terrorist organization just for his hometown, this courage was simply too great. Black Star was a righteous partner, with a good character and a nice personality, and his wanting to help Sunil was also purely because he wished to save them, without asking for benefits.

The favorability of Herlous toward Han Xiao had long exploded through the roof, to the point that he would sacrifice his life if asked to or use himself as a shield if needed.

Hearing this, the Sunil superior solemnly nodded. They really owed too much to Black Star. The other party had allowed the Sunil mercenaries to accept better employment, reducing the casualties of their race, and now he had even sent a large number of people over to help, only charging a nominal fee in return.

What a good person!

After arranging the 200,000 'mercenaries', the Sunil upper echelons spread the news of the Black Star Army coming to provide reinforcements to the entire race so that the countless Sunils would know that their opportunity had arrived.

Within the streets, countless people burst into tears as they lowered their heads in prayer.

The name 'Black Star' experienced a rapid increase in prestige in the area.

As Herlous took the Sunil mercenaries to walk down the street, accepting the gratitude of the civilians, he suddenly felt that the fire of hope in this city had been rekindled and felt a lot more hopeful in his heart.

Herlous had also witnessed the specialty of the players and believed that this catastrophe would be resolved sooner or later. However, therein lay a problem for him.

"When the problem of my race has been solved, where should I go?"

As though hit by a bullet in his heart, his body froze in confusion.

That's right, my purpose of becoming a mercenary was to help the race fight on. Once our danger has passed, do I still need to be a mercenary?

Herlous' footsteps slowed down as he entered a dilemma.

Thinking of how Black Star had provided him with help but he would leave right after his objective had been accomplished gave him a sort of feeling as though he was betraying Black Star's trust. His conscience could not ignore this fact.

Then... do I continue staying with Black Star to repay his gratitude?

Upon thinking of his noisy babbling mercenary partners, thinking of the various unknown planets he had seen, the unique lifeforms, and Black Star's ever reliable back facing them...

Herlous' tightly furrowed brows slowly relaxed.

Other than his civilization, it seemed as though he had found another home.

"Heh, without the burdens of my race weighing me down, I can probably obtain a sizable sum and find a pretty lady to get married."

Herlous felt the weight in his heart get removed and suddenly looked forward to the infinite possibilities in the future.

...

On the other side, the players had been warmly welcomed into the Forest City by the Sunils.

"I didn't expect the name of the Black Star Army to be this good."

The crowd of players murmured in surprise. After experiencing it personally, they only belatedly realized how much influence their faction possessed. The name of the Black Star Army seemed to be extremely prestigious.

The 200,000 players split up wandered around Forest City. Right now, the upper echelons of the Sunils were still working out a concrete strategy, so their mission had not yet officially started. At this time, no one would stop the players from moving around freely.

Many of the players utilized the same old method, attempting to trigger additional missions with the various Sunils or searching for equipment stores, skill mentors, general stores, and other functional locations. As a civilization, the Sunils of course had an NPC resource area, with most of the functions being able to serve the players.

Not long after, the players were mass recruited, with a whole list of missions to complete, including exploring the wild, collecting information on the beasts, clearing the beast colonies, regaining abandoned resource points as well as digging mineral veins. All sorts of work were available.

After accepting the various missions, the interfaces of the players would then display the respective tasks, which allowed the players to obtain more experience rewards from these sub-missions.

The popular missions were quickly swept clean, and the crowd's favorite was naturally the mission of robbing resource areas. Because most of the resources were materials, one could get some during the process.

The resource area missions were basically divided among the guild players, but because Sunil wanted to completely resolve the catastrophe, there were many other missions to be completed as well. This ensured that all 200,000 mercenaries had some missions to attempt.

After accepting the missions, players also triggered a series of mission requirements for the faction. The objective was to help the Sunils resolve the catastrophe but had nothing to do with their employment task. Even if one was not a mercenary, they could still trigger this series of missions by helping the Sunils.

In fact, the mercenary mission received by the players back then was the real bonus, which was given as a benefit of the Black Star Army.

With the mission acting like a carrot dangling above the players' heads, the 200,000 players could not wait to get started.

...

A couple of days later, countless robotic arms were busy assembling mechanical warriors in Base No.1's workshop. Han Xiao had his head buried in front of a lathe, focusing on rebuilding his Mechanic Army. Suddenly, his communicator rang.

"Hmm? Who is it?"

Han Xiao put down the items in his hands, taking out his communicator. Lots of possibilities flashed through his mind, be it a mission from Ames or some tasks that the Noriosse Consortium required him to do. It could also be some players having botched their missions and having the employer calling to complain.

All sorts of thoughts flashed by, but after glancing at the communicator, he found out that it was an unknown caller, which left him surprised.

After establishing a connection, an unfamiliar figure appeared in his screen, and he questioned Han Xiao fiercely.

"Black Star, what have you done to my men‽"

"Your men?" Han Xiao replied.

"Befuli! Don't tell me you forgot!" The other party's tone was sinister.

Now where had he heard this name...

Han Xiao stroked his chin before belatedly realizing. Isn't he that guy with the fiery golden eyes? Oh no, that guy with the Esper ability of shooting fire from his eyes.

That idiot had attempted to steal his spaceship and ended up being held captive, with his Esper ability being drawn every day, allowing him to obtain over 100 bottles of the Genetic Medicine. He was probably only left with skin and bones, a foot away from death.

That was to say... the other party should be the 'Purple Snake' Sykes, Befuli's leader and the Captain of the Purple Snake Space Pirates.

"Turns out, it's you." Han Xiao raised his brows. "Your subordinate tried to steal my spaceship, and you still dare to look for me?"

"Where has Befuli gone? Have you killed him?"

"Oh, the answer to that would be... you guess?"

Sykes had a vicious expression on. "Black Star, hand over my people, and I can pretend that this incident never happened."

"Urgh..." Han Xiao exaggeratedly exclaimed before saying, "Your subordinate attempted to steal my spaceship and was captured by me. Now, you want me to release the person and pretend that nothing ever happened? You don't look too pretty, but your thinking is indeed worlds apart from your looks. I'm not sure if I should even thank you for this!"

"Humph, Black Star, you indeed talk as much as the rumors say. However, did you think that I would look for you if I was unprepared?"

Sykes revealed a cold smile, with an inexplicable tone of confidence.

I talk a lot? Which b*stard spread that rumor... no, that's not the main point. Han Xiao regained his wits and immediately understood what Sykes was hinting at. A sense of helplessness spread across his face as he commented, "Who have you captured?"

The corners of Sykes' mouths curled up, and he pressed a button. The screen revealed a jail cell with a group of people tied up together.

Taking a closer look, this bunch was probably the players, no doubt about that. It should be a group of players that were headed for another mission and were ambushed halfway by Sykes' people. In that case, the other party definitely had people that had successfully infiltrated the Garton Star System.

"Black Star, hand over Befuli, or you can forget about seeing the mercenaries under you ever again."

The screen disappeared, and Sykes reappeared on the screen.

"Oh, we can discuss this..." Han Xiao deeply sighed before saying, "How about you just kill all the hostages?"

"News regarding you is being spread all over the galaxy, do you treat me as a fool! You have tens of thousands of immortal warriors under your flag, completely unkillable! However, I believe there will be many organizations that wish to experiment on such immortals and will be willing to fork out the cash. So, you'd better listen to me. I'll only give you five days to escort Befuli to the coordinates of a barren planet. If I do not see him, or if you play some tricks, my Space Pirates will specifically target your mercenaries and sell them to the other Star Clusters."

Sykes' tone carried some threat, immediately cutting off any possible thoughts of rebellion from Han Xiao.

"... Fine." Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

"Remember, five days' time!"

After stressing that once more, Sykes immediately cut off the communication.

If it was not for the fact that his right-hand man had been captured, Sykes would not have antagonized Black Star. Luckily, he did not need to hand over the hostages in person. Sykes was not prepared to go in person, getting someone to go over to the Garton Star System to handle everything whilst he stayed in the Gavin Star System. After all, safety was paramount.

Han Xiao rubbed between his brows, looking helpless. The players were still not strong enough. To allow them to explore and complete missions, he had been expecting such a matter to occur, but he did not think that it would come this quickly.

To have the players be killed because of being unable to repay the ransom, this was considered their own personal encounter. He was no nanny, and by rights, he should not care about this kind of matter. However, Sykes was a Calamity Grade, and for him to target the Black Star Army was a hidden danger. It seemed as though he would have to move out this time.

"F*ck, I can't even take a few god-damned days to rest! Right now, even the time taken to build my little cuties has been deprived!"

With an expression full of grievances, Han Xiao came to the cell where Befuli was being held at. Looking at the unconscious person, he threw an [Observer's Mark] on him.

"Isn't it good to be alive? I had almost forgotten about looking for trouble with you guys."

...

In the Garton Star System, a spaceship that the Purple Snake Space Pirates had taken over was floating quietly in the Universe.

In the dim spaceship cell, a bunch of players were tied there with space pirates on guard at the door.

"President, it seems that we've been down on our luck recently."

Poseidon, one of the core members of the Guild of Gods, turned his head to address Jupiter, who was beside him.

Recently? F*ck that, our luck has been bad the whole time. Who are you looking down upon right now? Jupiter had a dark expression, not even bothering to reply.

He had originally chosen a mission that was quite good and had prepared to bring his core members of the guild to complete the job. However, he had not even reached the place of employment when he was suddenly captured.

The universe was actually this dangerous?

The law and order there could not even be compared to Planet Aquamarine!

The vice president Shiva had an indifferent expression on. "It seems that we have encountered an emergency. Maybe it's a hidden mission."

"The last time we got into trouble, you said the same thing." Poseidon was not polite in his rebuttal.

At this time, a guard outside bellowed, "Who allowed you to talk? Shut your mouths!"

Everyone only turned to look at him before ignoring him, continuing to chatter on.

The guard could only spit out a sigh of resignation. He wished that he could pull out his guns to shoot the hostages into smithereens, but his leader's orders were to not kill even one of them. Killing them would be equivalent to setting them free. Since they were not afraid of death, what could they use to threaten them?

The guards were helpless and could only silently watch on as this group of people behaved more arrogantly than the pirates themselves.

Bang!

At this point, the spaceship suddenly shook, and screams of misery could be heard.

"What happened?"

The guarding pirate lost some color in his expression, hurriedly running over to check it out. However, upon turning his head, he found a majestic figure blocking his way, covering all the light from outside. The pirate's height only reached the figure's belly...

"I'm taking over this ship," the figure stated indifferently, his voice like thunder.

Before waiting for the pirate to respond, a strong blow shot to his side, the speed too fast for him to avoid.

The burly tall figure slapped the guard out of the way, splattering him into meat paste on the side of the wall.

Jupiter and the rest stared at this figure.

With his back to the light, no one could see his looks. They could only see what seemed to be a pair of curved horns on his head, one of which was broken in half.

Chapter 594: Malekith's Ambush! (1)

The exchange location was an uninhabited planet, and both parties would not meet each other. After putting Befuli down, Han Xiao left the planet. The space pirates would then fetch Befuli before releasing the mercenaries that they had caught. They would then contact Han Xiao to pick up the mercenaries.

Sykes had done so to be on the safe side. While honesty was not his strongest point as a space pirate and he frequently went back on his word, he was truly sincere this time. He only wished to get Befuli back and did not wish to provoke Black Star completely.

As long as he could get Befuli back, he would immediately pull back his forces in the Garton Star System and not provoke the Black Star Army again.

However, this was not what Han Xiao felt. It was truly wishful thinking if the other party thought that he would just forget about this matter.

Not too far away from the planet, the BlackLight Stealth was floating in space silently.

Through the window of the spaceship, Han Xiao monitored the planet silently.

He did not bring anyone along with him and moved out alone this time. Furthermore, he also brought the BlackLight Stealth out, which specialized in speed. His objective today was not only to exchange hostages.

Befuli had an [Observer's Mark] placed on him and was no different from Han Xiao's surveillance device. Han Xiao was planning to make use of his Chaos Observer innate talent to tail these space pirates and find Sykes's nest.

He had never juiced a Calamity Grade Super before.

He needed to exchange hostages in order to make Sykes let his guard down. While the players were not afraid of threats, Han Xiao did not wish for anyone to ruin the first mission for the players.

"It's about time..."

Han Xiao piloted his spaceship into the atmosphere of the planet and flew to the designated location.

As he approached the surface of the planet, Han Xiao was taken aback. The space pirates' spaceship was still at the designated spot.

"Didn't we agree not to meet? Why are they waiting for me here? Could it be that they want a face to face exchange instead?"

The doubt flashed past his mind, and Han Xiao parked his spaceship slightly further away. He then picked up the weak Befuli before disembarking from the spaceship.

Ta, ta...

Han Xiao stepped onto the brown sandy surface and kicked up a cloud of dust. The spaceship of the pirates was a few thousand meters away, and a couple of pirates were waving at him.

Han Xiao frowned.

"This feels strange. Risda, don't turn the engine off. Take off immediately if anything happens."

"Alright." Risda took over the command of the spaceship.

Han Xiao took Befuli and approached the pirates' spaceship. When he was near the spaceship, he looked at the few pirates and said in a deep voice, "I have brought the person you want. Where are my mercenaries?"

Since he was close enough to the pirates, Han Xiao immediately noticed something strange about all the pirates. They all seemed to be extremely afraid of something!

Before he could even make a move, something immediately went wrong!

Bang!

A large hole was suddenly made in the pirates' spaceship, and a black figure shot out like a meteor. This figure appeared in front of Han Xiao the next instant, and his fists that were wrapped in a thick layer of metal smashed heavily on Han Xiao's chest.

His frightening strength exploded forth from his fists.

Boom!

Han Xiao's body flew back like a cannonball and smashed into a stone mountain more than a thousand meters away. His entire body became covered in the rubble of shattered rocks with a huge dust cloud being formed.

The individual who had ambushed Han Xiao was standing in Han Xiao's original location. He was clad in heavy metal armor and looked as though he was from the Demon Race. Of the two horns on his head, one had broken in half. He was one of the eight Vanguard Officials of the Bloodshed Land, broken horn Malekith.

The force generated from his attack had sent the space pirates flying as well.

A couple of weaker space pirates had fractured their bones and were currently groaning in pain. They hurriedly scurried away to avoid the battlefield.

Swoosh!

The pile of rubble shook slightly, and Han Xiao burst out of the rocks.

This damage... Grade A Super? Is Sykes here personally to kill me? He then looked at the notification on his interface and was surprised. It isn't Sykes but Malekith? Who is this fellow? He doesn't seem like a subordinate of Sykes, and this name seems a little familiar.

How strange. Why would someone who I have never seen before want to deal with me? Is he an assassin sent by someone to deal with me? That's not right. A single person wouldn't be enough to kill me...

Han Xiao looked at Malekith with his brows locked in deep thought.

Both of them looked at each other from afar without saying a single word.

"I can feel that my previous attack didn't do much damage at all. The 'Undying' Black Star truly lives up to his name."

Malekith was the first to speak.

Undying? Is this my new nickname? Han Xiao then narrowed his eyes and asked, "Who are you? Why did you attack me?"

"You will know when we are done fighting." Malekith did not say another word, and his body burned with black Pugilist flames. He then took large strides forward and rammed into Han Xiao like a shooting star. The heavy armor on his body then sprang into action, and its structure suddenly seemed even more complicated as though it had entered combat mode.

Han Xiao cursed under his breath and activated his mechanical suit. The black Berserk Ape was equipped, and he received Malekith's punch.

Han Xiao immediately felt a huge surge for force pushing him back. Han Xiao's weight and strength could not be compared to Malekith's, and he was immediately pushed back with his feet forming two long ditches on the ground.

Hum!

Right at that moment, the figure of a Godoran appeared behind Han Xiao.

He activated the Nagakin Character Summon Card.

Muscle Is Truth!

Han Xiao could clearly feel the muscles in his body expanding and his entire body being filled with a never-ending supply of strength! His Strength attribute also shot up rapidly!

The instant Han Xiao stopped getting pushed back, he slammed his feet into the ground. The Berserk Ape mechanical suit suddenly revved up, and his waist and arms got into a throwing position. Both his hands grabbed Malekith's fists, and by making use of the other party's force, he did an overhead throw and threw Malekith in the opposite direction!

The instant Han Xiao released his grip, a loud sonic boom could be heard, and Malekith shot toward the sky at an extremely high speed. In just an instant, Malekith had already became a small little dot on the horizon, crashing into a mountain not too far away.

This was a skill that came along with the mechanical suit: Berserk Throw!

Han Xiao glanced at the other party's information only to be greeted with a bunch of question marks.

This meant that Malekith's level far exceeded his.

Han Xiao was still clueless about why the other party would be at the meeting point to ambush him. However, since Malekith did not want to give an explanation, he could only fight Malekith first.

Han Xiao threw out all the useless thoughts in his head and entered a battle focus mode. He then threw out a dozen compressed orbs, and his fully repaired Oathkeepers appeared beside him. The Hovering Shield Shuttle floated behind him, and they glowed with a golden light.

Because this incident was an unexpected one, Han Xiao did not have enough time to completely repair his Mechanic Army. He also did not have the time to improve his current machines and was still using old equipment from the past. The only exception was this Berserk Ape suit.

However, this suit alone should be enough to deal with the battle.

The other party was a Calamity Grade Pugilist and did not seem to have any killing intent. Thus, Han Xiao could not be bothered to take out anymore machines as he would feel the heartache if they got destroyed.

Malekith wore a set of heavy armor, and his defense was extremely high. Furthermore, he had the bloodline of the Demon Race, and his recovery strength was extremely powerful.

In just a few short breaths, his injuries were recovered.

Malekith then dusted away the rocks and dust on him indifferently before charging forward again!

Chapter 595: Malekith's Ambush! (2)

Bang bang bang!

Both of their figures clashed with each other over and over again like a dragon brawling with a snake. They exchange blows as they traversed the brown surface of the planet. Heavy blows landed on both of their bodies as powerful shock waves reverberated through the battlefield.

The shockwaves of the battle had destroyed the original surface of the planet, and craters could be seen all over the surface of the planet.

Malekith's total level was extremely high and was extremely powerful. While a head-on brawl was not Han Xiao's strength, thankfully, he had the Berserk Throw skill to throw Malekith around like a ball and break his Pugilist combos.

Han Xiao could choose to transform into the shuttle mode and escape from there at any time. However, he was extremely interested in Malekith's origins and so decided to have a good fight with him. In any case, the BlackLight Stealth was already hovering up in the sky, and Han Xiao could escape whenever.

Han Xiao then activated the nano transformation ability of the Berserk Ape mechanical suit and transformed into the [Giant Ape Form]. The mechanical suit then expanded rapidly, and various components seemed to have appeared out of nowhere to form thick layers on top of the existing suit. Han Xiao rapidly grew until he was a mini giant that was a head taller than Malekith. His Strength attribute skyrocketed once more, and the strength of [Berserk Throw] was increased.

Both parties were Calamity Grade Supers who had powerful defense and recovery. As such, the battle was stuck in a stalemate.

After battling Han Xiao for a long while, Malekith's eyes lit up, and he said with great excitement, "You are even stronger than in the rumors. I am going to get serious now. Please don't die so easily."

Malekith was a battle maniac, and the pleasure from finding a partner to have a refreshing battle was even greater than mating.

The next moment, Malekith began chanting a demonic incantation, and the flames on his body burned even brighter and greater. His eyes seemed to be burning with flames, and a dark red flame burst forth from the gaps of his armor. His aura was elevated a notch, and the temperature of the surroundings rose rapidly with the atmosphere being contorted by the heat.

"Talent of the Demon Race, high grade True Liberation!" Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. When they were in such a state, the combat strength of the Demon Race would increase greatly. With Malekith's Calamity Grade strength, the increase to his strength was frightening.

Bang!

Han Xiao could see the ground beneath him passing by rapidly, and he was sent flying despite being in the Giant Ape Form. The next second, Malekith narrowed the gap between the both of them in an instant, and the dark purple flames surrounding Malekith lashed out like a blade toward Han Xiao's neck.

If Han Xiao was struck by that blow, his cervical vertebra would probably fracture and his entire body paralyzed. He would need half a second to recover from the blow, and this half a second would be sufficient for a Pugilist like Malekith to perform a simple combo.

Han Xiao deactivated the Giant Ape Form, and his entire body shrank down. The attack brushed past the top of his helmet with only millimeters to spare.

With his attack missing, Malekith locked his fingers together and was about to hammer Han Xiao toward the ground.

At this moment, Han Xiao's helmet suddenly opened up, and two flaming whirlpools could be seen in his eyes. The next instant, two balls of white flame shot out from his eyes toward Malekith.

Boom!

Malekith's attack was interrupted again.

There were different kinds of demons within the Demon Race. When they unleashed their True Liberation talent, the difference between the different races would become obvious. For example, the demons that spat fire would be Fire Demons, and the demons that spat ice would be Ice Demons. Malekith was obviously a Fire Demon, and his fire resistance would be extremely high. Thus, Han Xiao's attack was not able to deal much damage but was able to successfully push him back.

Han Xiao had loaded some Genetic Medicine into his mechanical suit, and he had injected himself with Befuli's Genetic Medicine previously to use his one-off Character Summon Card.

With the small window that Han Xiao created for himself, he did not hesitate in the slightest and activated the Berserk Overload Form of his mechanical suit!

The nuclear reactor of his mechanical suit revved up at full power, and his speed, strength, and weapons all received an increase in attributes!

Han Xiao placed his arms together, and his nano weapons module was activated. His arm transformed into a large cannon barrel, and a brilliant beam of light shot toward Malekith.

Boom!

Malekith tanked the cannon fire and continued his charge, raising his hands to send out balls of Shockwave Blasts.

Explosions surrounded the two as both of them exchanged fire, with one of them advancing and the other retreating. Malekith's speed rose rapidly after unleashing his True Liberation talent, and the distance between the two quickly closed up. Very soon, Malekith appeared before Han Xiao again.

His fist that was wrapped up in flames was aimed right at Han Xiao's chest.

Hum!

Right at this instant, Han Xiao's body exploded forth with a blinding electrical bolt, and his fists actually landed on Malekith's face first like a bolt of lightning.

Boom!

His fists exploded in midair like a bolt of violent lightning.

The shockwave of the attack spread out from underneath Han Xiao's feet in all directions and formed a crater that was a hundred meters in diameter!

As for Malekith, he was already a shooting star in the horizon that quickly disappeared from one's sight.

[Power Detonation]!

If the attack was a close ranged one, said attack would gain 650 to 700 percent additional damage, power detonation damage, and sputtering damage. On top of that, it gained a sixty-five percent chance of critical damage as well as the ability to inflict status effects like knock up, knock back, suppression, and dizziness.

He did not only use this skill but also activated [Gene Liberation]. This was [Flaming Will] that had been strengthened by the Skill Level-up Card!

The accumulated strength of this attack was truly frightening!

Malekith was sent flying a dozen kilometers at the very least!

He would probably fly for a day in the sky before landing on the ground!

"Huu... huu..."

Han Xiao panted lightly. Hand to hand combat drained him of his stamina the most. His HP and Energy were still at a healthy level, but his stamina had been exhausted greatly.

Thankfully, the higher one's stamina was, the faster the recovery rate.

"This fellow is truly powerful. He is much stronger than Degulish and Nagakin. I am afraid that my previous blow was only able to give him light injuries."

Han Xiao wondered if he should continue the battle, and all of a sudden, he remembered Malekith's origin.

"A core officer of the Bloodshed Land, one of the eight Vanguard Officials under Heber. He is the subordinate of a beyond Grade A Super‽"

Han Xiao immediately became wary. Why would the officer of another beyond Grade A Super fight him?

At that moment, a large trail of dust could be seen from the wilderness, and it was Malekith running back from afar. This time, he did not charge forward but stopped a few meters away from Han Xiao. He had already deactivated his True Liberation state, and there was a red fist mark on his face.

"Well done, Black Star. You are an opponent worthy of my full strength. I truly enjoyed our battle." Malekith revealed a smile of admiration.

Even when in the True Liberation state, he was not able to suppress the opponent entirely and had even taken a small loss. Black Star was extremely powerful and even more powerful than people thought.

The objective of his visit had been met.

"I know your status already. Malekith, a member of the Bloodshed Land." Han Xiao did not want to continue fighting and only wanted to know Malekith's objective. "Why did you ambush me? Why would you appear here?"

"I am here specially for you."

Black Star was one of the Dragon Emperor's trusted aides, and the Black Star Army had become extremely famous recently. He had been instructed to observe Black Star and find a chance to test him.

When the Purple Snake Space Pirates abducted the mercenaries of the Black Star Army, the intelligence net of the Bloodshed Land had picked up this piece of news. Since Malekith was nearby, he had decided to snatch the spaceship of the pirates and wait for Black Star to find him. Then, he would be able to test Black Star's strength without anyone disturbing them.

If he was sufficiently powerful...

"Floating Dragon would only bury a talent like you. You should have greater ambition. With your strength, it is sufficient for you to be equal to me and become the ninth Vanguard Official." Malekith revealed his intentions and extended an olive branch. "So... are you willing to join the Bloodshed Land?"

Chapter 596: Stalling and Luring

Surprised, Han Xiao sized up Malekith from head to toe.

"You're here to poach?"

Han Xiao did not expect this at all. After all, he was an officer of Floating Dragon—regular forces would not be so reckless. Now, a core officer of Bloodshed Land had come to invite him and offered him a very high position as one of the Vanguard Officials as soon as he joined.

The Bloodshed Land and Floating Dragon were on different levels. Floating Dragon had always been supported by Ames' reputation alone. However, not only was Tyrant Heber Beyond Grade A, he was also the most senior among the four Beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring. The Pugilist class trained one's body and elevated one's life, so his life span was very long. Hence, the one thing that was Floating Dragon's biggest strength, Bloodshed Land had it too.

Furthermore, Bloodshed Land was an important ally of a Star Cluster civilization. They had rich resources, wide connections, and very strong military power. They had created many divisions in various Star Systems in another Star Cluster. Just from its size alone, it was already a giant in the Shattered Star Ring. Plus, unlike Floating Dragon, which was uncompetitive, they were still actively expanding.

For example, in the previous set of Wayne Cards' Shattered Star Ring card set, there were three cards under the Floating Dragon Island camp: Force Card [Floating Dragon Island], Individual Card ['Dragon Emperor' Ames], and Mercenary Card [Black Star Mercenary Group]. As for Bloodshed Land, there were fourteen cards under their camp!

I've been attracting quite the attention lately and shown my abilities—that's probably the reason I'm being noticed by stronger people.

Although things like this were rare, it was not unprecedented. Once Renown and Legendary Points reached a certain level, there was a chance for similar events to occur. All kinds of people would approach when one was famous.

The fact that Bloodshed Land had come to scout him proved that his position had gradually increased.

"I'm a little curious, aren't you people afraid that this will anger Ames?" Han Xiao smirked.

Malekith gave a faint smile, showing his absolute confidence. "You think that his excellency Tyrant would be afraid of Ames? Plus, this isn't the first time."

Han Xiao immediately grew curious. "You people poached someone from Floating Dragon before? Is that person still alive?"

"Of course he's alive, and his position now is very high."

"Did Ames not act on it?"

"Hmm, you do know her very well. Indeed she did. Back then, she dragged Floating Dragon Island along and fought her way through to our headquarters. Then, His Excellency Tyrant struck."

"How did it end up?" Han Xiao's eyebrows raised.

Malekith smirked with great admiration and said, "The original Floating Dragon Island was double its size now."

Ames had the lower hand...

This was a piece of secret information unknown to players in his previous life. It turned out that there was beef between Floating Dragon and Bloodshed Land. No wonder they had come to poach from Ames.

Wait a minute, if I reject the offer, will Bloodshed Land see me as an enemy?

Han Xiao became alert and asked in a serious tone, "Thank you for your invitation, but what if I refuse?"

Malekith wiped away his smile and stared at Han Xiao. His tone became assertive as he slowly said, "Reconsider it."

The hundreds of thousands of immortals under Black Star had attracted the attention of Bloodshed Land, but Heber rejected slowly convincing them one after another, so their leader Han Xiao had become the target.

Malekith did not want to return empty-handed with the mission given by the Tyrant personally.

Now, this is threatening...

Han Xiao frowned and slowly measured the pros and cons.

If he turned to Bloodshed Land, he would face the fury of Floating Dragon. The connections that he had made because of Floating Dragon would all disappear, and the Black Star Army and Planet Aquamarine would all lose their privileges with Floating Dragon. To Ames, he was quite important. Once he betrayed her, she would be even more furious, and the consequences would be dire.

The pros... seemed quite high too. The risk was accompanied by profit. Bloodshed Land's forces were much stronger than Floating Dragon's. He could build even wider connections, and Bloodshed Land could provide even better support to Black Star Army with their resources, he would be able to regain all the losses he made. The only problem was, he might have to move to the Star Cluster that Bloodshed Land was in to expand and develop.

Since Heber dared invite me, if Ames' revenge is successful, Heber will lose a lot of reputation. So, Heber will probably protect me at all costs...

After some consideration, Han Xiao said, "I've thought about it."

His brows loosened, and he smiled at Malekith.

"I decline."

Although he had analyzed the pros and cons out of habit, it was nothing more than a habit. Han Xiao had never planned to leave Floating Dragon from the beginning, and he was not someone so easily convinced.

Ames had provided him with so much help, all favors, and their relationship had been slowly but surely building. If it switched to Heber, he would have to build a relationship with his boss once again. Furthermore, the title 'Tyrant' did not sound very friendly. Bloodshed Land had way more rules than Floating Dragon, so it was impossible for them to show tolerance as Ames did for him.

Most importantly... I'm the one and only leader of the Floating Dragon Field Team. It'd be crazy for me to go to your place and be your number nine!

Malekith's smile completely vanished, and he glared at Han Xiao directly with a cold expression.

Han Xiao did not retreat and stared back while secretly prepared for combat.

The atmosphere became stiff.

Just as Han Xiao thought they were going to have a battle, Malekith suddenly snorted heavily and walked away.

Han Xiao loosened up and exhaled through his mouth.

It seemed like there was not going to be a fight. Black Star Army was going through a very important phase of its development, so it was best not to be on bad terms with Bloodshed Land.

This time, a spaceship with the marking of Bloodshed Land flew there from the sky. This was Malekith's real ship, hidden on the other side of the planet.

Malekith walked up the stairs. Suddenly, he stopped the hatch that was about to close, looked at Han Xiao, and said with a deep voice, "Black Star, we will meet again very soon."

Then, without concern about Han Xiao's reaction, he let go of the hatch and let it close. Bloodshed Land's spaceship quickly rose up and disappeared.

Meet again very soon... What does that mean? They're going to find a chance to deal with me? Or does it mean something else?

"Never mind, Bloodshed Land's territory isn't in Colton Star Cluster anyway, so it's very unlikely for them to come here for me. Since Floating Dragon and Bloodshed Land are peacefully coexisting, they definitely will not make big moves because of me."

Han Xiao shook his head. After he thought it through, he was not worried about it anymore.

"Right, I'm here to hand over the hostage." He suddenly remembered his original reason for being there.

After fighting with Malekith, he had almost forgotten the purpose of this trip.

Han Xiao went back to near the galactic pirate spaceship. Befuli was lying on the ground not moving, surrounded by a few lightly injured galactic pirates. They glanced at the BlackLight Stealth hovering above them. It looked like they were uncertain as to whether they should take Befuli away or not.

Upon hearing the footsteps, these galactic pirates turned around and saw Han Xiao walking toward them. They shivered as fear emerged in their eyes. Their bodies stiffened on the spot, and they did not dare move even an inch.

Initially, they did not have to meet, so their safety was ensured, but now that Han Xiao was right in front of them, they were afraid that would be the end of their lives. Furthermore, Befuli's skeletal appearance horrified them. They did not know what torture Befuli had gone through for him to end up like that, but they were certain that they did not want to experience the same.

Han Xiao glanced at them and casually grabbed a galactic pirate. They walked up the pillaging ship. The galactic pirate pointed the way, shivering, and they soon arrived at the prison cell.

However, the cell was empty.

"Where are my people‽" demanded Han Xiao with a threatening tone as he pressed onto the galactic pirate's scalp, tightening his fingers slowly.

"I—I don't know... they disappeared one and a half days ago!"

Feeling like his head was going to explode, the galactic pirate quickly explained.

Disappeared? Han Xiao raised his eyebrows. Then it occurred to him. Damn it, these kids logged off! He let go of the galactic pirate.

They probably went to sleep.

"One and a half days ago, which means they'll be coming online pretty soon. I could wait for a while..."

Han Xiao realized a problem, and he grabbed the galactic pirate's head once again.

"The hostages are gone, but you still want to make the deal. Are you mocking me?"

The galactic pirate was on the verge of crying.

We were all controlled by that demon. How could we tell you?

This time, flashes of white light appeared in the cell. A few Guild of Gods players came online and saw Black Star immediately—they were overjoyed.

"Quick, tell the leader. The Hidden Storyline is finally here!"

Less than twenty seconds later, more white light flashed. Jupiter and the others came online at the same time. They were all thrilled to see Han Xiao.

"What?" The galactic pirate rubbed his eyes to make sure that he was not hallucinating.

Han Xiao opened the cell and took the others out of the spaceship, throwing the galactic pirate in his hands onto the ground.

"Contact Sykes, our deal remains."

The shock on this galactic pirate's face turned into surprise.

The hostages had been snatched away, and they were in Black Star's hands. There was nothing to threaten him. Yet, Black Star still wanted to let them go and give them Befuli?

"Yo—You still want to carry out the deal?" A galactic pirate could not help but ask. It was hard to believe.

"What, do you not want to?" Han Xiao asked back.

"No no no, you misunderstood, let's go according to the deal." The galactic pirates hastily denied it. They were filled with the joy of escaping death.

A galactic pirate quickly contacted Sykes and explained the situation.

Sykes was stunned. He had never expected Bloodshed Land's people to interfere, which completely came out of nowhere.

However, even though the deal was affected, Black Star surprisingly did not change his mind...

Were my threats effective?

Sykes could only think of this as the reason.

He suddenly felt much better about himself. Haha, I managed to threaten someone so renowned.

Without caring about the communication between the galactic pirates, Han Xiao took Jupiter and the others aside, had the BlackLight Stealth land, and opened the hatch.

"You guys go into the ship. Risda will take you to the nearest city planet."

Jupiter's eyes gleamed and passionately said, "We want to help you to fight the enemies. Please let us assist you."

This was such a rare opportunity. He felt that he could definitely trigger the hidden mission.

Han Xiao saw right through Jupiter's intentions. Speechless, he wrote a mission on the spot and gave it to these players.

You have triggered Hidden Mission [Retreat]

Mission Introduction: You've been dragged into a storm, but you still can't interfere with your current strength. What you need to do now is retreat from here as soon as possible.

Mission Requirements: Leave in the BlackLight Stealth

Reward: 350,000 Experience, +200 Black Star Army Favorability

"Let's go!" Jupiter turned around and walked into BlackLight Stealth without hesitation.

The Guild of Gods players followed and all boarded.

Poseidon gave Jupiter a thumbs up. "If we boarded the ship without saying anything, we wouldn't have triggered this mission. Thank you, leader."

Jupiter smiled smugly and pointed at his temple. "This is experience. Learn from it."

Although this mission was quite different from what he had thought it would be, Jupiter felt that it was very likely a high level event after he read the mission introduction, but they did not meet the requirements to trigger it. Hence, it had become [Retreat]. Although it was quite a shame that was the case, they could only follow the mission. It was better than nothing, after all.

Han Xiao was still standing outside waiting for the galactic pirate's reply.

After a while, a galactic pirate trotted over and cautiously said, "Your Excellency Black Star, if there's nothing else, we will be taking Befuli away."

"Go, don't mess with me again. I won't let you go next time." Han Xiao waved and boarded his spaceship.

Only then did the galactic pirate breathe a sigh of relief. He quickly went back and notified his friends. They started up the pillage ship, hovering above the surface.

Just as the pillage ship was about to speed up and take off, behind the BlackLight Stealth hatch, gray light appeared in Han Xiao's eyes. He activated his Racial Talent and turned into Chaos Body. His physical form was gone, and he turned into gray fog.

Advanced Void Travel!

Entering the Void Vision, time seemed to have stopped. Han Xiao controlled his Chaos Body and left the BlackLight Stealth. As the duration of [Advanced Void Travel] was longer, he had more than enough time to cross a large distance and go near the pillaging ship.

Void Travel allowed him to go through walls. His Chaos Body went directly through the pillaging ship hatch, then found a distant cabin to hide. He deactivated Void Travel, without triggering the alarm, without getting noticed by the galactic pirates.

Hu!

The next moment, the pillaging ship quickly rose into the sky and flew away.

Chapter 597: Behind Enemy Lines Alone

The BlackLight Stealth took Jupiter and the others to the nearest planet with a city.

Jupiter and the others walked around the interior of the spaceship curiously. This was Black Star's personal spaceship, and it was extremely rare for players to board it.

Risda locked up the doors to a large portion of the spaceship, and the players were only able to explore some unimportant public regions.

"This spaceship must be extremely precious, right?" Poseidon muttered.

"I searched it before. This spaceship is the model of an advanced civilization." Jupiter nodded in agreement.

Now that the players had their own communicators, they could connect to the galactic network, getting rid of their status as a backward aboriginals. All the various channels of information were finally opened to them, and their knowledge increased every day. Together with Phillip's ability to search the web, they were able to search for any information they wished, and the players gradually grew used to searching for any questions they had.

"A spaceship is far too expensive. Who knows when we will be able to afford one?" Poseidon shook his head.

"Not necessarily. As long as we complete a few missions and raise some funds from the guild, it would be possible for us to buy a basic spaceship."

Jupiter was the guild leader of a prestigious club and would always have some plans. The resources that he had control over were also something that an ordinary player would not be able to compare to. A spaceship that had a sky-high price in the player's eyes was just about achievable as long as he gathered funds from the guild. After all, the guild of a club was essentially a company. All the core members of the guild were employees of the guild, and redistributing resources was an extremely simple affair.

He was considering the type of advantage having a spaceship earlier would bring him and whether it was worth the resources.

Right at that moment, a core member with the name of 'Michael' said, "Guild Master, we can actually buy a functional model instead. I previously checked the market for materials and fuel. Many large corporations are collecting these resources without any limit. While the prices are low, the profits are stable."

Jupiter's eyes lit up, and he said, "You mean we should buy a mining spaceship?"

"Yes, we should organize a mining expedition and mine for resources on an uninhabited planet. We can then sell these resources to earn a steady profit."

"We wouldn't be able to recover our costs too quickly at the start," Michael added. "However, if we complete missions while mining for resources, we would be able to gather enough funds to purchase more mining spaceships. After a period of accumulation, our profits will increase and snowball. If we can form a whole fleet of mining spaceships, our profits will definitely increase exponentially."

Jupiter was moved by this proposition. "So, the earlier we buy a mining spaceship the greater our profits?"

"That's right." Michael nodded. "Presently, everyone is focused on completing employment missions, and the benefits are plentiful. However, unions like Dynasty and King City, which are able to mobilize a large number of players, will be looking for other ways to make money as well. Time waits for no one."

Apart from making money, their responsibility as the guild of a club was also to provide better logistical support for the professional players. Jupiter could not help but fall into deep thought.

Poseidon then looked at Michael and said, "Are you in cahoots with the members of the other guilds? Quickly exit the group chat to prove your innocence!"

"Scram to the side." Michael showed his middle finger in response.

Poseidon then looked at the luxurious interior of the spaceship and said, "Wouldn't we be able to make heaps of profit by snatching this spaceship? We should be able to leave Dynasty far behind in the dust."

Everyone looked at him speechlessly.

"You are actually the spy, right?" Michael teased back in response.

"Tsk, a casual remark of mine has all of you so anxious." Poseidon clicked his tongue in response.

...

Going from the pickup point to the Fawn Star System required one to go through a few stargates, and the journey was not a short one.

However, in order to get rid of Sykes, a hidden danger, Han Xiao decided to wait patiently.

The pirates' spaceship was flying in space, and Han Xiao's Chaos Body was stuck to the wall of the spaceship in a very concealed spot. This made Han Xiao realize that the talent of the Chaos Observer was extremely suitable for conducting such non-rigorous stealth operations. To him, any operation that did not end up with him silencing all eye witnesses was considered non-rigorous.

Because he was currently in his Chaos Body form, Han Xiao did not have anything to do. As such, he could only scroll through the forums every day and understand how the players were doing in their various missions through the posts. Because they had not entered the galaxy for a long time, the players were pretty obedient, and most of the missions went pretty smoothly. Everything was also going smoothly with the 200,000 mercenaries on Planet Sunil.

The situation made Han Xiao feel at ease.

Apart from looking through the forums, Han Xiao spent his time looking through the [Observer's Mark]. He spied on Aroshia, Serbia the Fifth, and Herlous to pass the time.

After around ten days, the pirate ship finally left the Garton Star System and entered the Fawn Star System. Soon, they linked up together with the main troops.

The Purple Snake Space Pirates had more than forty battleships with the majority being small to medium sized pillaging ships. The flagship was a modified Crow Grade battleship, which was the main battleship model in the Fawn Star System. A space pirate fleet of such a scale was not one to be underestimated.

The spaceship flew into the fleet and met up with the flagship. A few space pirates supported the feeble Befuli through the walkway to the main hall of the flagship. Sykes was already waiting there with all his subordinates filling up the main hall. The other three Grade B Officers were standing beside him.

The moment Sykes saw the frail Befuli, he stood up abruptly and ran over with a questioning gaze.

"Befuli, how were you reduced to such a state?"

Befuli looked at Sykes with his lips trembling and tears in his eyes. He said in a choking tone, "Black Star is a demon!"

"What exactly did he do to you?" Sykes sized Befuli up from head to toe. In his memory, Befuli was a burly well-built man, but the Befuli before him looked like a rack of bones that would crumble at any moment.

Not just him, even the other space pirates looked over with disbelief in their eyes. They did not dare believe that this powerful comrade of theirs would be reduced to such a state.

Just what could have happened that would reduce a Grade B Super to such a state‽

The moment Befuli thought about his hell-like days, he could not help but reveal a face full of fear as he trembled.

"He... he locked me up in a dark cabin, and I don't even know how long had passed since then. He used some equipment to extract my Super-Gene, and my recovery speed became slower and slower. Even now, I have only been able to recover a little bit..."

Those who had strength would fear losing it the most. Every time he recovered a bit of strength, it would be mercilessly taken away from him again. After experiencing this endless loop of hopelessness together with the fact that he was locked up in a dark chamber, he lost all sense of time and suffered a huge psychological blow.

Upon hearing that, Sykes could not help but tremble slightly and regret his decision of provoking Black Star.

He had never imagined that Black Star was not only powerful but a pervert as well!

Sykes had only taken the risk to threaten Black Star because of Befuli's strength as a Grade B Super. However, Befuli was as good as crippled already and would need a long time to recover. Sykes only needed a useful Officer, not a crippled subordinate.

Even the other Officers who had friction with Befuli could not help but feel a sense of fear in their hearts when seeing Befuli in such a state.

"Black Star probably insisted on doing this exchange by making use of Befuli as an example to threaten us," another Grade B space pirate said.

Sykes nodded heavily.

"What are we going to do now? Are we not going to take revenge for Befuli?" someone suddenly asked from within the crowd.

Sykes face immediately darkened. He naturally did not wish to provoke Black Star again, but he was truly put in a tight spot at the moment. If he said that he did not want to get revenge on Black Star, would it not make him lose his prestige and leadership abilities?

"I have my own plans." Helpless, Sykes could only give a vague reply and attempt to change the topic.

Right at that moment, the same individual asked again, "What kind of plan? What exactly will we do?"

You again! Can't you just shut up!

"Is this something that you have the right to ask?" Sykes expression was ugly as he looked in the direction of the voice. He wanted to see which subordinate of his dared talk back to him.

Seeing their boss flying into a rage, all the space pirates made way to reveal the individual who was talking. The gazes of all the pirates in the room were also drawn over to this individual.

Eh... he seems like a member of the Galaxy Human Race, wearing a black windbreaker, and his looks... eh? Why does he look so familiar?

Sykes glared at this individual with doubt in his eyes. The next moment, the doubt turned into shock, and he let out a loud roar.

"Black Star! What are you doing here‽"

All the space pirates in the surroundings jumped away as though they had seen a ghost, and the area around Han Xiao became empty.

The entire hall became silent and Han Xiao looked at Sykes. Stroking his chin, he said slowly, "You don't need to be anxious. I am here to make a deal with you."

"What deal?"

"I want you to pay the price of freedom in exchange for..." Han Xiao snickered. "Your life!"

Buzz! Pa!

Just as he finished his sentence, he equipped the Berserk Ape suit immediately and took out his High Energy Concentrated Particle Cannon. The blast from the cannon broke through from the interior of the spaceship and out into space.

The suction force from the vacuum came like a powerful gust, and the pirates in the spaceship were all sucked out by the frightening suction force and thrown into space. A portion of the weaker Supers froze up immediately with their blood vessels rupturing. The environment of space was fatal to some low-grade Supers.

Only Sykes and a couple of the more powerful pirates were able to stabilize their bodies and resist the suction force. Only those who were at Grade B were able to barely endure the treacherous space climate.

The mechanical suit had its own regulation mechanism, and space did not affect him in the slightest as he floated in space.

Sykes had a face full of fury as his mouth opened like he was roaring. However, the violent gust from air being sucked out of the spaceship completely drowned out his voice.

Without saying another word, Han Xiao sent his fist toward the alloy ground and activated the Power Detonation skill!

Boom!

The shockwave of his punch spread out in all directions with bolts of lightning accompanying it, shattering the alloy floor!

With the shockwave spreading, the destruction of the spaceship hastened, and hole enlarged even further.

Without solid ground beneath their feet, all the pirates apart from Sykes were sucked out. Only Sykes was able to send out a sticky, purplish substance toward the alloy wall to stabilize himself.

This sticky, purplish gel-like substance was Sykes' Esper ability. This sticky gel was extremely poisonous and corrosive. It was also able to solidify in an instant to take the shape of various things. Furthermore, the purplish gel excreted could be stored for a very long time. Sykes could control the corrosiveness of this purplish gel, and this was where his title of 'Purple Snake' came from.

Despite Sykes being an Esper, he had his own armor as well. However, because he was not a Mechanic, the armor could not be compressed into a compressed orb. At this moment, his armor was in his personal storeroom.

While he hated Han Xiao to the core, he knew that the most urgent matter was for him to put on his armor. At the very least, he would be able to move around in space freely with it. He immediately made use of his purplish gel to scale the wall and sprint toward his personal store room.

Hu!

Han Xiao's thrusters were activated, leaving behind two trials of fire as he rapidly approached Sykes.

Right at that moment, Sykes waved his arm, and a wave of purplish gel shot toward him. As it came into contact with the walls of the spaceship, thick purple smoke was released as the alloy walls melted.

This ability is interesting. Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and his arm transformed to reveal a pipe.

The inside of the spaceship had not become a vacuum yet, and air was sucked into his mechanical suit through the nanoparticles. The air that was sucked in was then channeled to the pipe, and a high-pressure air cannon was fired to scatter the wave of purplish gel.

The corrosive gel splattered everywhere, and the entire place became filled with smoke.

Han Xiao sped up further and caught onto one of Sykes's arms.

Mechanical Force exploded from his entire body, and his thrusters started to shoot flames in the opposite direction. He then grabbed onto Sykes' arm and got into a throwing posture.

Berserk Throw!

...

"Will the flagship please respond! Please respond! What is the current status?"

The ships of the Purple Snake Space Pirates surrounded the flagship in space.

A few seconds ago, they had all lost contact with the flagship and could not get a response no matter how hard they tried.

Just when the ships were about to board the flagship to check what had gone wrong, the exterior armor of the flagship suddenly exploded, leaving a large hole behind. All the junk items from within the flagship were sucked into space, and many of their comrades were included.

Before the other spaceships could react, a large hole was also created at the bottom of the spaceship over a thousand meters away from the main hall. Broken metal bits and a human figure were sent flying out of the hole. That human figure was their boss, Sykes!

Sykes had been sent flying through half the flagship with a single Berserk Throw from Han Xiao!

Chapter 598: Man vs. Fleet

It had all happened so quickly and so suddenly that the galactic pirates inside the pillaging ships around were stunned for a moment. When their boss Sykes were rolling in the vacuum space, only then did they realize that this was an attack.

"Quick! Help boss!"

"The enemy should be in the main ship. Surround it and don't let him get away!"

As the galactic pirates yelled at each other, two pillaging ships closed in on Sykes, and the rest of the pillaging ships quickly formed a surrounding formation.

Through the porthole, Han Xiao saw the pillaging ships turn around and aim their cannons at him. Unworried, he smiled and contacted Phillip in his helmet.

"Phillip, assist me in virtual hacking."

"Order confirmed. Switching to virtual sights, hum..."

The tactical screen inside the helmet showed the hacking interface with a complex data stream. Green beams of light shot out from the chest of the mechanical suit and formed a virtual control panel. Han Xiao quickly typed the code.

The first one that he was going to hack was the Purple Snake Space Pirates' main ship that he was on.

_____________________

You have used [Virtual Intrusion] on Purple Snake Battleship.

Beginning to crack firewall (Level 2).

Undergoing level 1 authentication... Authentication passed!

Undergoing level 2 authentication... Authentication passed!

Intrusion successful! You have obtained the operational authority of Purple Snake!

Authority Level: Highest

Data has been sampled!

Backup generation complete!

+10% Success Rate, +25% Speed when hacking machinery controlled by the same artificial intelligence.

Your authority has been blocked by the other party's artificial intelligence, undergoing authentication... Authentication successful!

You have successfully retained your privileges!

Time till next authentication: 140 seconds

_____________________

The artificial intelligence used by the galactic pirate spaceship was clearly way worse than DarkStar's—their firewall was only level two. Han Xiao was already Calamity Grade, and his virtual hacking ability was also largely enhanced. Hacking a galactic pirate spaceship was a piece of cake, and he immediately obtained the highest authority level.

The higher the authority level obtained on the first intrusion, the lower the difficulty of hacking, and vice versa. This meant that the artificial intelligence of Purple Snake Space Pirates was no match at all.

The model of Purple Snake appeared on the control panel; all the modules were usable. Han Xiao clicked on the shield module.

"Activate shield with full power output."

The next moment, an oval-shaped light blue electromagnetic shield shrouded the entire spaceship.

Dong! Dong!

Outside the porthole, the tens of pillaging ships started firing immediately after seeing the shield activated. Cannons exploded on the shield nonstop, and the inside of the spaceship was trembling.

"The shield can last a few minutes, so there's more than enough time."

Without any worry or panic, Han Xiao started to hack the other targets.

He did not throw Sykes out just because he wanted to but to obtain control of this main ship and defend against the focus fire from the galactic pirates.

Sykes was one of the weaker ones in the Calamity Grade, so Han Xiao had a very high chance of winning if it was a duel. However, this was not a duel.

He was facing an entire galactic pirate fleet!

Han Xiao's initial plan was to snatch an advantageous location and make use of his ability as a Virtual Mechanic!

Not far away, Sykes was still floating in space. Although he could move by using energy, he was not a Pugilist, and his Esper ability did not enhance his movement speed.

As soon as he turned, he saw two pillaging ships piloted by his subordinates approaching that were clearly there to fetch him. Sykes' eyes gleamed, he used his energy and approached them.

Only at this moment did Sykes have the time to think of what to do next.

He initially did not want to become Han Xiao's foe, but now that Han Xiao had approached him, this could no longer be resolved peacefully. They were enemies!

Sykes was boiling, clenching his teeth. The fact that Han Xiao had come alone made him feel like Han Xiao did not take Purple Snake Space Pirates seriously at all.

Since that was the case, he would get rid of Black Star immediately without caring about anything else!

Murderous intent appeared in Sykes's mind.

The two pillaging ships finally drew close, so Sykes stopped his train of thought and prepared to wait for his subordinates to open the hatch for him.

Suddenly, something unexpected happened!

The two pillaging ships fired light cannons one after another, toward Sykes. His vision instantly became filled with white as a sense of burning quickly approached.

Sykes's expression changed drastically!

Inside the under fire Purple Snake, two more virtual models of pillaging ships appeared on Han Xiao's control panel. He had noticed the spaceships heading toward Sykes long ago, so he had first obtained authority over them. He did not want Sykes to end up in another ship.

His fingers danced on the control panel so quickly they left blurry silhouettes behind—his typing speed was astounding, and the artificial intelligence of the pillaging ship was no match. The pillaging ships became Han Xiao's one after another. Fewer and fewer attacks were aimed at the main ship. Instead, the pillaging ships controlled by Han Xiao started firing at the other galactic pirates. The galactic pirates were in a panic.

A Calamity Grade Virtual Mechanic could easily deal with an entire galactic pirate fleet alone!

This was especially so in the late stages of the Mechanic class, when at this level, their combat capability was extraordinary, able to adapt to both duels and team fights.

The situation changed completely. A few people realized that things were going south and immediately escaped with their ships. There was no such word as 'loyalty' in the galactic pirates' dictionary.

The battle lasted more than ten minutes. The cannon fire gradually lessened. Other than the spaceships that escaped or were destroyed, all the other spaceships were now controlled by Han Xiao.

Han Xiao walked through the captured ships one by one and carried out the remaining work—dealing with the galactic pirates inside. Some stronger ones were not killed, including the Grade B officers of the galactic pirate group. They were all tied and thrown into the Purple Snake. As for the hole in the ship, it had already been repaired by maintenance robots.

Capturing Sykes was not much trouble—Han Xiao used many ships and focused their fired on him. Although the power of the cannons of those spaceships was thousands of miles away from the DarkStar main cannon, they had the quantity to make up for it. Sykes had a huge mobility problem in space, so it was very difficult for him to dodge. He was basically a live target. It was brutal, and even Han Xiao did not have the heart to watch it.

After making sure that Sykes was almost done for, only then did Han Xiao control the spaceship to drag Sykes back to Purple Snake. He then threw him aside with the other galactic pirates.

"Bo—Boss..."

All the captured galactic pirates looked at the burnt, almost dead Sykes. They could not help but feel terrified.

Grade As rarely became galactic pirates. The unity of the Purple Snake Space Pirates came from how strong Sykes was—he made his subordinates feel very confident.

However, Sykes had easily been defeated, so his strong image in their mind had shattered.

The more they admired Sykes before, the more they were afraid of Han Xiao now.

"Some escaped, but they were all unimportant minions."

Han Xiao stood in front of them as he took off his Berserk Ape. All living galactic pirates were before him, so there was no need to hack anything anymore. The spaceship was in his hands.

Taking account of the spaceships that had escaped, he had seized twenty-four spaceships. Although most of them were cheap pillaging ships, there was the main ship that was a Grade Crow battleship, so it was not a bad return.

Sykes was heavily injured; his limbs were all locked by electromagnetic cuffs. He lay sideways on the floor and glared at Han Xiao with hatred and rage.

"Don't look at me like that. You messed with someone, so you should have been prepared for this." Han Xiao shrugged.

Sykes chortled with despair, speechless.

"Calamity Grade Supers should be able to last longer," Han Xiao murmured.

He was not going to go easy on a captive. With bright eyes, he took out the Super-Gene Extractor and approached Sykes step by step.

Seeing Han Xiao's passionate eyes, Sykes suddenly felt a chill run down his spine. He then recalled Befuli's terrifying state, and his expression instantly changed. Trying to be tough, he yelled, "Don't come closer! I will kill you! I will kill you for sure! Don't! Don—"

Han Xiao ignored it all and plunged the Super-Gene Extractor right into Sykes' veins, extracting his Super-Gene. The product was three tubes of dark red Ability Potions, thick as blood.

Sykes felt a sense of weakness coming directly from his bones. The little energy he had left was gone. The Esper power that he was so used to using could not be sensed anymore. It was like he had suddenly lost his body's senses, and he panicked.

This time, Han Xiao took out a fresh new Ability Potion and gulped it down.

Sykes' entire body trembled. Looking at Han Xiao gobbling his blood, he was submerged in horror. His eyes widened, and his lips shivered.

Not just him, all the other captive galactic pirates saw this and felt terrified and uneasy.

_____________________

You have received [Character Summon Card - Sykes (Temporary)]

[Character Summon Card - Sykes (Temporary)]: Purple Poison - Tide

Release a large amount of liquid poison, spreading out in all directions from the user. This acidic poison causes continuous damage every five seconds. The poison will not disappear after being released. It can be used to form acidic terrain or reused.

Damage: 580 – 920

This Character Summon Card will expire in 15 days.

_____________________

Skills had many abilities. The abilities extracted by the Ability Potion were random, but they were all different ways to use the Esper power.

This was the type of Esper ability that could produce physical materials. Although it was comparatively weak in battle, the produced materials would not disappear, so there were many more ways to use it.

The destructive power of this Esper ability is actually really high. As long as he has enough time, he can make enough poisonous liquid to cover an entire land or even an entire planet, making it lifeless...

The way Han Xiao looked at Sykes changed. It was like he was looking at a biochemical weapon, with slight disappointment.

You have such a strong Esper ability, but you chose to be a galactic pirate‽

Not long after, Ability Potions were made from all the captive galactic pirates. Han Xiao checked all the abilities then imprisoned everyone. Sykes received special treatment from him.

The Purple Snake Space Pirates have finally been dealt with. That cost me more than half a month...

Han Xiao looked on the forums. Other than Planet Sunil, the other players' first mission had mostly been completed. Most of them were successful, with a few of them triggered new events, but most of them had returned to Base No.1 to receive new missions. While doing so, they also updated their equipment and brought Han Xiao another wave of profit. Everything was on the right path.

I got more than twenty ships this time. Maybe fighting galactic pirates is also a way to make a fortune, Han Xiao pondered. He had not been strong enough back then, but now that he was Calamity Grade, regular galactic pirates would be a piece of cake. Not only could he take their spaceships, he could also capture the galactic pirates and turn them into sources for Ability Potions or even exchange them for bounties.

Sykes had a bounty of 2.8 million Enas in Black Raven Civilization, but Han Xiao did not plan to exchange him for the bounty now. He wanted to drain Sykes dry first before giving him in for the bounty.

After arranging the loot, Han Xiao brought along the twenty or so spaceships and headed back to Garton Star System.

...

A few days after Han Xiao left, when the escaped Purple Snake galactic pirates shared their experience, only then did the Fawn Star System hear about this. Black Star had beaten up the entire Purple Snake Space Pirates alone!

This was not big news but not insignificant either. The Purple Snake Space Pirates had constantly been committing crimes in the Fawn Star System, so they were quite well known. When such a large galactic pirate group was defeated by a single person, there was quite a number of people who paid attention to it and were curious about the reasons.

Some people said that Sykes kidnapped Black Star Army's people, some said that this was a hire accepted by Black Star, and some even said that Black Star was picking on galactic pirates to rob resources and the Purple Snake Space Pirates were the victims instead. All sorts of rumors were going around.

No matter what, a large group of galactic pirates being defeated was a good thing for the citizens of Fawn Star System.

Black Raven Civilization received this news and waited for Black Star to approach them and exchange the prisoner for a bounty, while they could take this opportunity to form a relationship with the rising Black Star.

However, after waiting for many days, they received the message that Han Xiao had returned to the Garton Star System.

The employees of the Bounty Department of Black Raven Civilization were confused. Black Star isn't coming to change for bounty. Does he not want it?

Since he does not want the bounty and the Purple Snake Space Pirates are gone, does that mean we can just cancel the bounty?

This was common. When some wanted criminal was killed and no one came to claim the bounty, the bounty would be considered complete.

However, this was denied by the superiors of the related departments in Black Raven Civilization. They decided to keep the bounty and wait for Black Star to claim it.

There were many reasons. One was to use this opportunity to bond with Black Star. This amount of money was going to be there waiting for Black Star to claim it, so he would most likely come in the future.

Another reason was that they were interested in the relationship between Black Star and Godora. When Black Star was attacked by DarkStar back in the day, the Dragon Emperor had acted and shocked the world.

In that incident, Black Raven Civilization's competition, the Holy Stone Civilization, seemed to have some sort of dispute with Black Star. This was an opportunity, and if they could get a connection with Godora from Black Star, they could be above the Holy Stone Civilization.

With Han Xiao's current position and fame, every move he made was connected to the nerves of many forces. What he represented was no longer just himself.

Chapter 599: Stepping onto the Right Path and Expanding Blueprints

Back on Planet Golden Gate...

The round trip had taken him close to a month. The twenty-four spaceships that Han Xiao had taken returned to Base No. 1. The pillaging ships were smaller in size, and after modifying the messy coating on their exteriors, these were absorbed into the assault fleet.

The Crow Grade ship was on the same grade as a Violent Falcon Grade battleship, so it was stored in the hangar. After it was repaired, it could be put into use.

Including those spaceships, Han Xiao had close to a hundred spaceships under his fleet. It was divided into four divisions. One was the strategic core division that was made of the Fortress Grade flagship alone. The second was the battleship division formed by Violent Falcon Grade and Crow Grade ships, in charge of guarding and direct combat. The third was the assault fleet formed by the seized DarkStar assault ships and the galactic pirate pillaging ships, with speed superiority. The fourth was the rented carrier spaceship division used to transport manpower.

As for the BlackLight Stealth, it was for Han Xiao and Han Xiao only. Made by the Federation of Light, its grade and performance were way ahead of all other spaceships in the Black Star Army. Also, Risda was not willing to let too many people use his body.

Watching the last spaceship being parked in the hangar, Han Xiao had Phillip close its gate and locked Sykes and the other captives in the secret cell of Base No.1.

This cell had been built from an extremely strong alloy, covered with many automatic weapons such as cannons, nerve gas, sedative injectors, large vacuum gravity field, and many others. Inside the walls were many mini cameras monitored by Phillip at all times. The security was extremely tight to prevent the captives from escaping.

Because he had extracted the Super-Gene of those captives every day on the way back, they all were weak, including Sykes.

Since Calamity Grades were able to recover much faster, Sykes received special treatment. His production rate was more than five times that of the others.

Han Xiao had stored hundreds of Ability Potions that were categorized. Some were for his own use; some were sold in the faction store.

The interior of Base No.1 was filled with bridges like a beehive. As Han Xiao walked on the streets, players could be seen everywhere, getting used to the new Main City.

Many people looked at Han Xiao. He was a renowned NPC in the eyes of the players, and he was the leader of the faction. When the players saw him, they all felt a sense of closeness to him, and quite a number greeted him, to which Han Xiao nodded back in reply.

There were many issues in the faction waiting to be resolved. Han Xiao checked through Sylvia's homework then returned to his room. He took out a concentrated nutrition bar and started chewing while settling these issues.

The first issue was to clean up after the missions carried out by the many players.

Other than Planet Sunil, most of the players carrying out missions around the Garton Star System had completed and returned. This was the first large scale hiring event for Black Star Army, so Han Xiao took it quite seriously. He told Phillip to filter out the problematic records in it and browsed through them one by one.

Of course, not all players were doing well. Some of the players had a rather low mission completion percentage. Furthermore, there was even a small group of people that messed around and completely messed up the mission, sullying the name of the Black Star Army. For the former, Han Xiao told Phillip to send a sincere apology to the employer on behalf of the Black Star Army. As for the latter, the Credibility Rating of their mercenary profile was deducted, and the grade of the missions that they could accept was lowered.

Since Han Xiao wanted to expand the Black Star Army with the help of the players, he was prepared for the problems that came with it. The issues now were all small problems. The effect brought by the players was much more beneficial than detrimental.

The first large scale hire event stabilized the name brought by the Godora award ceremony.

When looking for mercenaries, the employers in the Garton Star System all chose the local Black Star Army as their first choice. The Mercenary Alliance recognized the Black Star Army's position in the Garton Star System as the top of the industry and provided them with a continuous supply of high-quality employment missions.

The result of this was that the business of the Garton Star System mercenary industry was practically monopolized by the Black Star Army. Although the population of a Star System was very high, not many people needed mercenaries. The freelance mercenaries in the Garton Star System suddenly started to notice that they could hardly find high-quality hires anymore. The list given to them by the Mercenary Alliance consisted of most low reward jobs.

The freelance mercenaries were very jealous of the business enjoyed by the Black Star Army. Many people had realized that if the Black Star Army continued to grow at this pace, the available jobs in the Garton Star System would all be finished sooner or later, and the new jobs would then be taken by the Black Star Army as well. Then, the freelance mercenaries could very likely end up with no job, which was a very horrible future to think about.

The rise of the Black Star Army could not be stopped. The freelance mercenaries had to choose one of three paths. First was to not care about future developments and continue doing what they were doing; second was to leave the Garton Star System and find jobs in another place; third was to request to join the Black Star Army.

Quite a few freelance mercenaries took the third path. The Black Star Army was increasing in size and had an extremely good name, and since Black Star Army was on its way to monopolize the entire mercenary industry of the Garton Star System, joining them did not seem like a bad choice after all. From the victims of the Black Star Army's rise, there could be some who benefitted from it and enjoyed the Black Star Army's businesses.

In Han Xiao's plan, there was a part of it that included increasing their name with the players in order to attract freelance mercenaries. After the players joined, their size exploded to hundreds of thousands of members. The facilities of their base were mostly complete, and they had ample funds, so he was not planning to control the Black Star Army's number of members. He told Phillip to filter the background of the freelance mercenaries that requested to join, who then deleted some that were clearly incompetent and were there just for the easy missions, leaving those who were skilled and had good records.

About 7,000 freelance mercenaries were left after the first selection.

However, this number was still not decided yet. Han Xiao told Phillip to send a notice to those mercenaries to come to Base No.1 for an interview fifteen days later. Some would be disqualified again, and only the ones who remained after that would be recruited by the Black Star Army.

Recruiting more freelance mercenaries was a very important step of the Black Star Army's expansion.

The second issue waiting to be resolved was also related to the players.

After the first independent hiring event, these players were more familiar with the galactic environment and mission flow. Many players shared the difficulties that they met during the hires on the forums.

Han Xiao paid attention to these problems. In his previous life, he had also experienced the stage of not being used to the new environment after first entering the universe, so he had expected this. He knew about most of the difficulties the players faced.

As early as one year before Version 2.0 started, a part of his machinery production line had been building support items, which were intended to help with the players' ability to carry out missions.

Now that there was finally a demand for this, Han Xiao planned to put these mechanical items into the faction store as well. The timing was perfect—the players were just done with their first hire, and most of them had to return to Base No.1. The sales were definitely going to rocket.

In the store area of Base No.1, many people were going in and out. This was the place with the highest player density.

Although they could shop online through Phillip, they could only see the physical item at the store, which was also the collection point.

Many players used their latest earnings to buy equipment.

At this time, the faction store suddenly refreshed. A number of new items were placed at the top of the list with a very visible 'NEW' sign in their top right corner.

"New items so soon?"

"Let's see what they are."

Every update to the store would attract attention from a large number of players, and this time was no exception.

Di di di...

The sound of communicators rang continuously in the crowd. Many people took out their communicators to take a look. It was Phillip's supporting program that announced the update of the store, which could be browsed through the pre-order list.

Very soon, players realized that the new items were surprisingly not combat equipment.

They looked at the introduction of the new items.

[Mini Land Flattening Core]—Quickly changes the terrain of a small area into flat ground suitable for a temporary stronghold. The specific measurements are...

[Multi-functional Airdrop Bag]—Includes many machines needed for airdrop, suitable for various situations occurring during airdrop...

[Portable Mini Folded Fortress]—Can be expanded on unoccupied land, forming a temporary alloy fortress to be used as a stronghold, equipped with stronghold weapon slots and basic security functions...

[Automatic Guarding Cannon Turret]—Large caliber cannon, includes 1,000 Iron Core Shots, 300 Armor Piercing Shots. Provides firepower support...

[Patrolling Sentry]—Mini scouting robot, able to scout, patrol, and alert, can be used as a sentry for a stronghold...

[Interference Resistant Electromagnetic Bracelet]—Resists electromagnetic interference and data hacking to a certain extent...

[Portable Strong Electromagnetic Interference Device]—Interfere with the functions of the machines within a certain range...

[Nuclear Flying Backpack]—Provides long duration flying ability, includes self-destruction option...

[Force Resonator]—Adjustable vibration frequency, able to shatter metal and concrete buildings within a large distance...

[Worker Bee Armor]—Single Unit Mining Armor, used to gather minerals and fuel. Equipped with multi-functional digging tools and mineral firearms. High weight, suitable for handling ores...

The players faced complex environments while carrying out the missions. The mission requirements varied, including but not limited to infiltration, pursuit, mining, scouting, assassination, combat, and others. Sudden developments often occurred.

Although these mercenaries added by Han Xiao were not equipment that heightened one's combat capability, they could allow one to adapt to many situations. These were tactical items that could efficiently increase the players' ability to deal with accidents, enhancing their performance as mercenaries.

The technology used in these machines was not advanced, but they were things the players needed very much. They were cheap, useful support items.

For machines such as the turret, they were something that Han Xiao had created long ago. He had been using the turrets, but only now did he sell them to the players in large quantities. He was not yet selling the more advanced electromagnetic turrets and energy turrets but gunpowder turrets. The average level of the players now was around seventy, so the gunpowder turrets were still quite useful.

Some Mechanic players at the time could also build some of these products, but in terms of quality, cost, and price, their products were grossly inferior compared to those on the Black Star Army store.

These functional items were just right for the new needs of the players.

"These seem very useful."

"I was just about to accept a job. These new items came right on time."

The players were pleasantly surprised.

Not only the players in Base No.1, but the players who were on Sunil or doing missions on other planets also received Phillip's notification. They were all very tempted.

Especially the 200,000 players in Planet Sunil. They were dealing with the Catastrophe, so they had to deal with the complicated wilderness situations and even clear out the underground Prophecy Stone Mine. The addition of [Worker Bee Armor] was absolutely perfect.

Stock was limited, and the players hastily bought what they needed. The prices of these new products were very low, so their demand was high. Within twenty minutes, the inventory was cleared out, and many who could not buy them pre-ordered the next batch.

The players were used to the special 'Growing Faction' attribute of the Black Star Army. They felt that the reason that these new items appeared was because the players of the Black Star Army had worked together to develop the faction. Looking at the new items of the faction store, many players felt a sense of achievement.

After adding these support items, Han Xiao observed the sales. Since they were functional items, their price was low and affordable. Nonetheless, the entire inventory was sold out within half an hour. His funds rose nonstop as the players' money flew into his personal account.

This sale had made him an astonishing total of 6,600,000 Enas!

Including Noriosse's investment and the income from the last sales, Han Xiao had a total of 44,000,000 Enas!

This was a lot of money.

"Funds are abundant. With this money, I can build my Mechanic Army any way I want." Han Xiao was very content.

With so much money, if he was the only one using it, it could last him a very long time. However, of course, these funds had to be used to operate the Black Star Army and support the Black Star Army's expansion.

The blueprint that Han Xiao had set for the Black Star Army's development was gigantic. He planned to use the Garton Star System as a foundation, choose dozens of important NPC resource planets, and keep building sub-bases. He would turn the Garton Star System into the Black Star Army's headquarters, controlling the mercenary business there tightly or even monopolizing it.

Then, he would expand the business to other Star Systems and build sub-bases in other Star Systems, expanding step by step. Many parts of this plan required a lot of money, such as adding a large number of spaceships, recruiting, building partnerships with more organizations, and so on.

The identity of a mercenary group was just a stepping stone; Han Xiao's real target was to develop enormous military power, like Bloodshed Land.

The funds required for this blueprint was a number that he could not calculate or imagine.

The only thing he knew was that the money that he had now was far, far from enough.

His mission was heavy, and the road was long.

"This won't be completed within a short time. The sales route is already built anyway, so profit will keep coming. There's no need for me to be too tight on spending."

Han Xiao smiled. He took out his communicator and ordered a large number of materials from the raw material provider that he had been working with.

Finally, he had some free time to strengthen all his combat equipment to the Calamity Grade standard!

"Let's hope something like the Purple Snake Space Pirates incident doesn't happen again..."

Chapter 600: DarkStar Remnants

In Star Zone 4 of the Garton Star System was a Godoran public space station containing a certain erotic clubhouse.

Colorful and lively lights flickered, and the energetic, exciting music elevated the atmosphere. Ladies of different races with minimal clothing danced seductively on the round, rectangular shaped booths all around the place. Under them was a screen introducing, or making up, each lady's background, age, and so on, filling them with all sorts of terrible and erotic stories, stimulating the audiences' lustful thoughts.

Every booth was surrounded by a large group of males not taking their eyes off the dancer for a second. Their laughter was rough, and some even reached out to touch the dancer from time to time. Not far away was the bar with semi-private seats. Most of the people in them were males too, hugging and moving their hands around the alluring-eyed ladies accompanying them to drink.

Waitresses in revealing clothes carried drinks around, and the male customers from all sorts of races occasionally groped them.

The sound of laughter, mumbling, and teasing filled the extravagant atmosphere. It was like the air was painted with a layer of seductive pink.

At a luxurious table, a few males were chatting loudly and gulping down one drink after another. They were clearly mercenaries.

These people all had ladies in their arms. Their groping was rough and aggressive, such that pain could be seen in many of the ladies' eyes, but they did not dare to say anything. They could only smile.

These ladies knew who these mercenaries were; they were from a relatively well known mercenary group and were all Grade B Supers. In the eyes of these regular people, Grade B Supers were someone they absolutely could not mess with.

However, among these mercenaries looking for fun, there was an outcast.

At the side of the table, there was a tall and skinny man without any lady beside him. The drink in front of him was untouched, too. He was sitting up straight with his hands on his thighs. He was the odd one out in this environment; the others were having a whale of a time, but his expression was so serious as if he was doing scientific research. Even the passion of the other mercenaries was brought down.

"Come on Reynold, don't be so serious, drink some booze. It's on me anyway. Have as much fun as you like," the captain of this mercenary group said as he looked at his odd comrade. His tone did not sound like superior but instead was almost fawning.

Reynold's body did not move—only his neck turned as he looked over. His eyes were bright and sharp, like an owl in the night. Monotonously, he said, "Alcohol slows down my brain, makes me think slower. I need to keep myself sober."

"Er, then you can find a woman..."

Before the captain finished, Reynold said, "Women distract me and break my thoughts. Biological desire also affects my clarity."

"Alright then..." The mercenary captain giggled. He could not do anything about Reynold. Reynold's position in his mercenary group was very high and irreplaceable.

That was because Reynold was a Grade B Mechanic.

In the universe, the number of Mechanics was relatively low. They were rare, especially high-level Mechanics. Unlike Pugilists, Espers, and Psychics, Mechanics needed tons of knowledge. Only Mages could be compared with the amount of knowledge Mechanics needed. To Mechanics, knowledge was fundamental to becoming stronger.

His team had worked together with Reynold for quite a long time. Reynold had been providing them with weapons, devices, and repairing their spaceship and machines; he basically took care of the logistics of the entire group. Plus, he had Grade B combat ability. Reynold's position was even slightly higher than his, the captain.

If not because Reynold was so important, the mercenary captain would have been done with his strange personality long ago.

"Have you heard? Many freelance mercenaries want to join the Black Star Army. They say Black Star will monopolize the Garton Star System's mercenary business. What do we do?" a mercenary asked.

"Ignore them. It's still a long way to go for Black Star to monopolize Garton Star System even if he wants to. By then we will just go to another Star System to find work." The mercenary captain curled his lips and did not care.

Then, Reynold spoke with an expressionless face. "Let's join Black Star."

It was silent.

The mercenaries looked at Reynold in shock.

"What do you mean? I'm the captain, don't make decisions for me," the mercenary captain said with a displeased tone.

"Okay." Reynold nodded. He instantly took out his communicator, pressed it a few times, then stood up and walked away immediately after.

"Wait, where are you going?" The mercenary captain suddenly felt something was not right.

"I've left the group." Reynold walked further and further.

The mercenaries were stunned. Did he just quit the group without any hesitation because of a single disagreement? So decisive?

The mercenary captain panicked. He quickly stood up and yelled, "Are you out of your mind? No matter what, we've fought alongside each other for so long. We all took you as a friend, and you're just leaving like this‽"

"Me and you, we were cooperating equally. I did not sell myself to you, so why can't I leave?"

Without even turning his head around, Reynold walked out without stopping at all. Every step felt like it was measured precisely with a ruler. His back disappeared at the door.

The group of mercenaries exchanged looks with confusion.

"What the hell is Reynold thinking? Does he think there's no future working with us?" one of them said frustratedly.

The mercenary captain's face was gloomy. He threw the lady in his arms onto the floor without looking and heavily bashed the table.

Clank!

Cracks spread out on the table, startling everyone.

"That asshole!"

Without Reynold, the strength of his group was hugely reduced. Knowing that, the mercenary captain was furious, but there was nothing he could do.

...

Inside a passenger room on a galactic traveling spaceship in the Garton Star System, Brock looked at the interview notification from the Black Star Army on his communicator, and his eyes flickered.

He was a hybrid Godoran, a freelance mercenary. His resume had passed the first round of selection, and he had been notified by Phillip to go to the interview.

However, being a mercenary was just part of his fake identity. Brock's real identity was a hidden member that DarkStar had left in the outside world. Before he became a mercenary, he had been an elite member trained by DarkStar.

DarkStar's fleet had been wiped out, and almost all his superiors had been captured, but there was a group of DarkStar members who did not follow the fleet and hid in the outside world, keeping up their fake identities. These people had once been DarkStar's intelligence network, and now they were DarkStar remnants. Since the leader had gone bankrupt and bolted, they now had no leader and could only be concerned with their own safety.

Recently, Godora had been cleaning up the remaining DarkStar forces, and it was quite effective. Many of DarkStar's hidden intelligence channels were torn down.

For safety, the DarkStar remnants had stopped contacting each other. Some wanted to escape, some wanted to clean their background, and some wanted to change sides.

Brock was one of the people who hid very well. Not long after DarkStar was destroyed, he had actively broken away contact with the other remnants. His mercenary resume had nothing suspicious. On the surface, he had no connection to DarkStar—his identity was well hidden.

However, he did not plan to clean up his background.

Before DarkStar was attacked, Brock had accepted a mission to infiltrate Black Star, and he had decided to continue carrying out this mission.

With the help of his clean identity, he planned to pass the interview, become a member of Black Star, and stay hidden.

The first reason was that Godora was very close to Black Star, so with the identity as a Black Star mercenary, he could protect his secrets better.

The second reason was Brock's main motive. He was loyal to DarkStar and loathed Black Star; he strongly believed that the DarkStar leader would one day return!

With a gloomy expression, Brock thought, The Black Star Army is an obstacle. If I infiltrate it, maybe I can climb up to become a team leader or even an officer. I can split the Black Star Army from inside. Once the leader returns, it will be time for me to fulfill my duty. I will become a nail in the heart of the enemy...

...

The players bought the new equipment and excitedly started new missions.

While doing the missions, they were also exploring the universe. They were still at the first stage of familiarizing themselves with the universe, and it would probably take two to three more missions for them to fully get used to the galaxy.

On the other side, the hundreds of thousands of players on Planet Aquamarine were passing the test one after another. Every so often, tens of thousands of players would join the Black Star Army. These players were considered newbies, but they at least knew how to start a mission with the help of the forums, so they did not start with nothing. If there was anything they did not understand, they could even ask the first group of players that joined the Black Star Army.

Hence, Han Xiao did not have to worry about the players for some time. It was going in the right direction; he just had to leave them be and let them have fun.

Fifteen days passed by quickly, and it was finally the day to interview the newcomers.

Over the past two weeks, Han Xiao had placed himself in solitude and built many new machines. However, updating all his equipment was a very demanding task, so he had yet to complete it. He had no choice but to pause for a moment and take the time to interview these mercenaries.

In the base's vast hall, thousands of mercenaries waiting to be interviewed had gathered. There were humans, beasts, and insects, women, men, or sexless. They sized each other up.

"So, this is Black Star's headquarters."

"Looks quite grand, not bad."

Brock looked around. When he followed the big group in, he had kept observing the structure of the base, looking for weak spots and memorizing them, forming a map in his mind.

After waiting for a while, the alloy floor in front of the thousands of people opened up in a spiral manner, showing a circular hole. Dressed in his windbreaker, Han Xiao slowly flew up and landed in front of everyone.

The eyes of the thousands of people concentrated on Han Xiao. Some were curious, some were passionate, and some were filled with admiration.

With Han Xiao's current fame, strength, and position, he was indeed an important person in the Garton Star System.

"So, he's Black Star..." Brock narrowed his eyes slightly. He had seen a recording of Han Xiao before, but this was the first time seeing the real person. He sized Han Xiao up secretly.

Han Xiao glanced over the people, turned around to look at Sylvia, and nodded.

Sylvia nodded in return, then walked forward, cleared her throat, and spoke in her crisp voice.

"Welcome, everyone. You are all experienced senior mercenaries, anyone that passes the interview will become a member of us Black Star Army. You will need to sign the Mercenary Alliance's contract; all the benefits and privileges are stated inside. Of course, so are the rules and regulations of the Black Star Army, as well as your responsibilities."

Then, Sylvia stepped aside. Herlous was not there, so Han Xiao was using her as an assistant.

Han Xiao glanced over the crowd again and loudly said, "You all know the rules. If you have any problems, you can leave now."

The thousands of mercenaries murmured, but none left.

"Okay, we shall not waste any more time. Let's start the test." Han Xiao raised his hand. "It's simple. Every one of you will walk in front of me and let me tap you. Through the tap, I can roughly sense your Energy Rank. Those who pass will wait to the side."

The mercenaries had no problem with that. No one there questioned the ability of a Calamity Grade.

However, many were unconfident. This kind of test depended purely on Black Star's judgment. If he said that someone passed, they passed; if he said someone failed, they failed. There was no physical standard.

This time, Han Xiao said again, "Don't worry, for those who do not pass, I won't allow you to have wasted your time coming here. You will have two choices. One is, of course, to leave. The other is to accept training from the Black Star Army and increase your strength through high-intensity training. During that time, you won't be allowed to accept missions until you pass the test. Only then will you be allowed to use the Black Star Army's name to accept missions."

He took talents seriously. Clearly, the more strong freelance mercenaries, the better, but he knew that not every skilled mercenary would be willing to be under his command. Talents needed to be cultivated.

Therefore, Han Xiao had decided to create the Mercenary Training Camp.

The Great Mechanic Han had thought of this long ago; it was an important part of his expansion plan. In his plan, the sub-bases were not only strongholds but could also recruit and train people.

His recruitment target was not limited to mercenaries; he was going to recruit people from different planets. Planet Aquamarine was one example. Other than the players, there were also the planet's natives that wanted to enter the galaxy. Planet Sunil was the next target for that.

Upon hearing this, many mercenaries' eyes gleamed. The fact that they could still join Black Star even if they did not pass wiped away their worries.

They queued up properly to be tested by Han Xiao.

This interview method was to look at their attributes through the combat information triggered on the interface through touching.

While these mercenaries were clueless, Han Xiao knew their every ability back and forth, even their trump cards.

Testing one person took two seconds. There were six to seven thousand people there, so it would take many hours. This method was very troublesome, but the origins of freelance mercenaries were extremely complicated. Many of them were not citizens of the Garton Star System, so God only knew what their background was. Hence, Han Xiao felt he had to be careful. Plus, it had been peaceful recently, so he was able to squeeze out the time.

After some time, it was finally Brock's turn.

Without panic or worry, he walked forward and let Han Xiao tap him.

There was no risk of being exposed through testing his Energy Rank. After all, it was absolutely impossible for Black Star to know that he belonged to DarkStar just by touching him.

Brock was confident.

An opportunity to observe Black Star so closely was very rare. This was even an amazing chance for assassination. However, Brock suppressed those dangerous thoughts and prepared to wait by the side like the person in front of him.

The moment he turned around, Han Xiao's voice came behind him.

"You... wait!"

Chapter 601: No Reason Not To

Why did Black Star ask me to stop? And with such a strange tone...

Brock stopped instantly. He was shocked, and various guessed flashed through his mind.

Did I show the cloven hoof?

That's impossible... Brock took a deep breath, suppressed his worries, and turned around to face Han Xiao with a surprised expression.

"Your Excellency Black Star, is there a problem?"

Han Xiao sized Brock up then looked at the information on the interface again.

His level was way higher than those freelance mercenaries, so none of their attributes, abilities, or talents were secrets to Han Xiao.

Brock was Grade B borderline. Most of the freelance mercenaries there were Grade Cs with only a few Grade Bs. Brock was an elite among them, and he was the first Grade B tested by Han Xiao.

However, inside the Class List of Brock, there was a [DarkStar Elite Warrior], and there were also DarkStar abilities in his Ability List. Han Xiao had dealt with DarkStar for a few years, so there was no way for him to mistake it.

Plus, Brock was a hybrid Godoran, so the identity of this person was crystal clear.

He was one of the remnants, a secret member of DarkStar!

Some guts this guy has, coming to join my faction...

Han Xiao slightly squinted his eyes. Within a short moment, Han Xiao had guessed what Brock was thinking.

Wants to gain my trust, hide in my faction as a spy? Was this his decision, or was he ordered to? Han Xiao thought. What he was thinking of was further into the future. Not long ago, the Godorans had told him a piece of bad news—they had lost the DarkStar leader and Ember.

The DarkStar leader was a dangerous person, and Godora had let the master evil escape. Han Xiao kept feeling that they would make a comeback. He was wondering if Brock had been ordered by the DarkStar leader. If he had been ordered, that would mean that the DarkStar leader had secret means to contact his remaining forces!

He might be able to follow the lead brought by Brock and find the DarkStar leader!

With those thoughts, Han Xiao raised his eyebrows and smiled. He said to Brock, "You are quite skilled. I want to give you a special job. Are you interested?"

Brock was finally relieved. Suddenly, he felt like he had been too anxious.

I've really overthought this. There's absolutely no way that I'm exposed. Brock was completely relaxed now. Acting as if he was flattered, he said, "What do you need me to do?"

"Er, I want you to become the drill sergeant of the training camp temporarily, helping me train the mercenaries who have yet met the requirements."

"Sure, no problem." Brock nodded, secretly overjoyed.

Although the trainer was not considered an officer, and there was no opportunity to touch the core of the Black Star Army, this was a good start. The fact that he had been given a special position as soon as he joined meant that Black Star had taken notice of him. This way, it would be easier for him to gain Black Star's trust!

"Do your best. Go to the side and wait. After the test ends, I will make the appropriate arrangements."

Han Xiao encouraged him and sent away the excited Brock, then secretly threw an Observer's Mark onto the spy.

The Observer's Mark could locate up to five targets at once, he had the last slot left, and he used it on Brock. Next time, if he wanted to mark a new target, he would have to remove one of the five old targets.

Brock's spy identity was already exposed. However, not only was Han Xiao not going to eliminate Brock, he was boldly going to use him. With Phillip and the Observer's Mark, none of Brock's actions would escape his eyes. As soon as he did anything unusual, Han Xiao would know of it. Of course, Brock had just joined, so he definitely would not do anything bizarre for the sake of his disguise.

Most importantly, a spy would definitely work extra hard to gain his trust without any complaints. This was great manual labor. If he did not drain him properly, he would feel wasteful.

It just so happened that the training camp of Base No.1 had not yet been built, so only a Grade B could be the trainer of a large group of Grade C Supers. Training others was very troublesome, and Han Xiao did not want to waste his free time. Initially, he was going to call Ginette back, but now that Brock was there, it was enough. After all, no matter how much Han Xiao used or overworked him, he would not feel sorry for him.

This small incident did not cause any commotion and made many people more excited.

In their eyes, this meant that Black Star cared about talent. As long as they were strong enough, there was a chance for them to get a better position on the spot.

Time passed by, and Han Xiao tested them for another few hours more. More than 5,000 passed and became official mercenaries, and more than 1,000 failed and were sent to the training camp.

During the test, he discovered another three Grade B Supers. Sadly, they did not have any outstanding talents or abilities. They were considered regular Grade B Supers. Nonetheless, they were Grade Bs no matter what, so Han Xiao promoted these three to team leaders on the spot, giving them the authority to gather a certain number of Black Star mercenaries and form a fixed team.

There were two ranking systems implemented in the Black Star Army. One was based on merit, from 1-Star to 5-Star, followed by the honor title of 'Black Star Eighteen Knights'. They were promoted through contribution points, earning better benefits.

Another was based on position, meaning the management structure of an army. Han Xiao had learned from the Sky Ring Army about using both the class ranking system and merit ranking system. The higher one's contribution was or the stronger one was, the higher their position would be, and the more people they would be able to manage in a team.

Grade B Super met the requirement in terms of strength, so they got the position of team leaders.

Currently, the Black Star Army was divided into numerous factions: the Sunil Faction led by Herlous, the Battle Alliance Faction led by Harmon, the Associates Faction including Aroshia and other officers, and the Free Faction made by the players and some mercenaries. The Free Faction had the most people and could be considered the most common group of people.

Only Han Xiao could command everyone. Usually, these factions all did their own thing. This was most obvious for the Sunil and the Battle Alliance Factions; their members were close and very united.

Where there were people, there would be competition. Forming groups and factions was a problem that was definitely going to happen with larger numbers. As the Black Star Mercenary Group's size grew, so did the difficulty in managing it. In order to develop better, they had to imitate other large mercenary groups and design a layered management system, making sure everyone had their own responsibilities. This was also something that Han Xiao had been thinking about recently.

The upper positions were a difficult problem.

Currently, all the officers were basically combat personnel; there was no clear difference in their positions other than Herlous, who could barely be considered his assistant. Many positions were unoccupied, such as Deputy Captain, Area Manager, Business Manager, Logistics, Spaceship Commanders, and many more.

These positions were like screw holes, and elites and officers were the screws. Han Xiao needed to find suitable screws, fit them into the right holes, and tighten them. Only then would the management structure of the Black Star Army become solid.

"The army has hundreds of thousands of members. The base manpower is very high, but we're short of elite manpower. Sigh, I need to recruit more high-level people."

Han Xiao shook his head. Although the size of his base troops was superior compared to many large mercenary groups, high level combat powers were the drawback of his faction at the moment. He was the only Calamity Grade Super in the Black Star Army, and they only had about ten Grade B elites. When compared to the Sky Ring Army who had three Calamity Grades and hundreds of Grade Bs, he was far below.

Han Xiao was not short in people with potential under him. Sylvia, for example, had been Grade A in the previous life, Herlous had the potential to reach Grade A, and Hila and Aurora's Esper Potential even exceeded Grade A, not to mention the players with enormous potential.

However, the potential was not strength. These people had yet to fully grow, and Feidin who had the protagonist aura above his head was not his subordinate, just an employer who tagged along. The players had the version restrictions too. They could not become Grade B yet, at least not in Version 2.0.

It would be great if I could get a Calamity Grade Super.

Han Xiao sighed. Expanding his faction meant more accompanying difficulties. There were too many things that needed improvements.

The last candidate stepped forward. Han Xiao tapped him, and that person's attributes appeared on his interface.

With just a single glance, Han Xiao's expression changed.

Level... 135‽

This person's level was the highest in all the freelance mercenaries!

Just seven levels lower than himself!

Han Xiao felt wide awake. He looked up at this freelance mercenary called Reynold.

Hmm... Spacehuman, snow-white skin, seems to be a hybrid. Longer than the usual face, high nose bridge, not as handsome as me but gives off a special vibe. Looks like his character is colder and more rational. This guy's eyes are really bright... and he's staring at me too.

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows and looked at the other attributes of this person.

Reynold... 1147 INT, Grade B+ Mechanic? Wow, that's rare! This guy is the strongest among these people... Hmm, more than 600 blueprints, he has quite the rich pool of knowledge. Tsk tsk, as for talents... wait a minute, this guy has a Molding Talent‽

Chapter 602: Perfect Mechanical Sense

The Great Mechanic Han had a total of twenty-three talents, Reynold only had six fewer, seventeen talents. This was almost double what the three other Grade B freelance mercenaries had!

For those with high potential, as their level increased, they would regularly receive new talents.

In the current Black Star Army, Herlous was the one with the most talents among the officers—fifteen. He was much stronger than back then when he joined.

When Han Xiao recruited him, he had only had twelve talents.

In terms of the quality of talents, Feidin and Harmon were at the top. They both had Molding Talents.

Feidin's Advanced Luck Glow, of course, was undisputedly overpowered.

Harmon's [War God's Tenacity] and [Desperate Straits] combined with his Basic Luck Glow as a protagonist type character was like a health lock cheat and unlimited buff cheat, which was also very powerful.

The Molding Talent was what differentiated regular people from elites and bosses. Han Xiao was genuinely surprised that Reynold had one too.

[Perfect Mechanical Sense]

Total Machinery Affinity * 1.4. (Includes basic value, bonuses from passive abilities, and talents. This effect applies to the total value.)

When enhancing machines using Mechanical Force, the quality of the machinery will be temporarily increased by 1 – 2 Grades, up to Pink Grade.

+4 levels to all Mechanic class active abilities. This effect can exceed the level limit.

Remark: In your senses, every machine is a world of ecological balance.

"It's this talent!"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

In his previous life, there were players who had listed all the Molding Talents of the characters in Galaxy on the forums. Some of these talents were class exclusive; [Perfect Mechanical Sense] was exclusive to the Mechanic class and was considered one of the best Molding Talents. It influenced three things that were all connected to each other.

Needless to say, the 1.4 times multiplier to total Machinery Affinity was powerful.

Machinery Affinity was the core abilities of the Mechanic class, and it was used to increase the power of machines. For example, if a Mechanic had 500% Machinery Affinity provided by all his talents and abilities, [Perfect Mechanical Sense] would take 500% and multiply it by 1.4, making that 700%!

The rules of this bonus were the same as the Calamity Grade talent [Superhuman], applying to the total value. This meant that the stronger one's fundamentals were, the higher the bonus was. As their level increased, the effect of this talent would become greater and greater.

The other two effects of [Perfect Mechanical Sense] were also useful. The temporary increase of the Machinery Grade meant an enhancement of the machines' basic attributes. In simpler terms, trashy gray equipment would have the same effect as green equipment when he used it.

The last effect of adding four levels to all Mechanic class active abilities while ignoring the level limit meant the Lv.10 [Surging Mechanical Force] had the effects of Lv.14.

Those who had this talent could be deemed as 'one in more than a century' Mechanic class geniuses.

High level, strong talent, Grade B+... Reynold was the strongest person Han Xiao had ever recruited.

This was a high-quality wild leek!

"You're a Mechanic?"

"Yes." Reynold nodded.

"You're very strong, stronger than all of the officers under my command."

Han Xiao took it very seriously. He told Phillip to show him Reynold's mercenary resume. As he looked, he frowned slightly.

"The data shows you've worked as a mercenary for seven years, moved through five small mercenary groups. You were active in the Hyde Star System in the earliest days, only coming to the Garton Star System in the last two years. With your strength, it's more than enough for you to become a high ranking officer in large mercenary groups, why have you been in these small mercenary groups?"

He then stared at Reynold with inquiry in his eyes.

With a serious tone, Reynold said, "Large mercenary groups are too safe. I need more dangerous challenges to increase my alertness."

Han Xiao squinted. "Then why do you want to join mine? My mercenary group is a large one."

"I've faced enough challenges. What I need now is to break through, to learn more knowledge, to reach a higher level," Reynold answered with a very straight face.

"What you mean is, you want to step into the Calamity Grade?" Han Xiao raised his eyebrows.

"Yes." Reynold nodded heavily. "This is also why I'm here."

Then, he lowered his head slightly and said respectfully, "We are both Mechanics, and you have stepped into the territory of the Calamity Grade. To me, you're a pioneer on this path, and I'm still exploring, so... I hope to receive your guidance. For that, I'm willing to work for you."

So that's his motive for joining... Han Xiao figured it out. It was not the Black Star Army's privileges that attracted Reynold but my strength.

This guy is Grade B+ and wants to become Grade A. Hence, he came to find me, a Grade A Mechanic, to learn from, wanting to become my student. Well, this motive is nothing but logical; I don't see a problem.

In the five Super classes, Mechanics and Mages were keenest to learn. Exchanging and communicating knowledge was common for these two classes. Han Xiao understood Reynold's actions very well. It was just like the players who looked for NPCs to learn abilities from.

This isn't a bad thing... Han Xiao pondered silently. Reynold had a lot of potential. After recruiting him, the Black Star Army would have one more elite officer.

Sylvia was his only student, so adding Reynold would not be a problem. With his Calamity Grade strength and knowledge level, it was more than enough to teach Reynold.

As for helping Reynold get to Grade A, it depended on personal potential. Since Reynold had [Perfect Mechanical Sense], becoming Calamity Grade was basically a certainty, except Reynold did not know that himself.

Han Xiao made the decision very quickly. He nodded and said, "I can teach you, but you need to sign a longer-term contract."

"Of course." Reynold nodded. He believed that returns only came with hard work; Black Star was already much more casual about it than he had expected.

"Since you're a Mechanic... how about this? You will be responsible for the logistics. You shall manage the workshop factory and the product line in the base, building more production lines and carrying out daily maintenance, repairs, and technical adjustments. This will all be your responsibility; you can gather some people to help you."

Letting Reynold manage the workshop factory was very suitable. With his abilities, the machines that he built would be more than enough to meet the players' needs—it would be just as popular.

Plus, Reynold knew how to build product lines, and he also knew many blueprints. He was the only one that could help Han Xiao in terms of building!

This way, the job of building new product lines could be entrusted to Reynold from now on. Han Xiao did not have to do everything himself anymore. According to the needs of the hundreds of thousands of players, he would be able to save at least one to two months every year for other things!

After all, the production rate of a single person was limited; a logistics department had to be created.

"No problem." Reynold was very content with this position. What he wanted to do now was just train peacefully—he did not want to go out and fight people.

All the candidates were done with the test. Phillip made the new mercenaries sign the contracts before sending the information to the Mercenary Alliance. This way, the new mercenaries were officially members of the Black Star Army.

Other than a number of talented people, Han Xiao let Phillip arrange the positions for the new mercenaries and told Sylvia and some senior mercenaries to show the newbies around to familiarize themselves with their job. After all that, the newbies would take on their positions.

He had recruited thousands of people this time, so including the older mercenaries, Black Star Army had about 8,000 NPC mercenaries. It was many times larger compared to before.

Compared to the number of players, there were still very few NPC mercenaries. It was very difficult for it to explode in size, so the only way was to keep recruiting and building the numbers up.

The biggest surprise this time was Reynold. Even Han Xiao was tempted by the Molding Talent [Perfect Mechanical Sense]. If he could obtain this talent, he would not only be tanky but stronger in all aspects!

Sadly, he had yet to find a way to obtain this Molding Talent. Reynold was not an enemy, and even if he was, it was not certain that he could obtain [Perfect Mechanical Sense].

No matter, Han Xiao had plenty of patience.

...

Two days later, the new mercenaries all started to carry out their jobs.

The training camp of Base No.1 was officially built, too.

The more than a thousand unselected freelance mercenaries became the first batch of students. As the only drill sergeant at the moment, Brock officially took on the job.

On the first day, he was so exhausted that he almost vomited blood.

Training mercenaries was not as simple as just speaking—there had to be physical hands-on combat lessons, which was quite easy to get injured from. To train more than a thousand people alone, the amount of work Brock had to do was almost pitiful; he had completely no time to do anything else. After an entire day, he felt like his bones were about to collapse.

Remembering that he had to continue such a taxing job the next day too, Brock felt his world spinning.

However, after the first day ended as a trainer, Han Xiao deliberately went to encourage him. Brock was instantly motivated and full of energy.

Han Xiao's attitude gave him the wrong idea. Brock thought that his performance had been noticed by Black Star. Him getting this special job right after joining meant that he was important to Black Star.

After all, among all the candidates, he and that Mechanic called Reynold were the only ones that had received special treatment.

Black Star might be testing his abilities.

As long as he completed the mission as a drill sergeant and proved himself, he might be accepted by Black Star and promoted to a high rank officer!

Only after becoming a high rank officer would he be able to monitor the intelligence network of the Black Star Army.

Thinking about that, Brock decided to clench his teeth and hang on, not looking for an assistant and completing the mission alone. Only that way would he be able to prove his abilities to the highest degree, making an impression on Black Star!

"How dedicated..."

Inside his room, Han Xiao monitored Brock's every move in his Chaos Body.

Indeed, people with ulterior motives were the easiest to use.

Deactivating Chaos Body and returning to his human body, Han Xiao straightened his clothing and walked out of his room. He went to the machinery modification room of the base where Reynold and Sylvia were waiting.

It was a lesson day.

Sylvia was used to Han Xiao giving her these privileges, but now there was another person to share her teacher with, she felt very uneasy. She secretly sized Reynold up from time to time, with an unexplained sense of hostility.

Reynold looked straight forward at Han Xiao with an extremely serious face.

From that day forth, he would be learning from Black Star. This was an opportunity that he had earned with a five-year contract. It was very important to him.

Han Xiao stood before the two of them, pondered, and said, "The strength difference between the two of you is too huge. Reynold, I will teach you first. Sylvia, you can observe from the side."

The power difference between the two was way too high. The knowledge that seemed too deep for Sylvia would just be fundamental for Reynold. Of course, he was not going to teach them at the same time.

As soon as Han Xiao finished speaking, Sylvia opened her eyes wide. How could her teacher teach the newcomer first?

She instantly felt indignant and gave Reynold a fierce glare, only to realize that he was not even looking at her at all, so she could only bloat her cheeks and turn away angrily.

Bringing Reynold and the angry Sylvia aside, Han Xiao cleared his throat and prepared to start the lesson. This time, Reynold took out a pen and notebook with lightning speed from his pocket.

"Er, what are you doing?"

"Recording the lesson content." With a very serious face, Reynold quickly jotted down this conversation.

After taking a peek at the notebook, Han Xiao's mouth twitched, and he said, "There's no need to note casual chitchat..."

"No, any parts missing is disrespectful for you."

"Then wouldn't it be better for you to video..."

"No, as a Mechanic, observing all the details is a way of training too."

Reynold wrote down this conversation without hesitation, even drawing Han Xiao's expression when speaking. The speed of a Mechanic's hands was undoubtedly fast, so he was done recording almost as soon as Han Xiao finished speaking.

How stubborn. He's more like a Mechanic than me...

Han Xiao now had a rough understanding of this new comrade of his. He then started to officially teach the lesson.

It was called a lesson, but it was more like sharing his knowledge. What Reynold really needed was High-End Knowledge. After all, it was very difficult for him to make money. Plus, he did not have as many channels as Han Xiao did. Hence, Han Xiao slowly explained the High-End Knowledge to him.

Reynold was not a player, so he could not learn it instantly and had to slowly absorb.

Reynold listened extremely carefully, and his pen never stopped moving. Sylvia was completely lost. This knowledge was too deep for her—she could not understand it at all.

Clenching her teeth, Sylvia forced herself to focus and memorize the content even though she did not understand it. Reynold's appearance made her feel threatened; she did not want to get left far behind.

After teaching Reynold, Han Xiao then taught Sylvia.

Reynold did not leave however but listened at the side. Even though what Sylvia was learning was way too fundamental for him, he did not show any sign of being impatient and still listened attentively.

Time passed by slowly.

Han Xiao finally stopped his lesson. He looked at the time and announced the end of the lesson before leaving in a hurry to continue building his machines.

Sylvia and Reynold were the only ones left in the room, looking at each other.

"Er, if you have anything you don't understand, I can teach you too."

There were still many days ahead, so Reynold thought that he had to build a good relationship with Black Star's apprentice. He gave a smile that he thought was very friendly and charming.

However, he rarely smiled, so his smile was ferocious no matter how it was looked at.

"Who needs you to teach me?" Sylvia rolled her eyes. "You're new, so you should call me big sis, do you know that?"

Reynold frowned.

Oh no, is he angry? Sylvia suddenly felt a little regretful. Reynold could easily butcher her with one hand. He was even stronger than Herlous.

To make someone this strong lower his head to a barely Grade C Super, he would probably think it was a form of humiliation.

However, Reynold stayed silent for a while then nodded.

"Big sis," said Reynold with a serious tone.

"Ah, are you really calling me that?" Sylvia was shocked. With an awkward face, Sylvia said in an unnatural tone, "I was just kidding."

"No, you're right. I just thought about it. Since I'm new, calling you big sis is what I should do. I was ill-mannered earlier, I apologize. Thank you for reminding me."

There was not a single sense of unhappiness to be found on Reynold's face. His expression was earnest, and his tone was serious as always.

Sylvia's face stiffened. She found it difficult to deal with how serious Reynold was. She giggled and said, "No need. You don't have to be so serious. You can just call me by my name."

"No, I have to call you big sis, or it's too disrespectful," Reynold said solemnly. He even lowered his head to show his respect.

Sylvia felt her scalp tingle and could not take it anymore. She quickly carried her books and ran away.

...

After he finished interviewing the mercenaries, Han Xiao almost spent all the time in the days after that updating his combat mercenaries.

"It's finally done!"

Ten days later, Han Xiao's excited voice came from his personal machinery modification room.

Chapter 603: Machinery Innovation!

In the room, a strong metallic stench lingered. There were even heat waves in the air caused by the high temperature of melting steel.

Han Xiao had long become accustomed to such a smell. He hurriedly took out the last machine from the rapid cooling box, transforming it into a compressed orb, before placing it on the desk.

The table in front of him was lined with compressed orbs, all of which were new-generation machines.

This new generation of machinery was crafted with his Grade A Mechanic skills. Be it technical content, attributes, functions, and power, it had completely surpassed the older generation of machinery created when he was at Grade B. Thus, the machines replaced all his old equipment to become his new primary weapons.

His previous generation of equipment was unable to keep up with the battles at the Calamity Grade and was relegated to backup equipment.

This time, Han Xiao's comprehensive equipment outfitting could be said to be the largest scale he had done so far.

The original combat style had not changed; it was still his continuous stream of soldiers with the Army Style. Han Xiao had only strengthened these current styles.

Buzz!

With a flash of Mechanical Force, a portion of the compressed orbs were activated. Following the clanking sounds of machinery whirring to life, thirty-six new generation Hovering Shield Shuttles floated up, revolving around Han Xiao.

The new generation Hovering Shield Shuttle, codenamed [DT-03 Nano Transformed Floating Guard]. The whole set was labelled 'Watcher Instrument'.

Compared to the Halo Array of the previous generation, many aspects of the Watcher Instrument showed a definite change. The first was the shape of the Hovering Shield Shuttles, which had turned into a diamond shape. They had more edges and corners, and the color had also changed from white to a deep red. The connecting lines gleamed brilliant gold from the Kyle Alloy used.

In terms of function, the most significant change was the energy. Each floating shuttle was equipped with an ultra-micronized plasma arc reactor. It adopted the process of cold nuclear fission to generate sufficient energy with extremely low radioactivity, giving them high power outputs. The power output could also be adjusted at will. This equipment set was immensely strong, a dark purple Grade.

With the addition of two more High-End Knowledges, [High Class Energy Control] and [High Energy Weapon Control], Han Xiao had utilized them to create this new generation of machinery. He had even raised the blueprints of his machinery to the highest level, obtaining some potential points to cover his original reserves. It took a total of twenty-one potential points to upgrade both high-end knowledges to level five and four respectively.

Thus, just in terms of looking at his energy portfolio, he had already obtained good technological skills for it.

This time, he focused on strengthening his equipment. Reforming the energy cores was one of the main objectives, and the majority of his machinery had basically been swapped out to now contain controlled nuclear fusion technology.

The blueprints of the nuclear fusion reactors also had different drawings. Of which, the Plasma Arc Reactors were the best grade of blueprints that Han Xiao had obtained. The technology could be summarized as internally energized to form a magnetic field, which would heat the plasma and promote the fusion reaction. Not only was it efficient, it was also clean and controllable.

Above this High-End Knowledge would be Cutting-Edge Knowledge, which was about the study of stronger yet more unstable energy sources, such as antimatter and psionic energies. Generally speaking, only the Star Cluster Civilizations would possess Cutting-Edge Knowledge, so Han Xiao had to be satisfied with High-End Knowledge for now.

In the short term, Han Xiao had no intention of getting any Cutting-Edge Knowledge. Because he specialized in the Virtual Mechanic profession, the Cutting-Edge Knowledge in the Energy and Armed Branches would now cost three times their initial potential points. He only had two extra potential points left.

With a flicker of his Mechanical Force, Han Xiao began to operate the Watcher Instrument, testing out various functions.

The first was the most basic artillery power. He had Phillip open the weapon test module of the machinery modification room, and an alloy wall rose from the ground.

Hum!

The golden lines of the Hovering Shield Shuttle started to glow with a blue light, and the edges and corners at the tip of the shuttle suddenly unfolded, turning into a circular caliber gun. A blue laser beam blasted out, easily penetrating the alloy wall, leaving a smoking hole that could be seen from both sides.

"The penetrative power is indeed strong..." Han Xiao nodded. While the interface had described the weapon's attack power, he had a habit of testing it himself. He followed up by switching the weapon forms, testing the blasting type, assassination type, the subduing type, and the full blast type.

Because the energy output was controllable, it possessed multiple attack settings.

Han Xiao also tested the Watcher Instrument's shield durability. Unlike the Halo Array, a single floating shuttle of the Watcher Instrument could form a shield, with a high durability attached to it.

The most convenient feature of the Watcher Instrument was its Nano-Transforming ability. They could be combined with each other to become a larger caliber floating cannon or shield, and they could also be turned into a hand-held cannon. The Watcher Instrument could even transform into battle mode, turning into a Berserk Ape mechanical suit. Each of the miniature plasma arc reactors would continuously supply the mechanical suit for a wide range of uses.

"It is indeed worthy of being a Grade A mechanic's weapon."

Without any additional machinery, Han Xiao believed that Herlous could be beaten with just this Watcher Instrument.

Satisfied with the floating shuttle, he activated another pile of compressed orbs.

This time, the machinery that unfolded was the Giant Mechanical Hand. After replacing its energy core, the various functions had been significantly improved.

The Giant Mechanical Hand had always been a multifunctional equipment. It belonged to the Prosthetic category of machinery, where it could be used to slap, and the fingertips and palms could release ion cannons. It could also be turned into a compressed orb to hide in one's hands and feet to begin the series of chain attacks.

The machine could also be turned into an electromagnetic lock, used to suppress a target, or it could be changed into various tools to alter the terrain. It was quite versatile.

Han Xiao had also added new functions to the Giant Mechanical Hands. They could now merge with each other and become a single entity over hundreds of meters tall, akin to the Buddha's Palm of legends.

They could also be combined into an aircraft vehicle. Although the Berserk Ape mechanical suit was capable of interstellar navigation, it was only for a single passenger. The combination of the Giant Mechanical Hands could carry a small squad.

Talking about aircraft vehicles, Han Xiao had also developed an important piece of machinery.

[Short-Range Hyperdrive Engine]!

This blueprint came as a result of combining [Basic Spatial Technology], [Advanced Radar technology], [Interstellar Navigation Technology], and [Advanced Applications for Quantum Entanglement].

Unlike the large hyperdrive engines of the interstellar spaceships, this short-range hyperdrive engine was mainly used by individual soldiers or small aircrafts.

Of course, even though it had short range in the name, that was only compared to the normal hyperdrives in spaceships.

The Short-Range Hyperdrive Engine also had a limit—it needed a long period of time to locate the coordinates. The short-range hyperdrive engine had a charging time of twelve seconds, where the user could not move or break the connection, or else they would experience coordinate deviation, which could be fatal.

And its minimum cooling time was two minutes.

The BlackLight Stealth's microsecond hyperdrive was made by the Federation of Light, which was currently too complicated for Han Xiao to replicate.

Even though that was the case, his current device was still quite useful, allowing one to shift their troops strategically in a battlefield or to rush to a destination.

Han Xiao had already installed one of them in the Berserk Ape as well as some of the aircrafts. The effect was great, equivalent to a mechanical version of Hexflash [1. Hexflash is the shortened name for Hextech Flashtraption, a rune/skill seen in League of Legends (LoL).].

As for the burden shouldered by the single target while in hyperdrive, it was nonexistent to Han Xiao.

As a void species, his resistance to space was naturally extremely high.

Other than the enhancement to individual equipment, the Mechanical Army had also undergone significant innovations.

The first task was to fully restore the original four legions: Number 001, [Mechanical Beast Guards Army]; 002, [Strike Artillery Regiment]; 003, [G-1 Steel Army Corps]; and the Elite Troops Number 101, [Oathkeepers]. At the same time, Han Xiao had also slightly increased the size of the legions.

Building on these, Han Xiao had added another two legions.

Number 004, [G-2 Heavy Armor Riders]!

This unit consisted of 600 heavy-loaded mechanical soldiers. They resembled huge men riding on high-speed propulsion vehicles. Their way of attacking was charging forward as the vanguard, with a strong impact to cut through the formation of the enemy. These heavily armored riders were mainly melee, equipped with weapons such as high-temperature blades, high-speed drills, and spiral wheel saws. All the weapons could easily set off a bloody storm.

Number 005, [Mini Cube Troops]!

This was a special unit consisting of 1,500 micro-mechanical warfare soldiers. Such a mechanical soldier was dubbed the 'magic cube robot'. It measured only the size of a normal human palm, but even if something was small it could still contain the essentials. They possessed a high level of combat quality, and their size could work to their advantage on some occasions. This was why Han Xiao had created this army.

This unit also possessed an auxiliary function. The drawings of the 'magic cube robot' was derived from the knowledge [Super Nanometer Force], which would allow them to combine with each other to form a larger mechanical soldier. Each individual cube could be understood as parts of a larger mechanical soldier, and these parts could move freely and reshape at any given time.

At present, the scale of his Mechanical Army had reached 20,000. The number was still rising, as new mechanical soldiers were still being produced every day in the workshop.

The extra manufactured mechanical soldiers would either be directly merged into the various legions or used as backups.

In addition, the weapons of all mechanical soldiers had been upgraded, such as adding shock converters to the melee weapons, high pressure blades, and so on.

Plasma cannons, heat ray cannons, and radiation guns had been added to the slew of ranged weapons. The enhancement was also reflected in the turret structure, as Han Xiao had created a new type of turret.

Ammunition and detonation bombs had also undergone a reformation, having new devices such as vacuum oxygen detonation bombs, space warping bombs, thermonuclear mines, miniature nuclear grenades, and the new orbital sniper bombs.

Other than the original combat mods, Han Xiao had created two more battle tactics.

The first was the Restrain and Control Style.

Han Xiao had obtained a blueprint of an electromagnetic superconductor particle, about the size of a grain of rice. He had manufactured a lot of them, and placing them in a pile made them resemble some sort of black sand.

Superconductor particles contained strong magnetism, which could be manipulated through mechanical force.

This set was also known as 'Electromagnetic Adsorption Marsh'. When activated, the superconductor particles would resemble a black wave, carrying with them a strong electromagnetic force. Once they reached the target, the particles would entangle the target, releasing the adsorption force and binding the target.

The longer the controlling time, the wider the coverage of the superconductor particles, and subsequently, more difficult for the target to break free. Through mechanical force, the adsorption and its shape could be varied, which allowed this equipment to actively capture the target.

This was a strong crowd control device that lacked lethality. Han Xiao's inspiration for this came from Ember's fighting style, and Han Xiao's electromagnetic adsorption marsh also controlled particles, which resembled Ember's ability.

His second combat mode could be called the 'Dirt Cheap Style'.

In his previous life, players had named this style as the Tactical Support Style.

A few months ago, when DarkStar attacked Planet Aquamarine, they had used the main cannon to strike at himself from outer space. That was called Tactical Support.

The essence of this mode was to summon missiles to scrub the ground, summon space-based weapons to strike down, summon fleet salvos... it was essentially an upgraded version of the Multi-Turret Firepower Coverage Style.

Also referred to as being gangster!

The Army Style would crush most mechanic styles. Only two schools of thought were the most troublesome opponents of the Army Style.

The first was the Virtual Intrusion Style—that was the Virtual Mechanic profession that Han Xiao specialized in.

The other was this Tactical Support Style.

Han Xiao dropped all his compressed orbs and looked toward the other side of the modification workshop.

Over there sat a giant machine.

It was actually an impact railgun!

Chapter 604: Bad Feelings Most Likely Will Turn True

This impact railgun was called 'Eye of God', a satellite weapon that could move on its own after being detached from the spaceship. It could be plotted at the edge of the atmosphere to orbit around the planet.

Unlike the DarkStar main cannon, the Eye of God was not a particle beam weapon; it used physical ammo. Its shells were exceptionally large and could be used with many different types of ammunition, providing more tactical options. Attacking the surface from outer space, its attacks would gain more kinetic energy from the initial thrust and gravity. With Han Xiao's calculations, its accuracy was very precise.

The cost of this impact railgun was remarkably high, only next to the Berserk Ape mechanical suit, not including the cost of every shot it took.

With so much money spent, the returns were certainly great. The damage of Eye of God was outstanding. It was like a gigantic turret placed in outer space. There were only two restrictions. One was that its attack speed was very slow—the shell had to fly for some time. Another was that it could not be used in space—it could only be used to attack the surface from above. It was rather suitable for missions that involved airdropping down to the ground to deal with issues.

This was now the most destructive weapon that Han Xiao possessed, but there was only one. The Tactical Support Style only had a brief outline. However, Han Xiao had a lot of money, so he could build more if he had the time.

When the Tactical Support Style was complete, tens and hundreds of impact railguns firing together would be able to annihilate an entire planet in a short time, fully proving the fact that money meant strength for the Mechanic class.

Bigger was greater, more was better. When other Supers hit a barrier and were unable to move forward, only the Mechanic class could steadily increase their strength by spending money.

"Only with this equipment have I reached the level of strength I should have." Han Xiao nodded in his head.

The total cost was close to a million Enas. After updating all his combat machines, his destructive ability had really reached the Calamity level. He could summon nuclear bombs onto planets and destroy the ecology of the surface in a short period.

Watcher Instrument, Mechanical Exterior Prosthetic, Short-Range Hyperdrive Engine, Mechanical Armies 004 and 005, Strong Electromagnetic Swamp, Eye of God... Han Xiao checked all the machines. He then arranged the compressed orbs and wore them. As for the large weapons like the Mechanical Armies and Eye of God, they were placed in the spaceship warehouse.

Other than machines for combat, Han Xiao had also fused an interesting blueprint used for battles between spaceships, which he had built during the time.

The Barbarian Charge Cabin, a landing battle device.

This was a suspended cabin, attached to a spaceship and equipped with shock absorption devices. When the enemy's shield was destroyed, this charge cabin could be launched to bite onto the enemy spaceship. With its heat slicing equipment, it would then melt the enemy's armor and send the people inside it into the hostile spaceship. Of course, if things did not go well, the charge cabin could self-destruct.

During galactic wars, charge cabins were regularly used. The people inside had no means of retreating—they were all basically in a do-or-die situation.

Han Xiao felt this was perfectly suitable for the players.

Han Xiao was still studying the Violent Falcon spaceship, but he was short of a part of the knowledge, so his progress reverse engineering it was stuck. In his previous life, high-level Mechanic class players could build spaceships, but it was mostly done by a team. Everyone had different knowledge of the spaceship and assembled different parts.

Han Xiao did not want to divide the labor; he wanted to learn the entire process of building spaceships.

Building a spaceship alone was one of the Special Legendary Point milestones, just like the [Legendary Hunter] milestone that he had yet to complete.

However, he was still short in a part of its knowledge, and he happened to be lacking Potential Points. He was in quite a pinch.

After entering the galaxy, Han Xiao had not harvested as much experience, mainly just money.

He needed time to update his equipment after leveling up, and he had spent quite a lot of experience leveling up and fusing blueprints.

Therefore, his experience was almost dry.

I should find the time to get some experience...

His equipment was all updated, and other than getting more Potential Points, he also needed to continue increasing his strength.

I'm now level 142. Although I just entered Grade A, I can match up to higher level people with my equipment. Plus, my talents mean I can take a beating, so my advantage is huge. If the enemy's ability is common, the chances of me winning will increase significantly...

Han Xiao estimated his combat capability. Usually, most people in Galaxy entered Grade A between level 150 to 160; it all depended on talents, abilities, and attributes. He, however, entered Grade A at level 142. This was not common even among these powerful protagonist-type characters.

At Grade A, each Promotion at every twenty levels or each Class Advancement for the main class could be considered a separation line. Han Xiao was now at the level 140 to 160 grade, so the amount of experience needed to level up was enormous—billions and billions.

In his previous life, when the version that allowed players to level up to this level was released, the missions had all given at least tens of millions of experience. Despite that, the players had still had to spend a tremendous amount of time to level up just once.

Even though he could shear the players, it was still extremely difficult to obtain the amount of experience needed to level up to 160 straight away. Promotion was too far away at the moment, but there was another way to increase his strength—main class Class Advancement.

Han Xiao's [Virtual Mechanic] was now Lv.17. He was three levels away from his Class Advancement, which would need about three billion experience.

This time, Han Xiao did not plan to sell knowledge. Selling knowledge was a one-time sale, so he could only do it so many times. Plus, it was not suitable for him to give everything to the players at once.

He decided to sell blueprints, which was the larger profit chain.

Although the target market for blueprints was limited to Mechanic class players and the profits were not as high as with Promotion Knowledges, the upside of this was that there were way too many blueprints that could be fused, almost infinite. During Version 1.0, Han Xiao had acted as the Mechanic class mentor and made more players become Mechanics. The reason that he had done that was to expand the market for blueprints.

Furthermore, he did not just have to sell the players low level blueprints; he could even sell very high-level blueprints.

The players did not have the required knowledge, so even if they bought the high-level blueprints, they would not be able to use them until much later. Nonetheless, people would still buy them. It was better to have a high-level blueprint that they could not use than not having one at all. Just looking at it would make them look forward to the day they could use it.

He never underestimated the Chinese players' desire to stock up.

Thinking of the players... Han Xiao opened the forums. As usual, it was boisterous.

The players used the tactical equipment that he had sold last time in their new hire missions, and many people sent screenshots to share. Among them, the Worker Bee Armor received the most positive comments; it made many players find a new way to make money—mining! It was much more peaceful and steadier than fighting and killing.

The second most popular one was surprisingly the Nuclear Flying Backpack. The focus of the comments was not even flying but all about how good it felt to self-destruct...

This made Han Xiao even more confident about the Barbarian Charge Cabin.

He knew it—self-destruction and the players were a perfect match!

Han Xiao browsed through the posts. Other than sharing posts, chatting posts, and other random posts, there were also highly skilled players who posted guides which explained strategies among other things. Suddenly, Han Xiao realized a post was going up the popularity list very quickly.

'Wayne Cards Newbie Guide—Issue 3'

He clicked in, then realized that the player who had written the post was charmed by Wayne Card and used all the money that he earned to buy Wayne Cards, not equipment...

Noob!

Playing meaningless games every day and not doing missions properly‽

In the end, these players have still been contaminated by Wayne Cards...

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Could Wayne Cards actually be his biggest competitor?

He briefly scanned through and realized that the Shattered Star Ring card set had been updated, which was the focus of this post. It was being madly discussed by the players. In the updated cards, there was the Black Star Army.

_____________________

Shattered Star Ring Card Set adjustments:

- Mercenary Card [Black Star Mercenary Group] changed to Mercenary Card/Force Card [Black Star Army]. Increased card attributes, added special effects.

- Civilization Card [Godora] attributes increased.

- Force Card [Floating Dragon Island] attributes increased.

- Added Strong Card ['Black Star' Han Xiao]

- Added History Card [End of DarkStar]

- Force Card [DarkStar] moved to Disposed Card Set.

_____________________

Han Xiao suddenly understood why this post was so popular.

Currently, in the eyes of the players, the Black Star Army represented their faction. Seeing that their faction had appeared in the card set, the players were more than just excited. The comments were exploding. In their eyes, the updated Wayne Cards showed the result of their hard work for the growth of their faction.

Wayne Cards' update represented the changes of all areas in Galaxy to a certain extent. They had added an exclusive Strong Card for Han Xiao, and it had some decent attributes...

This meant that his actions had spread far, and he was someone very well known.

Han Xiao suddenly realized that Wayne Cards seemed to be a subtle leaderboard or list, showcasing the fame and position of people in the universe.

...

After looking through the forums for a while longer and extracting some potions from Sykes and the rest, Han Xiao closed the door and left the machinery modification room.

While spending close to two months building machines, Han Xiao did not forget his mission to escort Hila and Aurora to Floating Dragon Island.

Since the Black Star Army had grown in size, the players and the regular mercenaries took care of a lot of missions. Currently, there did not seem to be any high difficulty mission that he needed to complete himself. Hence, Han Xiao decided to first fulfill Ames' request.

Hila was usually in the Combat Training Room along with Aurora.

On the way there, Han Xiao met Sylvia, who seemed to be avoiding something nervously. She hastily greeted him and quickly escaped. Han Xiao did not pay any attention to it. He then walked further ahead and noticed Reynold looking around at the intersection, so he went up to him and gave him a few words of encouragement. Seeing that Reynold was about to take out his notebook, Han Xiao quickly shut his mouth and walked away with wide strides.

Upon arriving at the Combat Training Room, Hila was expectedly undergoing combat training, and Aurora had been dragged into it.

Due to past experiences, Hila had a very strong desire for power. After entering the galaxy and seeing so many people that were so strong, she felt an even stronger sense of danger. She would not have slept at all just to train if she could; she put all her time into training.

Of course, the results were visible. The Training Room could simulate real combat and force out the combat potential of Supers. Hila's talent had always been rather good. Combined with hard work, her strength grew quite quickly recently. A few days ago, Han Xiao had sparred with Hila and realized that she was many levels higher than before.

Han Xiao opened the door, and the simulated battle environment disappeared.

Hila stopped. She wiped away the sweat on her forehead, frowned, and said, "What are you doing here? You want to spar?"

She was wearing an extremely tight, black battle suit that looked like a layer of black skin, highlighting her alluring body shape, curvy and thin everywhere it should be.

Han Xiao looked at her and could not help but shake his head. "Can't you change into a more useful battle suit. Do I not have enough armor for you to choose from?"

Hila gave Han Xiao a look of disgust. "Too bulky."

"Bulky? It's called safe. Don't you just not like them because they don't look pretty? What do you know about aesthetics?" Han Xiao rolled his eyes. Tsk, women.

While those two argued, Aurora leaned on her knees and gasped for air, unable to even speak.

She had been forced to join the special training. Unable to keep up with Hila's training intensity, her body was almost collapsing due to exhaustion.

However, Aurora was not completely unwilling. She had experienced times of hardship and knew how important strength was, so she did not slack in her training at all. After all, the simulated battled would not deal any real damage, so if she was just slacking, she would not be so tired.

Han Xiao took out a concentrated nutrition bar and threw it to Aurora. "That's enough. Stop training and pack up. I'm taking you guys to Floating Dragon Island."

Aurora heard that and quickly stopped biting open the packaging of the nutrition bar, surprised. "Are we finally going to meet big sister Ames‽"

Hila's eyes became slightly brighter, and her lips curved up a little. After entering the galaxy, only then did she understand how powerful Ames was in the universe. She had been looking forward to training with her.

Di di di...

Han Xiao was just about to say a few words when the communicator suddenly rang. He took it out, and it was surprisingly Ames' communication request.

Speak of the devil.

"Ames?"

"Hmm, Black Star, when are you bringing my students over?" Ames' projection appeared, and a long pair of white, python-like legs entered Han Xiao's sight.

"I was settling some stuff earlier, so it was delayed. I will bring them to Floating Dragon in a few days." Han Xiao nodded.

"Okay." Ames paused and suddenly said, "Best come quicker. When you're here, I want you to go somewhere with me."

"Where?"

"Bloodshed Land," Ames said calmly without any noticeable emotion.

Han Xiao's eyebrows shot up. He had a bad feeling like his casual and relaxing time was about to end. "Can I not go?"

"Humph, no." Ames ended the communication.

Chapter 605: The Tyrant's Invitation, Shattered Star Ring Territories

Speechless, Han Xiao put the communicator away and thought on it.

Why is Ames going to Bloodshed Land? To make trouble?

Malekith had once said that Ames had some issues with Bloodshed Land. The Tyrant had taken one of her officers, and they had battled furiously, ending with Ames' loss. Han Xiao felt that Ames was not going there with good intentions this time.

She insisted on bringing me. Does she want me to assist her and stop the Tyrant's officers?

Han Xiao's lips twitched. He was now Floating Dragon's strongest officer. Back then, Ames did not have anyone whom she could use under her command. Now that she finally had someone who could fight, was she going to make full use of him?

There were plenty of strong people under the Tyrant. The eight Grade A Vanguard Officials were just the tip of the iceberg; Vanguard Officials were not the only position for their high-ranking officers. If Ames only took him along to Bloodshed Land, of course, she would end up being fine, but the same could not be said for him.

I hope we are not going there to fight... Han Xiao had a slight headache.

Hila had watched their conversation from the start till the end. Confused, she asked, "What kind of place is Bloodshed Land?"

"That's a gathering ground for a group of muscular men. It's just a dangerous place," Han Xiao replied unhappily.

As Ames had told him to hurry up, Han Xiao did not delay any longer.

He found Reynold and told him to stay in Base No.1. Then, he found Sylvia and told her to take care of the other issues. This was just standard procedure; the one who was actually managing Base No.1 was Phillip, and Han Xiao could monitor the situation remotely. Hence, there were not that many things to say. The Black Star Army's business could carry on as usual even though he was not in the base.

Settling these issues only took half an hour. Han Xiao gathered Hila and Aurora, who had now changed into new, neat clothes, and the three of them boarded the Blacklight Stealth, which was parked in the hangar.

Woo woo!

The rooftop gate of the hangar opened, and the anti-gravity stabilizer below the Blacklight Stealth activated, emitting a dark blue light.

The spaceship took off vertically, and a purple flame shot out from the thrusters.

In the blink of an eye, the spaceship turned into a stream of light and disappeared into the sky.

...

The Blacklight Stealth exited hyperdrive, slowly caught up with Floating Dragon Island, and docked.

"So, this is Floating Dragon Island..."

Disembarking from the spaceship, Aurora looked left and right curiously. She saw the brutes gathered on the dock immediately, who all looked fearsome. They were clearly not good people.

The brutes turned around and looked at them.

Hila saw this and quickly caught up with Aurora. She stood beside her and looked around at the brutes with alertness in her eyes, like a lioness protecting its child.

"Don't be so nervous. Although Floating Dragon allows galactic pirates, scavengers, and wanted criminals to stop here, no fighting is allowed... Er, not usually of course. Ahem, anyway, they won't bite."

As Han Xiao spoke, he walked over to the two of them, then wrapped his arm around Hila shoulders and looked around. "Hey, what are you people still looking at?"

The brutes then all turned and looked away, continuing with their business. Han Xiao's ride was too famous; no one wanted to mess with Black Star, on Floating Dragon Island especially.

Hila glanced at Han Xiao then looked at the hand on her shoulder and moved her body uncomfortably.

"My friend, you've returned again."

This time, Wilsander's voice came from nearby. He had gotten the news long ago and had been waiting to welcome Han Xiao.

What Han Xiao did not expect was that Jenny was there, standing right behind Wilsander.

He greeted Wilsander before looking at Jenny. He chuckled and said, "You're here, too, huh? Work has been busy, I suppose; you look gaunter than the last time I saw you."

Without any change to her expression, Jenny snatched a weapon from a guard and started firing at Han Xiao like a maniac.

Bang bang bang!

Han Xiao let the small-caliber laser land on his body without moving. This could not hurt him at all.

At the side, Aurora's jaw dropped from watching this. Hila clenched her teeth, looking like she was wondering whether to stop it or not. Wilsander was shaking his head and sighing.

Ka ka ka!

When the firearm overheated and could not continue firing anymore, Jenny finally threw it away and coldly said, "Ames is waiting for you in the palace."

Then, she turned and instantly walked away.

She knew that she could not hurt Han Xiao; she just wanted to vent her frustration.

As the Head Butler, Jenny had been as busy as a bee recently. Being very understanding, Han Xiao did not mind letting Jenny enjoy herself for a moment.

Anyway, this would not affect his actions. He would still expand as he planned to. Jenny's relaxed time was over and never coming back, just like her youth.

Han Xiao patted his clothes, unconcerned. He turned to look at Hila and said, "Let's go. I'll take you to see Ames. Memorize the roads on the way."

Speechless, the two of them looked at each other before nodding.

After bidding farewell to Wilsander, they went all the way to the palace at the center of the floating island.

The dragon bone throne floated in the palace. Ames was sitting on it, resting her head on her hand, and watching the three of them walk into the palace. She sighed and said, "Black Star, you're so slow, only bringing them here after a few months."

Han Xiao did not agree or disagree. Hila and Aurora bowed as a greeting.

Ames controlled her force field, lowering the height of the throne, and landed in front of the three of them. She smiled and said, "Alright, you will be my students from now on. You can call me teacher."

"Teacher," the two of them replied.

Ames was very pleased by that. Her smile became even more gentle. This was what she had once called Aesop. Now that she had her own students, it felt very special.

"Although our Esper abilities are different, I can teach you methods to develop yours using my experience, helping you to make use of your potential," Ames said gently.

Hila nodded solemnly. "Okay, when do we start?"

She was a training maniac, and with such a strong teacher, she could not wait to start training.

However, Ames shook her head and said, "Not now. I want you guys to go somewhere with me."

Han Xiao's eyebrows twitched. "Bloodshed Land?"

"Yes, all three of you are coming with me."

She's bringing Hila and Aurora too? Then it seems like we're not going there to fight... Han Xiao was relieved.

This was good news. He did not want to mess with the force of another Beyond Grade A out of nowhere.

However, to confirm Ames' intention, Han Xiao still asked, "That's Heber's territory. I heard there were problems between you and him. Why are we going?"

Ames' smile became dimmer as she slowly said, "The Tyrant is an ambitious guy. We don't get along. He even once stole someone talented from me, but this time, we are not going there to cause trouble.

"Every once in a while, the Tyrant hosts an enormous party. He sends out invitation letters to the important people of the Shattered Star Ring. Almost everyone shows him respect and attends. There are high ranking government officials of Star Cluster civilizations, representatives of large organizations, and sometimes even emissaries of the three Universal Civilizations. Of course, the Beyond Grade As of Shattered Star Ring are invited, including me... Humph, despite that guy being a pain in the neck, he is a very unpredictable man. Back then, I battled through his headquarters, but the next party, the Tyrant still invited me.

"Anyway, the Tyrant's parties have continued for many years. It has become an unspoken tradition between large organizations. This is a chance to make connections for many important people. The Tyrant has the ability to be the host. At the party, many important people will communicate and discuss various topics. A large amount of information will be leaked out every single party. The discussions between these people during the party decide the future developments of the Shattered Star Ring to quite a large extent."

So that's what this is... Han Xiao realized what was going on.

Simply put, the Tyrant hosted a Shattered Star Ring party, which people attended to make friends, chitchat, gossip, and all that. The difference was, the attendees all held very important positions, which, when all combined, could even decide the future of Shattered Star Ring.

Hosting this kind of gathering and turning it into a tradition for the high-class organizations... the Tyrant was indeed ambitious. His goal was massive.

"So, are you going to attend the Tyrant's party?"

Han Xiao was surprised. Floating Dragon had always stayed neutral. Plus, considering Ames' personality, she did not seem to care about this sort of thing.

"Of course I'm going!" Ames' voice became deeper. "I don't want to look so petty!"

What? What does this have to do with petty? Han Xiao was puzzled.

He then tried to think from Ames' perspective and finally realized what Ames meant.

I hate his guts. How dare he invite me to join his party! To show he's generous? F*ck, did he invite me because he thinks I won't go? If I don't go, doesn't that show that I'm petty? Go! I must go! I'm generous and awesome, why would I be afraid of going!

To Han Xiao, he thought this guess was about at least ninety percent right. This seemed like the kind of thing Ames would think.

Then why bring me? Oh, because the Tyrant has so many strong people under his command, so Ames doesn't want to lose on that front. That's why she's taking me there!

At least we're not going there to make trouble... Han Xiao was a little puzzled and could only comfort himself this way. "When does the party start?"

"There's still some time. We will leave tomorrow, heading straight toward Bloodshed Land's headquarters."

Bloodshed Land was located in the Seoul Star Cluster. If the Shattered Star Ring could be described in a flat 2D map, the middle would be the most dangerous, unstable cluster, filled with wormholes appearing and disappearing at random, connected to all places in the universe.

On the map, one side would be the edge of the known universe, beyond which was the unknown part of the universe that was unexplored.

The other side would be the tunnels toward other Star Fields that cover astronomical distances of the unpopulated desolate universe. That was how Risda had arrived, traveling through Star Fields for a very long time from another Star Field.

Surrounding the wormhole cluster were ten or so Star Clusters, all divided and controlled by the seven Star Cluster Civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring.

The Taralam Star Cluster was the closest to the wormhole cluster. It was plagued with scavengers. When Han Xiao was doing the Chen Xing missions, he had gone there once.

Between the Colton Star Cluster and Seoul Star Cluster was a desolate area. It could almost be considered their border.

On the other side of the Seoul Star Cluster was the largest Star Cluster, the Setin Star Cluster. Seoul was in the middle of Setin and Colton; it was the second smallest Star Cluster in the Shattered Star Ring.

In terms of government, the Star Cluster Civilization that ruled Seoul was called the Klent Kingdom, and the Star Cluster Civilization that ruled Colton was the Purple Crystal Civilization. These two civilizations coexisted peacefully. They had built many large Stargates in each other's territory. Godora's Stargate had been built by the Purple Crystal Civilization.

The Tyrant's Bloodshed Land was the Klent Kingdom's VIP. With a Star Cluster Civilization behind them, the Tyrant's party represented both the influence of a Beyond Grade A and the position of a Star Cluster Civilization. Hence, so many people would attend.

"So, we're going to the Seoul Star Cluster, right?" Han Xiao sighed. "Take my spaceship then."

Smiling, Ames said, "That's exactly what I thought."

Chapter 606: Bloodshed Land

In the middle of Seoul Star Cluster, the stars shone brightly. A stream of light slashed across the universe, bolting through the darkness. It was the BlackLight Stealth in hyperdrive. On the ship were only Han Xiao, Ames, Hila, and Aurora.

After a few days, the four of them finally arrived at Seoul from Colton, passing through many stargates and Star Systems. When passing through the entry stargate from Colton to Seoul, they were even searched by the stargate station.

Klent Kingdom's management of the Seoul Star Cluster was rather strict. They had set checkpoints around the entry stargates from other Star Clusters.

The entry stargate allowed teleportation across the desolate area between the two Star Clusters, saving a huge chunk of time. All the galactic travelers with a clean background would use the stargate, whereas those who took the path through the desolate region were mostly wanted criminals and secret organizations.

Bloodshed Land's headquarters were in the heavily controlled Star System, the core Star System in the middle of the Seoul Star Cluster.

In the ship's hall, Han Xiao looked at the location marked on the star map and curled his lips.

"Planet Heber. Tsk tsk... he used his own name for the headquarters, such a..." Just a Han Xiao was about to comment, he suddenly realized that he had done the same thing, so he instantly changed his sentence. "Such a wise choice!"

"Are we almost there?" Aurora looked at the star map curiously and realized that she could not understand it.

"The hyperdrive will end in about ten minutes and twenty-seven seconds." Han Xiao looked at the control panel presented by Risda. The spaceship was on autopilot at the moment, and all four of them were at the hall.

Aurora turned and asked, "Teacher, is Planet Heber similar to Floating Dragon Island?"

Ames lay down sideways on the sofa, elegant and casual. She smiled and said, "Different, Planet Heber's costs are higher. It's a modified planet, built by Klent Kingdom with Star Cluster level technology. It's more like a portable fortress. It's Heber's second strongest weapon."

Star Cluster Civilizations' ability far exceeded that of Star System Civilizations; they were on completely different levels. The most obvious difference was mobility—Star Cluster Civilizations could build stargates, so their transport speed was countless times faster than Star System Civilizations'.

Also, Star Cluster Civilizations had the technology to build planet-grade battleships, the most common one being the Planet Mining Mothership. It could 'devour' an entire planet, breaking it down inside and turning it into all kinds of resources.

For example, Planet Heber was a planet-grade space fortress built by Klent Kingdom.

"Second strongest? Then what's the Tyrant's strongest weapon?" Hila asked with a serious expression. She was more interested in the abilities of the strongest people in the Shattered Star Ring.

"His strongest weapons is, of course, his own body." Ames shook her head. "He can use his physical body to penetrate straight through a planet."

"Impossible!" Aurora exclaimed.

Han Xiao had Phillip search for Heber's history. It seemed like there was more than one record of him crashing through a planet. Rather, it looked like it was Heber's usual activity.

"Heber's body is extremely strong. Mud and stones cannot stop him. The high-density rock layer under deep under the surface is as fragile as paper to him, and lava is his bathing water. Even a planet's core isn't hot enough to burn him. Maybe a Fixed Star could hurt him, but not a planet, so crashing through a planet is not a challenge for him." Ames sighed.

Heber was almost her nemesis, yet even the highest strength force field could not tear Heber apart. Heber could move freely even under the pressure. If she used Floating Dragon to hit him, it would be shattered by Heber instead. The nemesis of force field type Espers was indeed this kind of indestructible enemy. After all, although force field Esper abilities were well rounded, it was more toward controlling—damage was not its strength.

Despite Ames being carefree, she was not ignorant. She knew her own weaknesses.

Hila frowned and kept silent. Heber's strength currently exceeded her knowledge range, so she did not know what to say.

"Heber penetrating a planet is like a sniper bullet penetrating several planks." Han Xiao shook his head. A Beyond Grade A Pugilist was terrifyingly powerful.

After chatting for a while, the Blacklight Stealth finally exited hyperdrive state. The light tunnel outside the porthole disappeared, and the universe reappeared.

Right under the spaceship, a small, metallic planet entered their sights. Its color seemed solemn and serious.

Planet Heber!

Han Xiao received a communication request from Planet Heber. If they did not identify themselves and continued loitering around Planet Heber, they would be deemed as an enemy.

Ames had the invitation letter, so after verifying their identity, Planet Heber sent the parking coordinates. Han Xiao told Risda to control the spaceship and land at the given location.

As Planet Heber was a moving fortress like Floating Dragon, it did not have natural sunlight. The top of it was covered with thick, dark artificial clouds to block the radiation from the universe.

The spaceship slowly descended. After passing through the black clouds, Planet Heber's surface appeared in their eyes.

Planet Heber was mainly made up of cold and dark colors; there was almost nothing dramatic.

Castle-like buildings stood tall, and tons and tons of bases were like mountains. These buildings emitted a dark blue light. It was somewhat futuristic and mysterious. Advanced technology seemed to be a planet-wide theme. Between the many bases, there were gigantic hollow-in-the-middle circular devices up to two kilometers tall. A purple light was rippling at its hollow part like it was operating as something.

Above the bases, battleship fleets patrolled.

This was a planet-level armored fortress!

Hila and Aurora were stunned.

The Blacklight Stealth landed at a dock between the bases. When they got out of the spaceship, a group of people were already waiting there. They were all Bloodshed Land soldiers, led by the Vanguard Official Malekith.

"Your Excellency Dragon Emperor, thank you for accepting the invitation. Welcome to Bloodshed Land."

Malekith gave a common bow. He had personally delivered Ames' invitation letter.

Ames did not reply. She looked at the surroundings, snickered, and said, "It's been a while since I last came. This place is boring as always. Heber really has no taste."

"Battleships and fortresses are the best decorations," Malekith replied. When he saw Han Xiao beside Ames, his eyes gleamed, and he said coldly, "Black Star, I said we would soon meet again."

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows, played dumb, and said, "Who are you? I've never seen you before."

"..."

The others looked over and stared at him.

"Alright, I was kidding." Han Xiao curled his lips.

Bloodshed Land's people were really interesting, trying to pick them apart as soon as they met. Malekith deliberately used such an ambiguous tone to hint that he had met Black Star privately before.

Han Xiao did not tell Ames that he had met Malekith before, and Ames had once had someone stolen from her side. Due to the previous incident, she should be very sensitive to this. If she knew that her trusted officer had met with Bloodshed Land privately again, she would probably not be happy with him.

Malekith looks like a savage with a small brain, but he's actually quite dirty, isn't he?

Okay, I will remember this.

Chapter 607: Provoke

A sharp green light flashed through Ames' eyes. She stared at Malekith and deliberately said, "What are you guys trying to do to my people again?"

"Your Excellency Dragon Emperor, don't be so sensitive. Black Star and I just happened to meet. That's all," Malekith replied calmly.

Ames squinted and turned to look at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao had nothing to hide, so he honestly replied, "He found me and wanted me to leave Floating Dragon to join Bloodshed Land. Tsk tsk, he gave me some good terms."

"And? What did you say?" Ames asked with a faint smile.

"Had I agreed, he wouldn't have brought this up again." Han Xiao shrugged.

Ames smirked, turned to Malekith, and said, "Hear that? Give up your tricks and lead the way."

Seeing that the provocation did not work, Malekith did not speak anymore and led the way.

There were still a few days till the party, but many people had already arrived. Bloodshed Land had prepared many rooms for the guests to rest in.

The four of them headed toward the rooms. As they passed through the numerous bases, patrolling soldiers and carriers were everywhere.

Han Xiao had time on the way to observe all sorts of facilities in Bloodshed Land. It was similar to how he remembered. In his previous life, there had also been players that were recruited by Bloodshed Land, so he remembered the map structure of Planet Heber.

If I remember correctly, the Planet Heber's surface is just a small part. There are bigger strongholds underground, Han Xiao recalled.

This time, the voice of a stranger suddenly came from not far behind them.

"Long time no see, Ames."

Han Xiao's first intuition was that the tone of this person sounded very taunting.

They turned around. A team of soldiers crowded around a man appeared behind them, the man was the one that spoke. He wore an exquisite robe and had a more feminine than masculine face, staring at Ames with a mocking expression.

The look in Ames' eyes slightly changed when she saw this person. "Carroll."

Carroll's unrestrained eyes scanned Ames' gorgeous face, snow-white neck, flat abdomen, and her thin, long legs, sizing her up fearlessly. He snickered and said, "I left Floating Dragon so long ago, but you're still as beautiful as before."

Ames' face was cold and indifferent.

Han Xiao noticed Ames' abnormal reaction; it seemed like her relationship with this guy named Carroll was unusual. He turned and glanced at Malekith and saw the rubbernecking expression on this broken horn Demon's face.

I see, Carroll is Ames' ex-subordinate... Han Xiao realized.

If Carroll had resigned normally, Ames would not have said anything. Instead, Carroll had openly deserted and joined Bloodshed Land with a high profile. He had even given away some of Floating Dragon's technological secrets and their map structure. Plus, he was now in a high position. To Ames, this was no doubt a betrayal. She felt hostile toward Bloodshed Land, even more so toward Carroll. Back then, when she battled toward Planet Heber, she had most likely had another goal—to kill Carroll. Only, she had been stopped by the Tyrant.

The truth was just as Han Xiao speculated; Ames and her old subordinate Carroll had become enemies long ago.

"To dare come and look for me, are you tired of living?" Ames said coldly.

Carroll had the Tyrant to rely on, so he was confident and unafraid. With a derisive smile, he said, "This is Bloodshed Land's headquarters. What, do you want to kill the Tyrant's logistics manager here? By the way, I heard you found an insect to replace my position. Hehe, you have quite a heavy taste."

With an expressionless face, Ames started to get intense.

Hila and Aurora noticed that the atmosphere was not right and became alert.

However, Carroll did not hold back at all. It was clear that he had come just to provoke them. He turned to look at Han Xiao and casually said, "Black Star? So, you're Ames' new officer? I can be considered your senior, do you want some advice and tips?"

"Tips?" Han Xiao raised his eyebrows. He was just standing aside and did not speak, but unexpectedly, Carroll spoke to him.

"That's right, I know her very well, and I have a feeling you need my guidance." Carroll shrugged and mocked, "After all, you like being her pet—shouldn't you know what your master likes?"

"Wow, this is the first time I've met someone who's even more of an ass than me." Han Xiao could not hold back his laughter. "Pal, do you sometimes have like punching yourself in the face when you look into a mirror?"

Carroll had thought that Han Xiao would be angered by his provocative words, so he was choked by this completely unexpected reaction. He paused then spoke again with mockery. "Don't get angry, I'm just speaking the truth. You're the same as the old me, just her pet. The difference is, you're just my replacement. Without you, there will be a Red Star or a White Star to replace you."

Han Xiao stroked his chin. Before he could return the taunt, Ames spoke first.

"Black Star is not like you; he's more trustworthy than you."

"Oh, then you'll have to be more careful." Carroll stared at Han Xiao with a sneer. "The more she trusts you, when you want to abandon her, the more determined she'll be to kill you... Hehe, you're probably worse than a pet, just a slave tied to her side."

This guy sure talks a lot of trash... Han Xiao rolled his eyes. A few words were far from enough to anger him.

Then, Carroll looked at Ames again, this time with even more apparent lust. "Did you know this? I once did not even have the courage to raise my head in front of you, but now..."

"I have no interest in what you think." Ames stopped Carroll from speaking. With an ice-cold look in her eyes, she raised her hand and said slowly, "Since you're deliberately taunting, it seems like you're prepared to bear the consequences."

Boom!

As soon as her sentence ended, a powerful force field appeared, and the ground cracked open inch by inch under the extremely heavy pressure. The force field headed straight toward Carroll.

This time, three roars came from around the place. Three shadows moved swiftly in front of Carroll, and thick Pugilist flames rose from their bodies.

The three of them blocked the force field with all their might.

The three of them were all Grade A Bloodshed Land Vanguard Officials, one being Malekith.

In an instant, an impact wave exploded, and the Bloodshed Land soldiers around all turned into rolling stones, falling and rolling away.

The three Vanguard Officials were sent flying, too. They launched a wave of energy midair to stop the momentum, landed on the ground, and stared at Ames with caution.

It had taken all three of them to stop Ames' one simple force field attack.

"As expected." The look in Ames' eyes became darker, and the air started to vibrate.

The attack earlier was just the most casual, simple hit from Ames, and now she was going to get serious.

Ohm!

A much stronger force field brewed, and the ground and buildings around started to crack.

Seeing this, Han Xiao had no choice but to take a few steps forward to stand in front of Ames. With a flash of Mechanical Force, Watcher Instrument hovered behind him in a circle, like a circle of light behind his head.

A dark light appeared in the barrel of the Hovering Shield Shuttle, targeting the enemies. Han Xiao smirked and said, "So, do you guys want to duel or fight me together? I'm fine with anything."

The eyes of the tree Vanguard Officials including Malekith all sparkled with anticipation.

Despite saying so, Han Xiao knew that the fight was not going to happen. This was Bloodshed Land's showcase of power; the Tyrant would definitely interfere. After all, they were guests no matter what. Plus, Heber would not allow Ames to destroy his party.

Nonetheless, he still had to express his stand. He could not stand aside and let Ames face the enemies alone.

Just when everything was about to erupt, a new energy force arose from far away, shooting straight up into the sky, as if flooding over the entire Bloodshed Land. Even the star lights in the sky seemed to have lost their color and become dimmer.

Boom!

From a distant place, the voice of a person appeared, deep and loud, like the sound of thunder.

"Ames, fighting in my territory, are you ignoring my existence‽"

As soon as he heard this voice, Han Xiao immediately felt the menacing tone.

Subconsciously, this reminded him of what he had felt when he went to the zoo during his previous life and faced the roar of a tiger.

The Tyrant, Heber!

Chapter 608: Probing

Everyone looked toward the source of the sound. The sound came from the middle district of Bloodshed Land and the location of Heber's palace.

Ames's eyes gleamed coldly, and she looked at Hila and Aurora before letting out a soft sigh. Her palm was then lowered and hidden within her sleeves. She was no longer planning on taking action, and the force field that had been brewing disappeared.

The tense atmosphere relaxed in that instant.

She then looked at Carroll and Malekith who had blocked her attack and calmly said, "Don't just stand there, lead the way."

When she decided to accept the invitation of the Tyrant, Ames had already predicted that something like this would happen. Her previous attack had already displayed her attitude. However, since the Tyrant had interfered personally and she was in his territory, she did not want a greater conflict to break out. After all, she did not come here to create trouble.

Malekith nodded and led the way.

Han Xiao then turned around to glance at Carroll.

Carroll did not say another word as he witnessed Ames' departure. He then retracted his smile and shook his head at the other two Vanguard Officials. "I thought that she would continue attacking despite the warning. Although I made sure not to go too far, with my understanding of Ames, this level of provocation should have been enough to enrage her."

Another Vanguard Official then said with a sigh, "The Dragon Emperor has changed. The rumors are true. She indeed wants to expand."

The Black Star Army represented Floating Dragon's expansion. Many organizations had noticed this situation, and Bloodshed Land was no exception.

Carroll's mission was to probe Ames' attitude. The majority of his words were targeted at Black Star and did not directly humiliate Ames. Through Ames' reaction, they would be able to gain plenty of information. If she truly wanted to expand, she would not provoke a greater conflict.

...

At the same time, in Heber's palace, only Heber and a Klent emissary were present. The footage of Ames and her entourage was displayed on the screen.

The Klent Kingdom placed great importance on the Tyrant's gathering and treated this as an important diplomatic mission. The emissary was a high official in the Klent Kingdom and personally attended the gathering to show the close ties between the Tyrant and the Klent Kingdom.

The Klents usually had slim figures, and when standing beside the seven-meter-tall Heber, the emissary seemed extremely tiny.

"Your Excellency Tyrant, you are as powerful as ever. You do not even need to make an appearance and can make the Dragon Emperor back down with a single roar. I still thought that I would be able to witness the majestic appearance of Your Excellency taking action," the Klent emissary said with a respectful tone.

"Hmm." Heber shook the gigantic, specially-made wine glass in his hands without saying a thing.

"It's a pity. If only she had decided to take action." The Klent emissary shook his head and smiled.

"The gathering this time is a huge event. She will offend many big shots if she creates trouble. Since she wants to expand, she won't take action," Heber said calmly.

"Aren't you afraid of her taking revenge after the gathering?" The Klent emissary chuckled. "She is someone who would do something like that."

"Isn't that what you guys would like to see the most?" Heber asked calmly.

"Haha, you are right. That would give you an excuse to suppress Floating Dragon Island." The Klent emissary laughed. He was the one who wanted to see Ames go all out without any consideration the most. "Even the Purple Crystal Civilization wouldn't stop you from entering Colton with this reason."

Heber glanced at him and could not be bothered to reply. While both parties were in an alliance, their motives were different.

The Klent emissary looked at Ames' figure on the screen and muttered to himself, "Ames... tsk tsk. If I could obtain such a woman who has the halo of a beyond Grade A Super, all other women would pale in comparison to her."

With his status and authority, he had countless partners, and appearance was no longer what he cared about the most. Status and identity were what made a woman more charming in his eyes. As the only female among the four beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring, Ames was naturally the woman who was the hardest to tame.

A Star System level civilization did not dare provoke a beyond Grade A Super, but to a Star Cluster level civilization, while a beyond Grade A Super was powerful, they would not be that wary of one.

Only a gigantic organization like the Tyrant's would be of significance to a Star Cluster level civilization.

Thus, the Klent emissary did not mind displaying his desire for Ames. In any case, it was no more than a thought.

"I hate willful women," Heber said slowly. "Her character needs to be polished more."

Upon hearing that, the Klent emissary shook his head. Ames was no more than a thought for him, but Heber was the one with the capability to take action.

...

Han Xiao and the others were on their way to the guest room.

After the previous conflict, the mood of the group was a little downcast.

"Black Star don't think too much," Ames suddenly said. "Carroll said those words on purpose."

"I know." Han Xiao shrugged in response.

"They should've been following Heber's instructions," Ames explained. "I wonder what his intentions are. Aesop predicted that this gathering would be different and asked me not to act rashly."

It turned out that Ames had already gotten Aesop to make a prophecy. Perhaps Aesop had also recommended that she come for this gathering.

"Carroll was one of the earliest members of Floating Dragon. However, he betrayed me for the Tyrant, gaining a high status in Bloodshed Land."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and said, "To allow a traitor to take on an important position, the Tyrant is truly charismatic."

Do not use an individual you doubt, and do not doubt an individual you use. Heber definitely needed to offer extremely plentiful conditions in order to poach people. When Malekith tried poaching him, Malekith had also offered him the position of Vanguard Official.

"He is the Tyrant, so he is not afraid of betrayals."

"Why?"

"When Carroll betrayed me, the Tyrant was able to protect him, but if he betrays the Tyrant, no one in the Shattered Star Ring will be able to protect him." Ames let out a sigh. "Furthermore, I have to admit that the Tyrant is far more charismatic a leader than I am."

"Are you very wary of him?" Han Xiao said with his brows raised. "I still thought that you weren't afraid of anything."

"Of course, I am not afraid of him, but no matter how much I hate him, I cannot change the fact that he is extremely powerful." Ames shook her head and paused for a moment before continuing. "Thus, try to remain low profile in the Tyrant's territory. You don't have to be angry because of Carroll. He said those words intentionally."

Ames looked at Han Xiao and took the initiative to give an explanation. She was afraid that Han Xiao would take those words to heart.

Han Xiao felt warmth in his heart. He did not mind what Carroll had said but did not think that Ames would care about his feelings.

According to his understanding of Ames, she did not seem like the person who would care about others.

"I feel that you have changed."

"How have I changed?" Ames smiled.

"You are more patient than before."

Ames smiled and did not reply. She then turned around to look at Hila and Aurora.

"Aesop said that only a little child would act in such a willful manner. He asked me to change. If not, I will suffer a loss one day."

Han Xiao rolled his eyes and replied, "That old Aesop is still so shameless. How does he have the right to say such a thing?"

"I think so too." Ames broke out into a bright smile and chuckled.

...

The guest room provided was located in a building to the side of Heber's palace. It was a gigantic castle that was made up entirely of guest rooms. There were already some guests who were currently staying in the guest rooms.

There were still a few days before the official start of the gathering, and many organizations would come earlier. The few days before the official start of the ceremony was the best chance to network and expand their social circle. After all, it was a rare opportunity for the big shots of the various organizations to gather together.

Malekith led the way into the castle.

At the moment, the main hall was filled with guests in small groups. The guests were all of different races and came from the different organizations of the Shattered Star Ring.

Upon hearing someone walk in, all the guests turned around to take a look. After recognizing that the incoming guest was Ames, all of them had strange looks on their faces. They wanted to come up to give their greetings but seemed to be wary about something and thus remained on the spot without moving.

All of them had heard the loud roar of the Tyrant. Since Ames and Heber had already clashed, they all felt that it was better for them to suck up to the Tyrant. Thus, no one stepped forward to strike up a conversation with her.

Ames could not be bothered, and their group left the main hall toward the rooms.

Bloodshed Land had prepared the rooms for them. Ames had her own room, Han Xiao had his own room, and Hila and Aurora shared a room.

When they got back to the rooms, Han Xiao was left alone.

He then activated a compressed orb, and it transformed into a detection device. After scanning the room, he confirmed that there were no listening devices.

Han Xiao nodded and took out another machine.

Buzz!

A brilliant beam of light flashed, and a holographic image covered the entire room. Even if there was a magic monitoring device, only the holographic image would be captured, and they would not be able to tell what he was doing.

While there were many big shots living in the castle and there should not be any listening devices, Han Xiao was used to being careful.

"Carroll..."

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he transformed into his Chaos Body. Activating his Void Vision, his sight ignored all physical distance, and he could monitor Carroll's actions.

The instant Ames had decided to step back, Han Xiao had planted an Observer's Mark on Carroll and removed the position of the space pirate.

The Observer's Mark was only there as a precautionary measure. In times of emergency, this Observer's Mark could come in handy.

Furthermore, Carroll was the Logistics Manager of Bloodshed Land and could come in contact with important equipment and blueprints frequently. Han Xiao felt that there would be a lot to gain from him.

I can make use of the Observer's Mark to gather intelligence during the gathering, Han Xiao thought to himself.

In his previous life, none of the players had discovered the Tyrant's gathering because they were not able to reach such a level. This was the first time that he had heard about the gathering.

While there was a conflict along the way, this gathering should be relatively safe.

Ames was probably there to show her presence, but this was an extremely good opportunity to gather intelligence for Han Xiao. Han Xiao decided to make use of it well. With all the participants of the gathering being big shots, they might be able to reveal some important information. With his memory of the various storylines, a small hint would allow him to think of many things.

The Version refresh had always been something of great importance to Han Xiao. After all, the players in his previous life had only received very vague details of the exact timing of the refresh. Han Xiao needed greater details and hoped to gain some insights from this gathering.

Chapter 609: New Territory, Empire Envoy

For a few consecutive days, Han Xiao and the others waited in the castle.

Everything was peaceful. Bloodshed Land's people did not start another conflict, and the Tyrant's Eight Ass Kissers... ahem, Eight Vanguard Officials did not appear again.

Other than not being allowed in the restricted areas, the guests could move freely in Bloodshed Land, and the soldiers would lead the tours.

Han Xiao occasionally toured Bloodshed Land.

Even the regular soldiers in Planet Heber's headquarters were low-grade Supers; there were almost no normal people. The people under the Tyrant were mostly Pugilists, so buff guys could be seen everywhere.

The soldiers wore gray, specially-made heavy armor, which enhanced their body strength and the effect of their Pugilist energy.

Han Xiao noticed that other than the normal soldiers, Bloodshed Land also had some elite soldiers. Their individual physique was stronger, and they wore better armor. Their armor had many exterior prosthetics such as tails, wings, huge claws, and so on. From what the soldier that led the way said, those soldiers were called Thousand Beast Soldiers, one of the elite armies of Bloodshed Land.

Han Xiao was more interested in Bloodshed Land's weapons and carriers; they were all incredibly unique and exclusive to Bloodshed Land. Clearly, the Tyrant had a group of Mechanics designing special equipment.

Bloodshed Land was happy to showcase their power to the guests, but what they showed was only the tip of the iceberg.

Han Xiao could not help but feel a sense of pressure. He was building his own organization, and although they had risen very quickly, there was still a very vast difference between them and large organizations like this, which had been around for so many years and gathered so many resources.

There was still a long way to go for the Black Star Army.

Over the past few days, guests had been arriving and entering the castles continuously.

Although Ames had come to attend the party, she was clearly unconcerned about such things. She had been staying in the room to teach Hila and Aurora, while Han Xiao represented her and socialized.

When he was not touring Bloodshed Land, Han Xiao was chatting with the guests. The guests all represented known organizations in the Shattered Star Ring, so this was a good opportunity to expand his connections and get to know other people.

There were leaders of huge financial groups, representatives of Star Cluster Civilizations, and the most successful people in various industries such as intelligence organizations and ammunition organizations. Han Xiao even saw the Mercenary Alliance's person in charge of Shattered Star Ring, who was very friendly and had a great chat with Han Xiao.

The position, identity, and influence of the guests invited were all at the top of the pyramid in the Shattered Star Ring.

Most of the organizations had heard of Black Star. Although they did not pay much attention to him, he represented Floating Dragon, and the Black Star Army had become quite famous lately.

Han Xiao's current Renown and Legendary Points had reached a certain level, so most of the guests acknowledged that Han Xiao could be part of the circle.

Up until now, Han Xiao had only been active around various Star Systems, which were just the tip of the iceberg of the Shattered Star Ring, so his influence was limited. Now, he had finally stepped into a higher level and met with the people that made up the 'core' of the Shattered Star Ring.

The other guests were divided into several levels. The comparatively lowest level consisted of the large financial groups, and in the middle were the large organizations. Floating Dragon Island was between the low and medium level.

The highest level comprised enormous organizations like Bloodshed Land, as well as the representatives of the seven Star Cluster Civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring. The degree of acknowledgment that they had for Han Xiao decreased as their level increased.

The attitude of the Star Cluster Civilization representatives toward Han Xiao was mostly limited to formalities, except two civilizations who were friendlier—the Purple Crystal Civilization and the Klent Kingdom.

Colton was Purple Crystal's territory. Plus, Dragon Emperor had been hanging around the Colton Star Cluster. To the Purple Crystal Civilization's representative, Han Xiao was considered half an ally to them. The Purple Crystal Civilization's attitude was gentle and friendly.

The Klent Kingdom's high ranked officials were more passionate. They even actively approached Han Xiao to chat, clearly showing their intention of establishing a relationship. Of course, Han Xiao had no reason to refuse.

Nonetheless, he had never had contact with any Klents, so he was quite confused as to why this guy was as passionate as an animal in heat...

After a few days, Han Xiao's communicator obtained the contacts of hundreds of people, who were all the best in their industries. Just these connections had already made this trip worth it.

When he returned to Floating Dragon Island and shares these contacts with Jenny, she would definitely be very touched.

Finally, the last day before the party arrived.

That day, to their astonishing surprise, the Tyrant sent someone to Han Xiao and the others, inviting them to attend a private meeting hosted in Heber Palace.

"Heber wants to meet privately? What's his goal?" Han Xiao was curious.

"No idea." Ames shook her head. "We'll know when we get there."

She wanted to know Heber's stance, so she accepted the invitation.

They walked into Heber Palace and arrived at a huge conference room. Three thrones hovered three meters above ground in a triangular shape.

On one of the thrones sat a seven-meter-tall giant, giving off a very strong vibe. As soon as they walked into the room, they subconsciously looked over. Heber's presence was dominating, so he could attract the attention of others immediately.

This was the first time that Han Xiao had met Heber in person, and he was instantly reminded of a crouching lion.

Huge. That was Han Xiao's first impression of Heber.

"Sit." Heber looked over. His eyes were tranquil, and his tone was calm, yet it possessed a natural pressure as if dominance was deeply embedded in his bones. No matter what he did, it would give people that feeling.

Ames snorted. She hovered up and sat on one of the thrones. Han Xiao and the two sisters stood beside the throne.

"What did you call me here for?" Ames asked in a deep voice.

Heber looked at the empty third throne and said, "There's one more person missing. We'll talk when everyone's here."

Then, Tyrant closed his eyes and rested, leaving Ames aside.

Assertive... Han Xiao's lips twitched uncontrollably.

Ames snorted, already used to it. This was Heber's way of doing things. Straight forward and forceful, he did not like to have peaceful chats.

After a while, the gate opened again.

A child wearing an oversized Mage robe floated in wobbly, and a few tiny magic dragons swam around his body obediently.

This child's face was chubby and round, and his ears were sharp. He only looked six or seven years old. A red and white Mage robe hung on his tiny body, like an exquisite and luxurious blanket. Instead of him wearing the Mage robe, it was more like the Mage robe wrapped him up, the tail of which almost touched the floor.

Beneath the child were a few masked men wearing black hooded robes. They were looking down as they walked, seeming mysterious.

"You're here, too?" Ames' tone heightened.

"Heard there's something huge this time, so I'm here to take a look." The child sat on the empty throne. With an exceptionally tender and childish voice, he nodded at the other two and said, "Ames, Heber, it's been some time since we last met."

Han Xiao then realized that this child was another Beyond Grade A in Shattered Star Ring—[Magus] Austin. An unfathomable Mage.

Austin looked very young, but he actually belonged to a long-lived race. He was born with an incomparable Magic Affinity. Like the others, he had many titles: 'Bender of Rules', 'Creator of Forbidden Spells', 'Half Spell Body', 'Ruler of Arcane', and others.

Han Xiao looked at the hooded black robe masked Mages below Austin. Every Mage crossed their arms in front of them, their hands hidden in the large sleeves, and stared at the ground like silent sculptures.

So, these are the Forbidden Sorcerers. Han Xiao squinted.

[Magus] Austin's organization was called Hidden Red Robe Abbey, one of the holy lands of Mages in the Shattered Star Ring. They focused on studying and discussing magic, occasionally handling magic-related investigations for some civilizations. As long as one was a Mage in the Shattered Star Ring, most of them would be willing to join Hidden Red Robe Abbey. That organization had the characteristics of a guild.

Hidden Red Robe Abbey was separated into outer members and inner members. Outer members were all free people that would not have to hold much responsibility, if any. If one wanted to learn deeper magic, they had to pass tests and sign a magic contract to become inner members of Hidden Red Robe Abbey, following orders.

Only the inner members were considered to be under Austin's command. The Forbidden Sorcerers were Hidden Red Robe Abbey's elites. Due to different organizational structures, their military power was not as strong as that of Bloodshed Land, but if the outer members were included, their numbers would probably be much larger than Bloodshed Land.

Other than Ames, Heber had invited another Beyond Grade A. There were four Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring, and three were gathered there.

Heber then opened his eyes and said, "Everyone's here. Let's get down to business."

"Wait, where's the other guy?" Ames asked. She was talking about the last Beyond Grade A who was not there.

"He said that it's too far, and he's too lazy to come."

"That sounds like him indeed." Austin chuckled.

Heber did not want to waste time chitchatting. He got straight to the point and slowly said, "The purpose of this meeting is to introduce someone to you guys."

The other side of the gate opened, and a person walked in. Everyone looked over with curiosity, wanting to see who this person that Heber wanted to introduce to the other two Beyond Grade As was.

This person was a human species, about 2.5 meters tall. His skin was light red, he had short hair, and his face was unique but mostly suited the aesthetic of Spacehumans. He wore a soft, uncommon robe, it looked very complex and luxurious; the material could not be determined. The patterns on the robe were exquisite, the base of which was crimson red.

Facing three Beyond Grade As, this person remained calm. He stood in between the three thrones and greeted the three of them gently.

"Let me introduce," Heber said slowly, "the Crimson Empire's envoy, Zoel."

The pupils of everyone instantly contracted.

Han Xiao's face remained the same, but there was a storm in his mind.

The Crimson Empire, one of the three Universal Civilizations!

The highest level civilization sent an envoy to attend the Tyrant's party‽

Has Heber already formed connections with the three Universal Civilizations?

Wait a minute... Han Xiao suddenly realized a problem.

On paper, the Shattered Star Ring belonged to the Federation of Light's territory. However, the Crimson Empire had sent an envoy secretly to the Tyrant's party where all the important people would attend. The meaning of this was extraordinary.

Han Xiao's mind worked fast. Suddenly, he recalled something, and the look in his eyes changed slightly.

He remembered that the background of Version 3.0 [Crimson Tide] was the expansion of the Crimson Empire, affecting various Star Fields.

It turned out that a sign had already appeared.

Han Xiao took a deep breath and calmed his emotions. The Tyrant's party might be an ambush!

Ames frowned slightly and recalled Ames's prophecy before departing.

This party is indeed not simple...

The room fell silent.

Zoel looked around slightly and broke the ice. "I'm honored to meet the three Beyond Grade As of the Shattered Star Ring."

"We're honored, too," Austin replied before looking at Heber inquisitively.

Introducing a Crimson Empire envoy, what did this mean?

"What we are going to talk about next is the theme of this party. I'm now telling you guys in advance," Heber said with a deep voice. "Not long ago, the Exterior Universe Explorer Device that the Federation of Light had outside the Shattered Star Ring sent a report back. It crossed an enormous area of desolate universe and was circling around a new Star Cluster area outside the edge. That's an unowned Star Cluster, and it needs to be explored and included in the Shattered Star Ring's map."

The others had different expressions on their faces.

No wonder the seven Star Cluster Civilizations all sent a representative to attend this party, Han Xiao realized.

Ever since the Peace Treaty was signed, all three Universal Civilizations had been trying to explore the unexplored universe and expand the known universe.

Every time a new land appeared, new battles erupted.

Since all the Star Clusters of the Shattered Star Ring belonged to the seven Star Cluster Civilizations, the new Star Cluster was a cake that everyone wanted a piece of, if not the whole cake.

"The Federation of Light wants the new Star Cluster to be added to the Shattered Star Ring. We, however, want to deem it as the starting point of a new Star Field," Zoel said.

Although he did not speak of the details, everyone understood what he meant.

The Shattered Star Ring was Federation of Light's territory, but a new Star Field did not belong to anyone. The Crimson Empire's goal was huge—what they wanted was not just a Star Cluster.

In the explored universe, the center Star Fields were bustling, and the Star Fields at the edge were more chaotic and backward. Star Fields at the border like the Shattered Star Ring were where the competition was most intense—only these places had opportunities to continue to explore and expand further.

"Therefore, on behalf of the Crimson Empire, I hope to receive help from you." Zoel stated his goal.

Heber stayed silent. He had introduced the Crimson Empire envoy to the others, so it was clear that Bloodshed Land had made its decision.

So, the Federation of Light or the Crimson Empire?

Austin and Ames exchanged looks and stayed silent.

Han Xiao's eyes became firm. They're making a big move!

Chapter 610: Openly Poaching

The three thrones floated in midair, surrounding the emissary of the Crimson Empire in the middle.

"What can we get if we help you?"

After pondering for a while, Austin was the first to respond.

Everyone present had a certain status, and even the emissary of the Crimson Empire could not expect them to work for nothing.

It was no more than a pipe dream if he wanted the beyond Grade A Supers to help him without offering any conditions.

"A new territory represents new opportunities. Only a piece of white paper is easy to color. If we are able to transform this newly discovered Star Cluster into the beginning of a new Star Field, anyone who wants to explore or expand their territory will have to enter the territory of the new Star Field. At that time, the new Star Field may become a Star Field that has the same weight as the Shattered Star Ring. The benefits hidden within it are frightening," Zoel explained as he waved his hands to reveal a holographic star map from his communicator that had the new territory marked.

It was outside the boundary of the Shattered Star Ring, and a dark unexplored region of space was marked on it.

After crossing through a long, desolate space belt, a bright region appeared from within the dark region of space. That was the new Star Cluster that the Federation of Light had found.

From smallest to largest, the regions of the galaxy were classified as planet, Star Zone, Star System, Star Cluster, and finally Star Field.

The Crimson Empire wanted to obtain this new Star Cluster not just to expand their territory but because it formed the bridgehead for any future exploration. The Crimson Empire would then be able to make use of this new territory of theirs as the starting point of their exploration and continue to expand their territory. All the new regions that they discovered after this would belong to the new Star Field, which was part of the Crimson Empire.

The Federation of Light controlled the Shattered Star Ring, and the Crimson Empire wanted to obtain another neighboring Star Field. They were not willing to share this exploration path with the Federation of Light.

As Zoel analyzed the pros and cons of supporting him, Austin and Ames listened silently by the side.

As for Han Xiao, his attention was drawn to the star map that Zoel showed.

No matter how he looked at it, he felt the position of the Star Cluster to be extremely familiar.

After taking a closer look at it, something clicked in his head, and Han Xiao was filled with agitation.

My goodness, isn't that part of the Flickering World‽

The [Flickering World] was the Main Storyline of a later version, and it was a completely new Star Field. Billions of stars shone brightly to light up the dark universe.

Pioneering the discovery of a Star Field would definitely bring about plenty of benefits.

The players of the entire galaxy would all participate in this Main Storyline mission to pioneer the discovery of a new Star Field. There were also countless races and civilizations that entered the Flickering World. This became an event that caused a huge reshuffle in power among all the organizations and battles to break out everywhere.

The new Star Cluster that Zoel had shown was a part of the Flickering World. It was the tip of the iceberg.

Who would have thought the events of the later versions were already beginning to unfold?

Only a small corner of the region has been discovered. To explore the new region fully, many years will be required. It is still a long way from the current version...

In the past, the players had performed missions for the various organizations, but this time, they might have the opportunity to be the ones in control. Just as the emissary had said, a new territory represented new opportunities. Perhaps this was the best chance for him to move up the food chain.

While the Black Star Army was not powerful enough and was still a great distance away from large organizations such as Bloodshed Land, Han Xiao had a huge advantage. He knew how things would develop.

If he wanted to have the rights to be in control, he needed to have a more powerful organization. They stronger he was, the more benefits he could obtain. His present self was far from sufficient. Thankfully, there were a few more versions to go.

Han Xiao could not help but grow anxious as he pondered silently.

The birth of the Flickering World meant one thing. The Crimson Empire succeeded in the end and managed to snatch the new Star Cluster from the Federation of Light and transform it into a new Star Field.

When he was deep in thought, Zoel had finished explaining his conditions. In summary, the Crimson Empire would provide them with aid in secret.

The support of a Universal Civilization was a very tempting condition. While the Federation of Light was in control of the Shattered Star Ring, they rarely interacted with the various organizations of the Shattered Star Ring and appeared to be high above.

Austin frowned and had a serious look on his face. However, when coupled together with his childish appearance, it looked extremely comical and adorable.

"I am not too interested in such a matter and would rather study curses at home. So, I apologize, but I would like to remain neutral. I can only promise you that I will not help the Federation of Light."

After considering for a while, Austin gave his response. He wanted to stay out of this matter and remain neutral.

"I understand." Zoel was not too surprised. They were all beyond Grade As, so he could not force the other party. The outcome of the other party remaining neutral was not too bad. Zoel had only managed to persuade Heber to help him after putting in a great deal of effort. The main purpose of the meeting today was to inform them of their empire's stand and reduce the number of helpers for the Federation of Light.

"What about you, Ames?" Heber asked.

Ames was not interested in such a matter and was about to follow Austin and reject the proposition. However, she paused for a moment and looked at Han Xiao.

"Black Star, what do you think?"

"Hmm?"

Han Xiao was currently deep in thought, and upon being called, he was stunned for a moment.

Seeing everyone's gaze on him, Han Xiao pondered for a moment before nodding. "The Crimson Empire can naturally be trusted with their reputation. The esteemed emissary is correct in saying that this is a once in a lifetime opportunity with great benefits hidden within it. I personally feel that the Crimson Empire has a sixty percent chance of succeeding at the very least."

Zoel's eyes lit up, and he revealed a smile. While wondering when he had successfully converted this fellow, he nodded at Han Xiao and said, "Good eyesight."

Han Xiao also nodded back in response. "Thus, I feel that you shouldn't be in a hurry to reject. This isn't a bad thing."

Upon hearing that, Ames thought for a moment and did not reject Zoel directly but said, "Let me think about this."

The expressions of both Austin and Heber immediately changed.

Both of them had known Ames for years and knew that Ames had actually intended to reject the proposition. However, she had immediately changed her mind after listening to Han Xiao's advice.

Black Star's importance to the Dragon Emperor had far exceeded their expectations.

Not just a hired thug but an advisor? Austin stroked his chin and fell into deep thought. That's right, with Ames' personality, she will need a reliable strategist if she wants to expand, and Black Star seems pretty capable.

"Black Star, I heard from Malekith that he tried to poach you but was rejected," Heber said.

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed, and he slowly nodded.

"I rarely try a second time, but I would like to ask you again personally."

Heber raised his arm out to Han Xiao and said in a solemn tone, "Black Star, join me."

Boom!

Ames' aura exploded, and an immense pressure was exuded.

Her tone was chilly.

"Trying to poach one of my men before me, do you not respect me at all‽"

The frightening pressure assaulted Heber from all directions, but it seemed as though he could not feel it. He ignored Ames and fixed his gaze on Han Xiao. "Do you agree or not?"

Han Xiao's face began contorting.

Oh my goodness, poaching someone so openly, he is truly tyrannical.

He had never expected Heber to personally make an invitation at this moment. This fellow truly did not care about what the occasion was and only about how hard his fists are!

"My apologies, but my answer is the same." Han Xiao shook his head helplessly.

Heber nodded and was not angered by the rejection. It was as though he had never brought up this topic at all.

He liked talents but was not willing to force someone who did not want to submit.

The force field was still growing in strength, and Heber turned around to look at Ames. "Aren't you going to stop your force field? Do you want to fight?"

Ames remained expressionless as her aura continued to grow. She almost wanted to completely ignore the advice that Aesop had given her.

Austin could only interfere helplessly lest they ended up fighting. With a snap of his fingers, he cast a calming spell on Ames.

"Alright, alright, this isn't the first day you've known her. Don't act so rashly."

Chapter 612: Resource Battle?

"Here will do." Carroll brought the others to Bloodshed Land's Open Air Combat Training Ground No. 30 and stood opposite Han Xiao. He then moved a long distance away till Han Xiao became a small dot in his eyes.

Han Xiao looked around. This training ground was empty and unobstructed. Around its edges were tall mechanical towers connected by dozens of blue, high-temperature electromagnetic wires. It looked like a futuristic baseball field but many times larger.

The floor was made of gray metal plates. Burn marks left by explosions and slash marks could be seen all around the place, some pits too. Clearly, this training ground was often used.

"In my territory, you have to follow my rules." Carroll's voice came from afar. "First, the battle area is limited to this training ground. If you cause destruction outside of this, you'll bear the consequences. Second, causing severe damage to the opponent is not allowed. So, don't worry, your life won't be in danger."

As Carroll spoke, he activated the training ground. The floor trembled. Pits appeared from the metal floor, and mechanical soldiers rose up one after another, surrounding Carroll.

Hum!

The mechanical towers at the edge of the training ground vibrated. A beam of light shot out from their peaks, gathering on top, forming a projection of a three-minute timer.

Carroll smirked and said, "Don't say I'm bullying you. Before we start, you have three minutes to prepare. After three minutes, this place will be covered by a protective shield."

Black Star was a guest. He would not have brought too many combat machines, and they would most probably be stored in his ship. By giving him three minutes to get the machines, after the shield covered the place, Black Star would be unable to receive external support and would only be able to fight with the machines in the venue.

As for Carroll, he had a continuous supply of armies because Combat Training Ground No. 30 was a facility that released machines from below to let people train with them. Many routes used to transport mechanical soldiers were hidden under the metal plates on the floor, connected to the logistics warehouse underground. This meant that even with the protective shield, Carroll could obtain a nonstop supply of backup.

Carroll knew that a battle between two Mechanics would most likely become a battle of resources. Black Star had limited resources while he had infinite, so he was already undefeated.

The protective shield was transparent. It was a perfect opportunity for him to publicly shame Black Star.

He could basically foresee the ending of the battle—Black Star's machines would be used up, scraps would be everywhere, Black Star himself would be surrounded by his army, and he could look down on Black Star from a high spot casually, making Black Star admit his defeat.

Ames wanted to let her subordinate vent her anger, so defeating her subordinate would make her even more embarrassed.

Furthermore, he did not hide his main stage advantage. If Black Star cowered from it and cancelled the challenge, knowing it would end in his defeat, Ames would lose face as well.

One way or another, he was only going to benefit from it.

Carroll smiled confidently.

On the other side, Han Xiao was not surprised by Carroll's main stage advantage at all. He contacted Risda and told him to bring the Blacklight Stealth over, airdropping his Army Boxes.

Ames was still standing by him. "Black Star, are you confident?"

"A little," Han Xiao replied casually.

"Then, I shall trust you."

Ames' tone was gentle like the wind. Although Han Xiao challenging Carroll to a battle surprised her, it was clear that Han Xiao was doing it for her. She was happy for some reason.

She had always placed a lot of trust in Han Xiao, and this was no exception. She patted Han Xiao's shoulders and took Hila and Aurora out of the place. They went up the tall building beside the training ground and watched the fight from above.

Around the training ground, there were people climbing up the buildings to watch the fight every minute. There were hundreds of them, all Bloodshed Land officers or elite soldiers. Malekith and a few other Vanguard Officials were among them. They formed small groups and chatted.

The fight between Carroll and Black Star was not kept secret; the message very quickly got passed to the officers. They all came to the scene to watch the battle.

"Black Star is quite daring to challenge our officer in our territory," a Vanguard Official said as he looked at the two people in the venue.

"He challenged Carroll because he's Floating Dragon's traitor?"

"Must be. A few days ago, Ames was forced to hold back by His Excellency Tyrant. She's probably resentful, so she let Black Star fight for her. Hehe, it'll be embarrassing to lose." Someone looked at Ames who was also watching from afar and speculated, "Maybe Ames will stop the fight when her subordinate is in danger."

"Carroll's strength, tsk..." Malekith shook his head slightly.

The impression that the Vanguard Officials had of Carroll was very complicated. On one hand, he was a traitor. Although Tyrant was confident using him, him being a traitor still made others not want to get close to him.

On the other hand, Carroll was in charge of logistics and had almost no opportunity to fight. Unlike them, the Vanguard Officials, who were signatures of Bloodshed Land and all well known, Malekith and the others did not know Carroll's strength clearly. All they knew was that he was also Grade A.

"He has the location advantage no matter what, so he basically won't lose."

...

In the palace, Heber was still casually chatting with Austin.

This time, Austin's expression suddenly changed, and he said in a strange tone, "Tyrant, it seems that a problem is occurring in your territory."

Heber frowned, took out his communicator, pressed a few times, and got the report from his subordinates.

"Black Star challenged Carroll?"

Austin cast a spell, and space rippled. A large mirror appeared, showing the scene of the training ground.

"It seems like they're about to fight. Aren't you going to stop them?" Austin asked.

Heber looked at the mirror, thought for a moment, and shook his head. "Since Ames is not involved, I have no reason to stop a normal spar."

"What if your man loses?"

"My Bloodshed Land is not one to never admit defeat." Heber pointed at the mirror. "Keep watching."

...

At the same time, three party guests were following a Bloodshed Land soldier and touring the place.

The Purple Crystal Civilization's representative Ralph was walking side by side with a high-ranking Klent official and having a great chat. The relationship between Purple Crystal and Klent had always been good.

Behind them, the leader of a financial group followed. His name was Rossozzi. His business was huge and invested in both Star Clusters. He could be somewhat considered Ralph and the Klent high ranking official's friend.

The three of them were discussing business issues, when a group of people suddenly flew over them, catching their attention.

"Where are those people going?' Ralph asked curiously.

The soldier shook his head and said, "I don't know. They seem to be heading toward Combat Training Ground No. 30.

Just as he was done speaking, another group of people bolted past them from above, and a dark spaceship quickly flew by.

The three of them were all knowledgeable people. They recognized that the spaceship was the Federation of Light's Stealth Grade spaceship. Of all the guests, it seemed like only one person had a Blacklight Stealth.

Floating Dragon's Black Star!

The Klent high ranking official was instantly interested. "Looks like something happened. Let's go and take a look."

Ralph shrugged and did not mind it, neither did Rossozzi.

...

When the countdown had about a minute and a half left, the Blacklight Stealth arrived above the venue. Six Army Boxes descended from above like meteors, dragging a long tail of flames.

Han Xiao raised his hand toward the sky, and a bolt of tree-shaped lightning shot up into the sky from the ground, hitting the six Army Boxes. They opened in midair, and compressed orbs fell like rain onto the floor.

Clank!

The instant they landed, the compressed orbs expanded and turned into six Mechanical Armies.

Mechanical Beast Guards Army, Strike Artillery Regiment, G-1 Steel Army Corps, G-2 Heavy Armor Riders, and Mini Cube Troops occupied the venue and surrounded Han Xiao. Han Xiao was in a sea of machines.

Twelve Elite Oathkeepers guarded Han Xiao. Their exterior armor rippled from head to toe like moving scales, carrying out a self-check.

All sorts of artilleries landed behind him or hovered in midair. Other than the regular electromagnetic artilleries and laser artilleries, there were the new lava artilleries and heat artilleries.

The number of troops is a little high.

Carroll was surprised.

Nonetheless, he was still completely confident.

Black Star's Mechanical Army only occupied a small part of the training ground, while his Mechanical Army had a much higher number and almost occupied half of the place.

And it was still increasing.

There was a round of machinery transport gates at the edge of the training ground. Standard mechanical soldiers crawled out one after another, surrounding Black Star's army.

Almost endless backup, this was where Carroll's confidence came from.

So many machines. Black Star definitely spent a lot of time and money.

Evil intentions flashed through Carroll's eyes.

If I destroy all his machines, Black Star's strength will be greatly decreased. His stock will all be gone.

The formation was complete. Since there would be a protective shield later, Han Xiao did not use Eye of God. He checked through the machines; there was around ten seconds left on the timer.

Boom!

The mechanical towers at the edges activated. A light blue shield slowly rose up and shrouded the venue. All the spectators were blocked outside.

The ceiling was hundreds of meters high. When the shield completely closed, the countdown would end.

The style, technology, and model of the machines controlled by Carroll were all clearly different from Han Xiao's. Most of them were standard disposable machines.

Buzz!

The two of them released Mechanical Force at the same time. Thunder and lightning roared. Calamity Grade Mechanics had the [Mechanical Force Field] ability, which made the Mechanical Force enhancements cover an area. The entire place was covered.

After so long, I've finally encountered a Mechanic of the same grade. Han Xiao squinted. This was his first time battling a Mechanic of his grade.

Berserk Ape wrapped around his body, and a virtual screen appeared before him, displaying the Virtual Intrusion image.

Carroll was not a Virtual Mechanic; he wore a Single Unit Mechanical Suit. Pieces of armor extended from his armor and quickly turned into a more than thirty-meter-tall heavy fortress, covering Carroll from all angles. The thick and heavy armor clearly had impressive defensive capabilities.

From the gap between the fortress, many large-caliber cannons extended out.

Carroll used the Heavy Machinery Style. Large size; heavy, thick armor; strong firepower... those were the clear specialties. This was a heavy, defensive carrier. Carroll wanted to make use of his advantage in a battle of resources, so he gave himself a hard, thick turtle shell.

He was not Han Xiao; he did not have a tough body and was most afraid of enemies rushing close. Therefore, he used a defensive strategy and planned to not even let Han Xiao touch him.

"Correct method." Malekith and the other spectators nodded. They did not think that Carroll was a coward—this was a suitable strategy given the situation.

Just as Carroll's fortress was fully expended, the shield completely closed, and the countdown ended!

Boom!

The next instant, lasers flashed, and cannon fire roared!

The battle had erupted!

Han Xiao's Mechanical Army clashed with Carroll's!

Boom boom boom!

The armies fought intensely; the scene became chaotic.

Machines could not talk, so they fought in silence. Metal crashed against metal, creating bright sparks.

Boom!

The large-caliber cannons on Carroll's heavy fortress locked onto Han Xiao and fired. Every shot made the barrels recoil instantly. The sound of firing was like a hammer smashing onto metal.

Hu!

Huge balls of light went straight to Han Xiao, and the high temperature bent the air around them.

Just as they were about to hit Han Xiao, Watcher Instrument opened like a peacock opening its feathers. It appeared behind Han Xiao and flew in front of him, turning into force field bending shields. The attacks did not explode when hitting the shield but were diverted toward other directions.

Bang bang bang!

All the cannon fire was deflected. Some shots flew far away, hit the protective shield, and exploded; some landed on the ground, stirring up a strong wind, tearing down the mechanical soldiers of both sides in the area.

Han Xiao glanced around. He clenched his fist. Mechanical Force lightning landed on the parts on the ground. [Waste Modification] resurrected his mechanical soldiers, allowing them to continue the battle.

Seeing this, Carroll stopped attacking Han Xiao. His heavy fortress started targeting Han Xiao's Mechanical Army, wanting to quickly eliminate Black Star's army.

"It won't be so easy!" Han Xiao snorted.

Buzz!

He raised his hand. The pipe on his arm launched a string of compressed orbs. They expanded midair and turned into more than ten huge mechanical arms. The next second, these mechanical arms nano-shapeshifted, combined together, and turned into a hundred-meter-wide palm, three times bigger than Carroll's heavy fortress!

Han Xiao waved his hand. The gigantic palm slapped right down onto the top of the heavy fortress, like a palm hitting a ping pong ball.

Boom!

The wind blew away the surrounding mechanical soldiers. Even through the protective shield, Malekith and the others outside could feel it.

The metal ground cracked open from the heavy pressure, but the heavy fortress was covered by a shield and was hardly damaged.

Inside the heavy fortress, Carroll sneered. This fortress was not something ordinary but an important equipment that he had made; it could block Calamity Grade attacks.

This time, Carroll felt the fortress suddenly start trembling.

The gigantic palm's fingers bent and pulled the heavy fortress out of the ground. Like throwing a baseball, it swung and sent the heavy fortress flying across a long distance, heavily landing on the protective shield and creating a string of electrical sparks.

Boom!

The Bloodshed Land elites in that direction of the protective shield almost fell from seeing a huge pile of metal flying toward them.

The heavy fortress rolled and landed on the ground, shaking the floor. However, the shield still protected the fortress. Its damage was negligible—remarkable defense. Only Carroll, who was inside, suffered from the sudden fall.

Malekith saw this and analyzed, "Carroll's defense is very strong. Black Star seems to be unable to break through Carroll's armor. It looks like this battle will be under Carroll's control and turned into a complete battle of resources. That's Black Star's fatal weakness."

Chapter 613: Turned Table

"This fortress's defense is quite good. It's Grade A equipment."

Excitement flashed through Han Xiao's eyes.

Carroll's information popped up on the interface. His level was higher, some of his attributes and abilities were question marks, and his Energy Rank and health could not be seen.

Han Xiao was not surprised. He was only level 142, so even regular Grade As had a higher level than him.

The heavy fortress' defense was very strong but not indestructible. However, Han Xiao did not want to fight head-on. As a Virtual Mechanic, he had his professional ethics. He started Virtual Intrusion and gave the controls of the gigantic palm to Phillip.

"Phillip, have some fun with him. Block his fire and don't let him destroy too much of my army."

"Order confirmed. Executing, hum..."

The gigantic palm slapped down again. Suddenly, the bottom of the heavy fortress emitted thrusting flames. The bulky fortress took off and dodged the attack, moving quickly in midair.

This was a flying fortress.

The gigantic palm chased the heavy fortress, and they started to duel in midair.

As Han Xiao focused on Virtual Intrusion, flames surrounded him, and the Mechanical Armies of the two sides fought intensely.

The strength of the five newly updated armies did not just increase by a little. Turquoise lava cannons blasted through iron; heat cannons melted metal; Space Bending Bombs were like mini black holes, creating vortexes in space everywhere they exploded; not to mention, the Mini Nuclear Mines could even plant mushrooms.

The Cube Army formed teams of three sizes: normal-sized Mini Cube Robots, small fused mechanical soldiers about half a man tall, and robots that were the height of a mini giant. They all had their advantages; some were swift, and some were tough.

The G-2 Heavy Armor Riders slashed right through the enemies. All sorts of melee weapons shattered their foes into countless parts all over the floor, creating blank spaces on the battlefield like erasers.

The performance of Han Xiao's Mechanical Army was an entire level higher than Carroll's standard mechanical soldiers; they were all semi elites.

The efficiency of the slaughter was exceptional, cutting down Carroll's mechanical army area by area.

Han Xiao's Mechanical Army had the upper hand from the moment the battle started.

However, the backup came nonstop and could not be fully eliminated. The wreckages stacked up on the ground. Carroll was dedicated to using up Han Xiao's stash; he did not even control the army to attack Han Xiao and only focused on his Mechanical Army. He did not care even if he had to lose three of his units in exchange for one of Han Xiao's.

As such, Han Xiao's five armies were slowly losing numbers.

The mechanical soldiers that occasionally got close to Han Xiao were either blasted by the Watcher Instrument or shattered by Oathkeepers.

This kind of battle of resources was like a stalemate.

A Vanguard Official could not help but ask, "How long are they going to fight for?"

Malekith shook his head and said, "At least a few hours."

This time, another shadow jumped up. The other Vanguard Officials looked over and were shocked.

"Number two, you're here too!"

"Hmm, the commander told me to take a look." The person who had just arrived was a tall, skinny human. His body shape was a breath of fresh air among the muscular men that filled Bloodshed Land.

This guy's nickname was Hunting Blade. There were different styles among the Pugilist class, not just the brutal style. The one that he took involved using swift weapons. He was ranked second among the Eight Vanguard Officials, hence, number two.

There were rankings among the eight Vanguard Officials. The commander Vanguard Official was the boss; he was the most senior and strongest among the Vanguard Officials. He had been receiving personal guidance from Heber, reaching Grade A+, and was a training maniac. He spent almost all his free time in training. Second seat Hunting Blade was very strong, too. The two of them usually carried out more dangerous missions and could hardly be seen. Now that Hunting Blade had suddenly appeared, it surprised the other Vanguard Officials.

Upon briefly looking at the battle, Hunting Blade quickly analyzed it and slowly said, "Black Star looks to be having the upper hand but is actually stuck. Carroll wants to drag the battle out, so Black Star must quickly end the battle. If he can't penetrate Carroll's defense, when his armies are too damaged, the situation will take a direct turn downward, and he will lose for sure."

"That's what I thought." Malekith nodded. "The situation is looking good. Carroll has the home advantages and is considerably strong. Black Star has a very slim chance of winning."

"Carroll is... not too bad."

Hunting Blade nodded and expressed his approval for Carroll's strength.

On the other side, Ralph and the other two arrived. They climbed up the building to watch the battle, asked the spectators around them, and figured out what was going on.

"Black Star challenged Bloodshed Land's officer in their territory? He's got some guts."

Ralph was shocked.

"He's doing it for Ames. Floating Dragon Island's current officer challenging an ex-officer and traitor, it's meaningful." The high-ranking Klent official chuckled.

Ralph nodded. He turned to look at Ames, who was not far away, and realized that Ames was completely focused on the battle.

Boom!

The attacks from both sides never stopped, and it was entering a stalemate.

Suddenly, Carroll's heavy fortress sped up in an instant and distanced itself from the gigantic palm before shapeshifting.

The heavy machines split up into mechanical parts and combined again. At the same time, Carroll threw out a pile of compressed orbs that expanded into new parts. Countless parts quickly fused together.

In the blink of an eye, the parts became a forty-meter-tall huge, human-shaped mechanical suit!

Large Battle Suit, [Giant Soldier—Ship Destroyer]!

The Ship Destroyer was human-shaped. It had two arms and two legs but no head. Its top was the tapered ending of its body. Its color was striped black and green. Thick, heavy armor covered its joints and weaknesses. It was wide and short on top, and narrow and long below. Its legs were equipped with thrusters and caterpillar track wheels. Its body was covered in mounted weapons, and behind it was a pair of metal thruster wings.

To describe it in a simpler way, this thing looked like an upside-down green trash can with limbs and wings.

Carroll looked at Han Xiao from above before sitting in the cockpit in the middle of its body.

Bang!

The Ship Destroyer made a swift roll after landing, its huge body shaking the ground. It then half squatted on the floor and pulled out a Thermal Melting Sword with one hand as its other hand's armored plate expanded into a huge bulky alloy shield.

The Heavy Machinery Style replied on various enormous machines for combat. These large mechanical suits were usually called Giant Soldier Mechanical Suits. Its thirty to forty meters height could compare to some smaller spaceships.

Such a large size meant that more energy sources and complex structures could be included inside, so its performance was remarkably high, and it could be used to battle in space. It was equivalent to a more mobile and agile galactic carrier.

Virtual Mechanics could take part in universe wars by hacking; Heavy Armor Mechanics could build these Gundam-like Giant Soldiers to fight battleships.

The Ship Destroyer Giant Soldier held the alloy shield in front and started sprinting forward. Its shield heavily clashed with Han Xiao's gigantic palm. The tremendous force instantly deflected the gigantic palm aside. Overpowering the gigantic palm twice its size, the Ship Destroyer raised its Thermal Melting Sword and slashed horizontally across the battlefield.

Hu!

The high temperature produced white light that slashed across a huge area. Friend or foe, countless mechanical soldiers were shattered into pieces by the heavy sword.

Han Xiao squinted. The Watcher Instrument fused together into a large caliber cannon. A bucket thick dark blue light beam launched out and landed straight on the Ship Destroyer's chest.

Hum!

A light-yellow shield appeared and blocked this light beam. The light beam exploded into countless pieces and could not hurt the Ship Destroyer itself.

Even Gundam is out. He's really motivated.

Han Xiao curled his lips. He was not surprised at all. After so many days of peeking, he had seen Carroll maintaining this Giant Soldier mechanical suit several times.

The Class Advancement of a Mechanic also affected the result of fusing blueprints. After choosing one branch, other than the Potential Point cost of learning knowledges from the other branches being tripled, some of the blueprints of the other two branches could not be fused.

Han Xiao had chosen Virtual Mechanic, so when he gambled on blueprints, he could not get some of the Heavy Armor Mechanic blueprints, such as Giant Soldiers like the Ship Destroyer.

Carroll clearly did not use the Giant Soldier to just defeat Han Xiao; it would be like trying to kill a mosquito with a cannon.

His goal was to use the Giant Soldier to quickly wipe out Black Star's Mechanical Army.

He did not want to use the Ship Destroyer trump card initially, but the quality of Black Star's Mechanical Army was beyond his expectations. His disposable troops died too fast, and the backup could barely keep up. If he did not use the Giant Soldier, Carroll worried that he might have lost control of the situation.

"Carroll turned from defensive to offensive. Even I can feel the energy wave of this Giant Soldier. It's very strong. It would take me a very long time to defeat it." Outside the protective shield, shocked, Malekith's impression of Carroll improved.

Hunting Blade nodded. "Now, this is decent."

Far away in the palace, Heber let out a faint hum, expressing commendation.

At this time, a sudden change occurred on the battlefield!

The mechanical soldiers on the training ground suddenly all stopped moving as if someone had pressed the 'pause' button.

Carroll was stunned. Just as he wanted to control the Ship Destroyer and move, what he got was a bunch of random noises from the control panel. The artificial intelligence did not reply at all, and the nerves connection completely stopped working.

The Ship Destroyer stood still just like all the machines on the training ground.

The battlefield that had just been filled with bullets suddenly became deadly silent.

The sudden change caused the expressions of all the spectators to stiffen.

Ding!

A crisp sound came from the Berserk Ape's Virtual Intrusion panel.

Han Xiao clenched his face and snickered.

His voice traveled out, extremely loud and clear on the completely silent battlefield, so everyone could hear him.

"Alright, the foreplay is finished."

Han Xiao clearly knew that Carroll had the home advantage, so he had never been willing to turn this into a battle of resources. He had used the Mechanical Armies to stall the enemy's troops and give himself time to use Virtual Intrusion.

Now, with Risda and Phillip's support, the hacking was complete.

These standard machines were all controlled by the same artificial intelligence, which was beaten up by Risda and had lost control. All the machines controlled by Carroll stopped functioning—they would only recover after a system reboot.

Taking the opportunity, Han Xiao walked toward the Giant Soldier.

Dong! Dong!

As he walked forward, rows and rows of mechanical soldiers fell to the ground, all paralyzed. The scene was magnificent, like thousands of people kneeling to welcome their king!

One word, glorious!

Han Xiao walked forward unobstructed—this was the easiest process of closing the distance he ever had.

Virtual Mechanics were best at fighting other Mechanics. As the saying went, 'No cannons, no guns? The enemy will build for us.'

Seeing all his machines being taken over by Han Xiao, Carroll's face inside the Ship Destroyer cockpit was furious. He felt a strong sense of humiliation.

As a Mechanic, when his machines were taken away by someone else, it was an indescribable feeling, like losing all dignity.

"Quickly, reboot the system!" Carroll yelled.

"Dia—Diagnosing, getting rid of the virus, estimated time unknown..."

An alarm echoed in the cockpit, accompanied by a piercing noise.

"Sh*t, it's too late!" Seeing Han Xiao approaching, Carroll finally started to panic.

However, he still held onto the last bit of hope. As Black Star wanted to do this as quickly as possible, he only used the most brutal way to paralyze the Ship Destroyer's operating system and did not obtain its control. Therefore, he could still hide in the Ship Destroyer.

As long as Han Xiao did not penetrate the Ship Destroyer's armor before he rebooted the system, he would still have a chance to regain control of the situation.

However, the next moment, Carroll's last hope was gone.

All of Han Xiao's Mechanical Army aimed at the Ship Destroyer, and countless attacks covered the sky. The Ship Destroyer's shield only lasted two seconds against those attacks before shattering.

Boom!

The chest armor was focused on as explosions erupted. The Ship Destroyer could not handle such a strong force and collapsed to the ground, face up.

The gigantic hand disassembled itself and turned into more than ten large mechanical hands, which became drills and dug out a hole in the Ship Destroyer's body.

Between the wires and energy pipes, Carroll's cockpit was exposed.

Due to the system failure, Carroll could not even parachute out. The Ship Destroyer became a cell that imprisoned him.

Looking at Han Xiao jumping into the cockpit, with a horrified expression, Carroll hastily said, "I admit..."

Before he could finish, Han Xiao's large hand grabbed onto his mouth like an iron claw, making Carroll swallow the rest of his words.

"Go!"

Berserk Throw!

Boom!

Carroll was thrown out of the Ship Destroyer and flew right into the sky rolling, ascending hundreds of meters quickly and landing on the ceiling of the training ground's shield.

He did not have a strong physique. Despite being Calamity Grade Super, his toughness was far beneath that of a Pugilist. His head was spinning from this throw, and he entered the [Stunned] state from the Berserk Throw.

However, before he landed, Han Xiao flew right under him in an instant.

Hundreds of meters was just one leap for Berserk Ape.

Buzz!

The next second, blinding lightning emerged from Han Xiao's body, illuminating Carroll's terrified expression.

Like pulling a bow, Han Xiao's arms pulled back before his fists bashed down heavily onto Carroll's chest, pressing him onto the ceiling of the protective shield.

Boom!

Like a ball of lightning in midair.

Power Detonation!

Gene Liberation!

Germinal Organization Leader Character Summon Card—Armor Piercing Consecutive Attacks!

Han Xiao did not hold back. With the three layers of bonuses, his attack power was elevated to a terrifying level.

Boom!

The explosive soundwave created a circular wave.

The power of this punch penetrated Carroll's body and shattered the protective shield of the entire training ground!

Amid the shattered shield, Carroll flew up into the sky like a rocket, leaving circles of expanding waves.

Dark red blood dripped from the sky.

All the Bloodshed Land spectators opened their mouths wide and looked up at Carroll, who was flying into the sky.

Malekith was stunned. In just ten seconds, Han Xiao had ended the battle of resources and finished the duel.

It was way too fast!

So fast that he could barely react to it!

Chapter 614: Official Party

Carroll flew higher and higher.

While the other spectators were stunned, Hunting Blade was the first to react. He jumped up into the sky, caught up to Carroll's ascending body, and grabbed Carroll with his hands like a chicken, not giving Carroll the chance to yell, "I'll be back!"

The two of them landed in the training ground filled with machine scraps, stirring up a wave of dust.

As soon as Hunting Blade let go, Carroll collapsed to the ground. With one hand supporting himself and another clutching his chest, he coughed nonstop.

"Ahem..."

Blood spilled from the corners of Carroll's mouth, his face pale. Despite wearing a simple single unit battle suit, this punch still did quite a lot of damage to him.

However, he had the physique of a Calamity Grade Super. Although it was far from Pugilists', he did not lose combat capability from one attack; he had just broken a few bones, and his lungs had almost exploded.

Although Han Xiao did not hold back at all, he knew that a Calamity Grade would not be heavily injured easily given the fact that they still had energy to protect their body. Furthermore, this was a spar; he could not kill one of Bloodshed Land's men in their territory. Beating the opponent was enough.

Virtual Intrusion had created an opportunity, and Han Xiao had always been good at grabbing opportunities. He was cautious, too. In order to prevent any accidents, he did not ridicule Carroll and directly blew him away, guaranteeing his victory.

Carroll's injuries were not too severe, and he still had the ability to fight. However, he had been blown out of the venue, and the machines that he controlled were temporarily paralyzed. Even though he could continue to fight after the system rebooted, it was clear that he had been defeated by Black Star.

The battle had ended, and the result was his defeat.

"You..."

Carroll's face was filled with frustration. He clutched his chest and coughed a few more times while glaring at Han Xiao, who landed nearby.

"Sigh, that was close. I almost lost."

Han Xiao removed Berserk Ape, smiled, and shook his head.

Bullsh*t! You clearly won easily! many spectators screamed in their minds.

Han Xiao looked at the Virtual Intrusion panel. There was close to no time left before Carroll's artificial intelligence rebooted, so he looked around and said, "You've lost. There are so many people watching. You'll accept it, won't you?"

Carroll noticed the eyes of the spectators on him. He clenched his teeth and felt beaten. He had a huge home advantage but was easily defeated by Black Star. This guy's combat capability was too strong...

The identity difference between the two of them amplified the effect of his loss.

Black Star was Floating Dragon Island's current officer, whereas he was a traitor in others' eyes. Now that the traitor had been defeated by someone from Floating Dragon, it was clearly the result people wanted to see. Not to mention, he had just provoked Ames a few days ago, and then he was beaten by Black Star. With those thoughts in mind, Carroll felt extremely embarrassed.

Carroll looked in Ames' direction subconsciously, only to notice that Ames did not even look at him, the loser, but at Black Star. This made him even more furious.

In the spectator area outside, Ames exhaled lightly and smiled in relief.

At the moment Black Star blasted Carroll away with that thunderous punch, she had felt the unhappiness that she had kept in over the past few days all disappear, vented with Han Xiao's punch. She immediately felt that even the sun was brighter.

Ames found that Han Xiao looked pleasing to her eyes no matter how she looked at him, so she kept staring at Han Xiao.

As for the person whom she had always been 'thinking about', Carroll, Ames did not even want to take another look at him. The position of this traitor had become nothing in her eyes; she had let it go.

"I have someone better," Ames murmured.

Not far away, Ralph sighed. He had only met Black Star a few days ago. At that moment, Han Xiao's position in his mind became slightly higher. "Dragon Emperor found a spectacular guy."

If there's a chance in the future, maybe I can entrust some sensitive missions to Black Star... Ralph pondered and thought about hiring Black Star Army. The Purple Crystal Civilization ruled Colton, and Black Star Army's stronghold was in Colton, so there was a natural reason for them to work together.

Rossozzi rubbed the tentacles on his chin. On the surface, he was not affected at all, but in his mind, he thought. I heard that Noriosse have invested in the Black Star Army. They have quite the potential. Hmm... seems worth investing in them.

After socializing over the past few days, he knew Black Star, too. Due to the fact that there were many important people among the guests, he did not make any proposals to Han Xiao; only now did he think of investing.

The high-ranking Klent official squinted slightly and suddenly said, "Black Star defeated Tyrant's man in Bloodshed Land. What will Heber do?"

Not far away, Malekith and the other Vanguard Officials were thinking about this question, too.

Someone frowned and asked, "Will His Excellency Heber interfere?"

Malekith shook his head. "This is a spar, so probably not..."

Carroll's defeat was certain. The Vanguard Officials were used to battle; they were not too shocked or stunned by the result, only surprised by Black Star's strength.

Many Vanguard Official were eager to spar with Han Xiao, too.

The question that they were most interested in at the moment was Heber's stand toward this.

At the same time, in the palace...

"Your man lost," Austin said jokingly.

"I have eyes." Heber frowned slightly before waving his hand. "Nothing to watch anymore, turn it off."

"Aren't you going to reply?"

"No need to." Heber was not angry. Since it was a fair fight and Black Star had won fair and square, it just showed how capable Black Star was.

Austin stopped the stream, and the two of them stopped paying attention to the incident.

Heber did not interfere, but no one thought that he did not know about this. Seeing nothing happened, they understood that Heber approved of the result of this battle.

Bloodshed Land believed in strength; Carroll being defeated publicly made the others embarrassed, too.

Many spectators shook their heads and left. Malekith and the others gave Carroll a disappointed look and disappeared.

Carroll knew that the result was decided and had nothing to say.

"Don't forget our bet," Han Xiao kindly reminded.

"What blueprints do you want?" Carroll clenched his teeth. The Tyrant definitely knew about the bet. If he did not live up to it, it would bring shame to Bloodshed Land.

He did not have a choice but to carry out the promise.

"Let me think, the mechanic fortress earlier and that Giant Soldier mechanical suit. I want these two." Han Xiao chuckled.

"Okay!" Carroll's heart was bleeding.

Then, Han Xiao requested three other blueprints. He had peeked at Carroll's weapon inventory before, and there were many things that he wanted, but Carroll did not use all of them in the battle, so Han Xiao could not request them.

As a Virtual Mechanic, although he could not fuse the blueprints for some exclusive machines from other branches, he could still directly learn them if he obtained the blueprint. After all, when gambling on blueprints, a single knowledge combination had dozens of possible blueprint outcomes. Class Advancements only made some of them unavailable, but with the blueprint, as long as his knowledge met the requirements, he could build that machine.

"I will give you the blueprints tomorrow. You don't have to worry about me going back on my word; I have at least this much credibility."

Frustrated, Carroll said that before leaving without even cleaning up the training ground. He did not even dare look at Ames.

Unbothered, Han Xiao looked at the interface notification.

[Ames' Fury] Completed!

You have received 15,000,000 Experience

You have received +15 Renown

+2500 Floating Dragon Faction Favorability

+20 Ames Favorability. Current relationship: [Confidant]

+2 Heber Favorability. Current Relationship: [Indifferent]

This time, Ames landed beside Han Xiao with a smile on her face.

"Good fight."

"Well, I couldn't keep watching you get bullied," Han Xiao joked and found an excuse to explain his actions.

"I know." Ames smiled faintly. She suddenly felt somewhat nostalgic.

Ever since she reached Beyond Grade A, it had been a very long time since she had felt what it was like to be protected. She had never expected to feel that way again.

I'm so much stronger than Black Star, but he was the one that helped me in the end... Ames laughed in her heart.

Aurora looked up at Han Xiao, then at Ames. She tugged on the edge of Hila's clothes and said softly, "Big sister..."

Hila looked straight and coldly said, "What?"

"No—Nothing..." Aurora shrank back.

...

After collecting his machines and placing them into the Blacklight Stealth, Han Xiao and the others returned to their rooms.

This challenge did not cause anything afterward, but very soon, all the party guests knew about the battle between Han Xiao and Carroll through the spectators.

Black Star had fought for Ames in Bloodshed Land, defeating Floating Dragon Island's traitor openly in the Tyrant's territory, and the Tyrant approved it with silence. Black Star had gained respect on the Dragon Emperor's behalf, and many were surprised.

After the battle, the day passed peacefully.

The next day, the official party finally started.

The people had waited days for the official party.

All the guests dressed up neatly and formally, gathering in Heber's palace hall. This place had been rearranged into a party venue. There were all kinds of rare food and drinks as well as musicians standing by at the side.

Not just the hall, around half of the entire palace was the party venue, all arranged properly. The guests could walk around the place as they like. There were also many small, private rooms upstairs for guests that wanted to communicate privately.

The goal of the party was to invite the people of the top organizations in Shattered Star Ring to discuss all sorts of topics, expand their connections, build relationships, exchange information, plan the development of the Shattered Star Ring, and so on. It was like a social club but more serious, business-focused, and high class.

The guests were chatting with each other. Ames stood by the side and did not talk to anyone. Hila and Aurora were beside her. They did not know what to say during this kind of occasion, so they did not speak either.

Han Xiao was socializing on behalf of Ames. People came to chat with him passionately from time to time. He dealt with the guests while at the same time observing others, quietly collecting information.

Not a long wait after, the host of the party, Heber, finally appeared. The place instantly became quiet. Everyone stopped talking and looked at Heber, waiting for him to speak.

"I'm glad to see so many familiar faces this time once again." Heber looked around. "I hope you guys will benefit from this party like always. So... let the party begin."

Chapter 615: Austin's Gift

As the musicians started to play, the party officially began. The guests all had their own goals. They split into twos and threes and headed to more private areas to discuss business.

Heber took a few guests up the stairs. Not far away, the Klent high ranking official also went upstairs with a few others.

Seeing this, Han Xiao squinted and pondered.

The Tyrant and the Klents are allies. He has already secretly joined the Crimson Dynasty's side, so maybe the Klents have become the Crimson Dynasty's friend, probably even earlier than Tyrant. After all, the Crimson Dynasty wants to rope in the Shattered Star Ring's organizations, so their priority should be the Star Cluster Civilizations. The Klents got persuaded first, then recommended Bloodshed Land as an ally. The reason Heber introduced the envoy to the Dragon Emperor and Magus might be because the Klents asked him to negotiate with the Beyond Grade A Supers...

This would mean that in the seven Star Cluster Civilizations of Shattered Star Ring, Klent Kingdom might have already joined the Crimson Dynasty's side.

Connecting to the storyline of his previous life, the main storyline of Version 3.0 [Crimson Tide] was the Crimson Dynasty's expansion stirring up all the Star Fields, including the Shattered Star Ring. However, most of that chaos were not directly caused by the Crimson Dynasty but the organizations of these Star Fields themselves.

Back then, the players did not have access to any inside knowledge. After Han Xiao connected these two things... the Crimson Dynasty might have been behind all the organizations that caused trouble during [Crimson Tide]. They pulled strings and made the structure of the universe unstable.

Heber did not introduce Zoel to all the guests, probably because the Crimson Dynasty did not want to be too high profile. They might have only invited some representatives of the stronger organizations to private meetings, like the Beyond Grade A meeting a day ago.

So, the storm is already brewing...

Han Xiao shook his head. According to his calculations, the effect brought by the Crimson Dynasty's actions would not appear in Version 2.0. The most likely scenario would be these effects gradually appearing over the ten or so years during the version update after Version 2.0, which would then turn into the Version 3.0, [Crimson Tide].

Currently, it was only the early stage of Version 2.0. Other than the Planet Aquamarine players, the players on other novice planets were still playing with mud. There were still a few more years till the next version update. During this period, the likelihood of something huge erupting was very low.

Planet Aquamarine's original main storyline was the conflict between DarkStar and Godora. However, DarkStar was gone, so his Black Star Army had become the players' new main storyline. The storyline was now semi free exploration, so the players would not face something huge in Version 2.0.

This was the best time for his faction to grow.

As the Great Mechanic Han was contemplating, Rossozzi approached.

"Black Star, I have some things I want to speak to you about."

Han Xiao stopped his train of thought, smiled, and nodded. "Mr. Rossozzi, what is it?"

Rossozzi rubbed the messy tentacles on his chin and said, "I want to invest in Floating Dragon Island and your Black Star Army. Maybe we should discuss the detailed terms and conditions."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. Lucky, another one here to give me money!

He turned around and looked at Ames. Ames did not disapprove and let Han Xiao fully handle it. Han Xiao pulled Rossozzi aside, and the two of them discussed the details.

Not long after, the two of them quickly decided on the investment plan. Similar to the terms and conditions of the Noriosse Financial Group, Rossozzi's group would also provide resources to the Black Star Army and Floating Dragon Island in exchange for returns in other aspects.

Investing in military organizations had always been important to large financial groups; Rossozzi's was no exception. After finalizing the details, he left satisfied and content.

The official contract and terms would be sent over after the party ended. Han Xiao was rather glad. The Black Star Army had obtained one more investor, which was very helpful to the development of the faction.

"Black Star."

Someone else called out to him.

Han Xiao turned and looked. To his surprise, it was Austin. He brought along a group of Forbidden Sorcerers and came before Han Xiao.

"Your Excellency Magus, what is it?" Facing a Beyond Grade A, Han Xiao was formal.

Austin did not reply. He smiled and opened his palm. A dark blue light appeared in his hand. It turned into a vortex, and the light quickly disappeared. Then, a small gray orb appeared.

Han Xiao looked closely. This small orb was not solid but was made of flowing gray fog. It was compressed by a certain power and kept its shape of a small ball.

"This is..." Han Xiao was confused and did not understand Austin's intentions.

Austin played with the small gray fog ball and slowly said, "Once upon a time, my spiritual body travelled to a phantom secondary dimension and met a strangely strong Void Lord. It almost eroded my spiritual body but was defeated by me in the end. This is the core essence that the Void Lord left behind after dissipating. I want to give it to you."

Han Xiao was stunned.

A Void Lord's core essence was extremely rare. Almost only Mages could obtain such materials.

Entering a secondary dimension was an ability only high-level Mages possessed. They could often obtain all sorts of strange and weird items.

In terms of profiteering... ahem, production abilities, Mages and Mechanics stood at the peak among the five Super classes. In terms of collecting materials, Mages might be even better than Mechanics.

Mechanics were mostly in a bankrupt state all the time, completely the opposite of Mages. A class that could burn their mana bar to earn money with zero cost, via Enchanting, was basically everyone's common enemy.

Han Xiao deeply understood the meaning behind the phrase 'random acts of kindness only lead to either rape or robbery'. So, what is Austin's intention behind suddenly giving me a gift? Don't tell me he's trying to win me over like Heber, but took a more subtle and gentle route?

"Why give it to me?"

"Because I feel you might need it more than me." Austin winked.

Han Xiao was then reminded.

That's right, when I used Observer's Mark on Zoel yesterday, Austin noticed it.

Could this be the reason?

"You're not a Mage, but you can control Void Energy. It seems like you've been eroded by Void Genes before. Most species turn into monsters after that, but you controlled it and turned it into your ability. You're very lucky. Therefore, the Void Lord's core essence can enhance this ability and give you stronger power..." Austin proved Han Xiao's guess.

Austin had no idea that Han Xiao had the player interface. To him, the reason Han Xiao could use the Void Energy was because he had been eroded by Void Genes before. Plus, there were skeletons of Void Dragons buried within Floating Dragon Island, so he thought that he knew what had happened to Han Xiao. Hence, he wanted to help Ames' officer.

Anyway, it was nothing to him.

Han Xiao could only cough and agree with Austin's speculation with silence. Then, he started pondering.

His race was already a Void Race, and a Void Lord's core essence could enhance the strength of his Void Genes and increase his attributes. Furthermore, during his next Race Evolution, there would be a chance that he would be able to skip the next stage in the evolution chain and jump to the stage after that, giving him even stronger void race options.

It was indeed very useful. Plus, it was extremely rare and almost unobtainable on the market.

"What do I need to give in exchange?" Han Xiao squinted. He was definitely tempted, but he knew not to take gifts without asking its price.

Austin had a huge amount of resources, and a Void Lord's core essence was just a drop in the ocean, but Han Xiao did not think that Austin needed to give it to him.

Even if Austin was helping Ames' officer because of Ames, Han Xiao was not willing to accept a gesture of kindness from a Beyond Grade A stranger.

The relationship between him and Austin was far from him being able to accept gifts so easily.

"This is a gift. You don't have to... hmm..." Austin seemed to suddenly recall something. He then changed his words mid-sentence and said, "Maybe, one day in the future, I will need your help. Consider this a prepayment."

"Sounds good, as long as it doesn't go against my position and principles."

"Of course."

Han Xiao nodded and accepted the Void Lord's core. He gave it a close look.

_____________________

[Void Lord's Essence]: The core of an advanced Void being, contains high quality void energy, extremely precious. Many Mages are willing to pay a high price for it. You can also give it to certain special characters to trigger missions. You can even eat it, if you're not afraid of it giving you a stomachache... oh, I mean not afraid of being eroded by Void Genes.

_____________________

Han Xiao placed it into his pocket and bowed to Austin to express his gratitude.

Austin smiled with his adorable face before slowly saying, "Heber is reckless, and Ames is careless. I know your potential clearer than they do. One day, you might leave the Dragon Emperor and build your own name. It has been too long since a legend was born in this Star Field... I will be observing you. Don't disappoint me."

Before Han Xiao could reply, Austin took his Forbidden Sorcerers and left.

Han Xiao had a strange expression on his face.

Austin did not speak as if he was high and mighty; he was very friendly and gave Han Xiao a good impression, but those words made him feel like he was facing an elder...

...

The party went on. The people present all had their business to discuss. Occasionally, someone would approach Han Xiao to discuss some topics, but not often.

Other than Rossozzi and Austin, the others that went to chat with him mostly just had a casual conversation. Han Xiao was happy with not being busy. When he had no one to chat with, Han Xiao would enjoy the food and drinks in a corner with Ames and the sisters, chitchatting.

As time passed, the party gradually came to an end. The guests got most of the intelligence or partnerships they wanted. Han Xiao eavesdropped on some intelligence that was not really considered a secret but was unobtainable to regular people. After all, everyone there had high positions, so even the information they casually leaked was quite valuable.

In the private room upstairs, the Crimson Dynasty envoy, Zoel, had already privately met important people one after another.

Chapter 616: The Party Ends, Trip to Sunil.

"We will consider your offer."

The Star Cluster Civilization representative opposite Zoel stood up, bowed respectfully, and left the bright guest room. Zoel was the only one left in the room.

Zoel shook his head lightly, lifted the wine glass from the table, and took a sip. The heated emerald-colored wine poured like a string of fire down his throat.

He had seen more than ten people who represented the top organizations of the Shattered Star Ring. Everyone had been respectful to him due to his identity, but when they discussed the details, none had made a clear decision.

However, siding with the Crimson Dynasty was a huge decision that needed a long time to consider—Zoel understood that.

The Shattered Star Ring was the Federation of Light's territory, but Star Cluster Civilizations were not the Federation of Light's subordinates. There was no loyalty. All civilizations were independent. They only approved of the Federation of Light's authority—that was all. Every civilization had its own ambitions, every civilization wanted to expand, and the new Star Field was the opportunity.

"Currently, of the seven Star Cluster Civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring, only Klent is siding with us firmly. Judging from the current situation, there should be some more Star Cluster Civilizations that will side with us. Combined with some large organizations like Bloodshed Land, there should be sufficient chess pieces."

The Crimson Dynasty's ambition to expand was not limited to just this. Zoel was only in charge of the Shattered Star Ring; there were envoys in other Star Fields. They had included the entire Galaxy in their plan. The new area outside the Shattered Star Ring was just one of the things that the Crimson Dynasty wanted.

It would take years just to complete the initial part of the plan.

...

The party was coming to an end. The people were done with business and gathered in the hall. Heber appeared again, gave a closing speech, and announced the end of the party.

The party looked casual, but it was everything but casual. Many issues that could affect countless people were decided there, through a few words between some important people. This was part of the fundamentals of how the universe operated; one's power was closely related to their resources.

Han Xiao benefitted quite a lot as well. Not only did he get to know secret information about the Crimson Dynasty's plan and mentally prepare himself, he also made a lot of connections. He had finally made it to the top of the social circle.

Although he had achieved this mainly because of his position on Floating Dragon Island, this was a good start. He would not have gotten the chance to join this party with his own strength and power. The right to enter the circle was more important; his position would gradually become higher.

If 'connections' could be quantified, Han Xiao's connections had multiplied tens of times in this party. The people he had contact before were mostly Star System Civilizations and people in the mercenary industry. Now, he had the contacts of top organizations from all kinds of industries in the Shattered Star Ring. If he faced difficulties in the future, he would be able to receive more comprehensive and stronger support.

The nickname 'Black Star Networking Group' became even more suitable.

Furthermore, he had met other two Beyond Grade As of the Shattered Star Ring and surprisingly made a connection with Austin.

The guests bade farewell to Heber and left. Han Xiao and the rest walked out of the palace and immediately saw Carroll, who was waiting right outside with a long face.

"Black Star, here are the blueprints you wanted." Carroll threw Han Xiao a new communicator; the five blueprints were stored inside.

Han Xiao took a brief look and confirmed that the blueprints were right. He nodded and walked past him. He did not want to have any further communication with Carroll.

Ames looked forward and walked past Carroll as well.

Carroll was left alone, feeling awkward and completely ignored.

This time, a shadow occupied his vision.

Carroll looked up and saw Heber standing beside him, looking at him from above.

"Your Excellency Heber..." Carroll's face turned pale and stuttered, "Sorry, I lost this time."

"Will you lose next time?" Heber said coldly.

It was a simple question with zero blame. Carroll suddenly felt energized like he was encouraged. "Absolutely not!"

"That's my subordinate." Heber slowly nodded, turned around, and walked away.

...

Han Xiao and the rest did not want to stay on Planet Heber. They headed directly to the dock, boarded the Blacklight Stealth, and left Bloodshed Land, heading back.

While Ames trained the sisters, Han Xiao told Risda to control the spaceship and went to the training room, checking the five new blueprints.

One of them was the heavy fortress that Carroll had used during the spar. Its official name was 'Flying Fortress'. Its defense was extraordinary and could be used as a flying carrier.

There was also the Giant Soldier, which could replace spaceships as a weapon in space. Its mobility, armor value, destructive power, melee and ranged combat capabilities, and other attributes were all beyond average. It was quite the well-rounded equipment, as well as Han Xiao's first Giant Soldier blueprint.

Heavy Armor Mechanics built heavy machines; these machines' basic attributes were usually higher. These two things could be used as Grade A standard combat equipment directly.

The other three were also important blueprints to Carroll. One was medium-sized armor that was about six to seven meters tall, operated by more than one person. Its performance was excellent and was best for offensive combat. It was suitable to be sold to guilds.

Another was a type of anti-gravity electromagnetic hovering motorbike carrier that was equipped with a shield to block the universe's radiation and allowed interstellar travel. Han Xiao had the Berserk Ape mechanical suit, so he did not need it. However, the great thing about these kinds of motorbikes was that they looked extremely cool. It could be the next tier replacement for the Nuclear Flying Backpack. Of course, Han Xiao had to improve the blueprint and add a self-destruct function.

The last one was high-caliber, ship-mounted artillery, a type of spaceship attachment blueprint. Ship-mounted weapons were mostly heavy firearms, which were, of course, much more powerful than portable weapons.

The prerequisite knowledges for those five blueprints were mostly from the Armed Branch, and the highest level knowledge was only High-End Knowledge.

After checking through the loot, Han Xiao took out the Void Lord's core essence and looked at it carefully.

This tiny ball filled with gray fog had a very special texture when he held it. It was as if it did not exist and he could just shatter it easily. But when he actually tried to, he would feel a very strong repelling force.

Void Lord's core can enhance Void Genes, like the Void Dragon Pith but stronger. Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

In the power pyramid of Void species, the Void Lord was at the top. Most of them existed in the secondary dimension as seen by Mages or hid in Void Vision and rarely interfered with reality. A Void Lord could be considered a high dimensional life form. A similar being would be Magic Beings. Void Lords gathered Void Energy to build their body and project it onto reality. They had thousands of forms. Even in Galaxy, where there were so many races, they were still considered rare beings.

This was not the first time he used this kind of item. Consuming the Void Lord's core was very beneficial to him. Usually, there would be risks of consuming genetic items, but the adaptability between the same species was very high. The chance of a side effect occurring was minimal.

Han Xiao opened his mouth and swallowed the tiny gray ball of fog. A freezing feeling exploded from his mouth and instantly expanded to his entire body as if even his soul was frozen.

Han Xiao could sense his own body at a microscopic level, and he could see his cells gradually growing stronger under these waves of highly-concentrated Void Energy. His genes changed once again.

_____________________

You have used a Void Lord's Essence.

Fusion Progress: 38%... 61%... 100%

Fusion Complete!

Compatibility: Perfect

Permanent Attribute Increase: +8 STR, +12 DEX, +10 END, +10 INT, +15 MYS, +8 CHA

Your Talent [Intermediate Strengthened Life] became slightly stronger.

_____________________

The freezing cold quickly went away. Han Xiao took a deep breath and looked at the interface notification.

The attribute increase was quite impressive, a total increase of sixty-three points. More surprisingly, there was a clear notification related to [Intermediate Strengthened Life]

This talent had been with him for a long time and provided him with a lot of health. The last time this talent leveled up, he had already speculated that he would have to use more gene items with no side effects to continue making the talent stronger. The Void Lord's Essence had proved him right.

Although the effect of [Intermediate Strengthened Life] was unchanged and did not level up, since there was a notification, it meant that this was the right path to take. Han Xiao decided to make collecting rare Void species' materials a new mission.

...

Han Xiao first took Ames and the sisters back to Floating Dragon Island. It was a peaceful trip.

Arriving on Floating Dragon Island, the Blacklight Stealth parked at the dock. Ames and the sisters got out and turned to look at Han Xiao, who was beside the hatch.

Han Xiao looked at Hila and Aurora and smiled. "You guys, train with the Dragon Emperor properly and quickly become stronger. I'm still waiting for you to help me."

Aurora raised her tiny hand up and said very seriously, "I will definitely work hard."

Hila opened her mouth but did not know what to say.

She suddenly realized that the two of them had to part again. She and her sister would be training on the unfamiliar Floating Dragon Island and start a new chapter in their lives.

It could be a very long time before she saw Han Xiao again. Hila could not help but think of the times back on Planet Aquamarine when she used to look up at the starry night. She felt her emotions become a mess.

Hila knew that she did not know Han Xiao very well. They had spent little time together, less than the time they had spent apart...

She hesitated then softly said, "Be careful."

"Got it, bye."

Han Xiao waved, and the hatch closed.

The next moment, the spaceship took off and disappeared.

Ames turned toward the sisters and said, "From now on, you will be starting your official training. I'll be very strict."

"I'm looking forward to it." Hila inhaled deeply, her expression dignified.

...

Away from Floating Dragon Island, the Blacklight Stealth entered hyperdrive and headed toward Planet Sunil.

Attending the Tyrant's party in the Seoul Star Cluster had taken quite a lot of time including travel. During this time, the Black Star Army had been maintaining its business. The players had yet to cause any big problems, so everything was operating as usual.

Not long ago, Herlous had sent a message. After 200,000 players worked for months, the Sunils finally made a huge breakthrough. They got rid of a large amount of Prophecy Stone mines, and the strength of the Psychic Current visibly weakened.

At this pace, the threat of the Catastrophe would very soon be completely eliminated, saving the Sunils.

However, as they dug deeper into the mines underground, they noticed some strange phenomena, so Herlous requested backup from him personally.

The information Han Xiao gained during Tyrant's party gave him quite a lot of pressure. He wanted to speed up the Black Star Army's development, so he decided to visit Planet Sunil himself and completely solve the Sunil's problems. At the same time, he would scout the area and prepare to build the third sub-base.

Furthermore, while doing that, he could reap the experience of 200,000 players, collect three billion experience, and level up to level 145, meeting the Class Advancement requirement.

Chapter 617: Planet Sunil's Natives!

The pure white clouds flew in the sapphire sky of Planet Sunil like pieces of silk. The gentle wind brought along a thin veil of fog and blew across the dense sea of trees, shaking them like a wave.

Green was an amazing color. Looking down on the surface, Han Xiao felt soothed.

The Blacklight Stealth slowly landed in the military area outside Forest City. Herlous was already waiting there with the Sunil superiors. Further away were many patrolling armored Sunil soldiers.

As soon as Han Xiao walked down the gangway, Herlous rushed toward him and gave him a passionate hug.

"Black Star, you're finally here!"

Han Xiao patted Herlous' shoulder, signaling him to let go. Herlous excitedly introduced the Sunil superiors to Han Xiao one after another.

They shook hands and greeted each other. The Sunil superiors were very humble. Black Star's position in the galaxy was far above that of the entire Sunil race. Plus, Black Star had helped them solve the issues of their planet. They would never forget this.

After the introduction, they started talking business. Han Xiao asked, "What's the situation now?"

"Amazing!" Herlous was exhilarated. He knew the most about the effect of the Black Star Army over the past few months; the situation of the Sunils had tremendously improved.

As he spoke, Herlous took out his communicator, opened the map projection of Planet Sunil, and explained in detail.

The threat on Planet Sunil came from the beasts. The cause of the Catastrophe was the Prophecy Stone mines hidden underground in various places. The sheer quantity caused a reaction and formed Psychic Currents, making the beasts go haywire.

Therefore, Sunil's first target was to clear out the Prophecy Stone mines of this planet.

However, due to the wild being dangerous, the exploration difficulty was exceedingly high. The Sunils only controlled a very small area and could not bear the cost of expanding their territory—many young warriors would be sacrificed if they did.

Thus, the Black Star Army just so happened to make up for this. With the help of spaceships and carriers, 200,000 players fearless of death discovered close to a thousand Prophecy Stone mines within a few months.

The shorter the distance from the mine, the stronger the Psychic Current. There was almost no beast living nearby, so the players could easily destroy all the Prophecy Stones in those mines.

According to the calculations of the Sunil Research Department, the overall strength of the Psychic Current on the planet had decreased considerably. The interval between Catastrophes was likely extended to more than ten years, which was two to three times greater than before. This meant that the Sunils' situation was not as urgent anymore. They had more time to rest and prepare. The result was exceptional.

This result was announced to the entire race, giving them previously unseen energy and hope.

The situation of their race was tremendously improved. All the Sunil warriors were excited.

Among them, Herlous was the most excited. His race was his home. The Black Star Army was the savior of Planet Sunil, and he was the one that connected the two sides. On one hand, he was excited due to his decision back then; on the other hand, he sincerely appreciated Black Star's help.

Of course, this result was not good enough. Since they wanted to solve the problem, the Sunils hoped to be more thorough.

"What are the difficulties faced in clearing out these mines?" Han Xiao asked.

As soon as he said this, the faces of those present became grave. Herlous said in a deep voice, "We had speculated about all sorts of situations and obstacles we might face, but we never expected it to be this serious."

Han Xiao was suddenly curious. From the way Herlous put it, it seems like even 200,000 players cannot get rid of this problem.

"By the way, where are the mercenaries? Why don't I see them?" Han Xiao looked around and realized that there was not even one mercenary.

"Mostly still exploring and fighting outside in the wild. We built many camps to make sure that the mercenaries could resupply in the wild and not have to keep returning to Forest City. Only a small portion of the mercenaries currently reside in Forest City," Herlous explained.

I see. That's completely normal... Han Xiao nodded. It seemed like he needed a reason to recall all the players in the wild so that it would be more convenient for him to reap experience.

Putting this thought aside for the moment, Han Xiao rubbed his chin and asked with confusion, "So, what difficulty did you guys meet?"

"Well, the shallow mines were easy to clear out, but there are also tons of mines deeper underground, maybe many times deeper than the shallow mines. These are more difficult to clear and need bigger tools and more manpower, but this isn't the main issue..." Herlous sighed and projected an image. On it were many strange-shaped beasts, but they all had the characteristics of insects.

"This is..." Han Xiao frowned.

"As we dug deeper, we reached a completely different layer of rocks. We shockingly discovered the tracks of some unidentified beasts. After the initial investigation, we realized that they are ancient underground beasts that never came to the surface. They are an enormous race living under Planet Sunil's surface. From just the few nests we've discovered, there's already more than a hundred million of these beasts. We have no idea how many more are in the underground world we have yet to explore..."

With a grave tone, Herlous said, "Maybe they are the real owners of this planet."

Han Xiao now understood.

Sunil's original mother planet had been destroyed, and they had only migrated to this Planet Sunil after that. Thus, they could be considered guests taking over the owner's home.

As there were limited resources, Sunils did not explore underground, up till today. Only now did they realize that a large race existed under the planet's surface. Those monsters were the natives of this planet.

If not for the Black Star Army, Sunil would still not have noticed such a huge threat lurking within the very planet that they lived on.

"For some reason, these monsters built their nests around the Prophecy Stone mines and indirectly protect the mines. They reject outside beings very strongly. Their body is very hard, they're very swift, and they are able to secrete corrosive slime on their skin. They are about the same size as wild wolves. Dozens of underground exploration teams have been wiped out. The underground is their stage. It's very difficult for us to fight when we can't maximize our strength underground.

"Protect the Prophecy Stone mines?" Han Xiao pondered. Most underground creatures liked to be close to radioactive minerals—some even consumed them as food. However, the Prophecy Stone mines were not radioactive but stimulated beasts into a crazed state. Logically speaking, beasts would get as far away from the Prophecy Stone mines as they could, but these underground beasts had built their nests surrounding Prophecy Stones.

A word popped up in Han Xiao's mind.

Mutation!

"Their race might be traced back to thousands of years ago. Lives change to adapt to the environment. Over a very long time, their genes mutated," Han Xiao said. "Think about it, the Catastrophe causes all the beasts on this planet to go crazy, but you people have never met these monsters before. This means that they have never gone crazy and come to the surface, which shows that they're used to the Psychic Currents and are immune to them. They have developed an extremely strong psychic resistance."

The Sunils were guests that only migrated to this planet recently, while Prophecy Stones had existed for countless years. They had no idea about the Prophecy Stones' effects on the native beasts throughout those countless years.

Herlous nodded. "That's right. We call these underground monsters Subterranean Mutants."

"Therefore, you guys summoned me to..." Han Xiao had a guess.

"Your Excellency Black Star, we hope to get your help," a Sunil superior said seriously with the utmost respect. "We want to eliminate all Subterranean Mutants and completely control Planet Sunil. Our problems can only be resolved if we kill these underground monsters. Plus, there are countless resources underground. We can only collect them after the Subterranean Mutants are dealt with."

In order to completely get rid of the Catastrophe, destroying all the underground mines was the only way. Hence, the Subterranean Mutants were the biggest obstacle. Furthermore, mining for underground resources would be unavoidable in the future. Subterranean Mutants were clearly a barrier for their development. In terms of population alone, the number of Subterranean Mutants was probably hundreds or even a thousand times that of the Sunils. The Sunils had absolutely no intention of coexisting with a species this large in numbers.

I thought so... Thinking of the beautiful nature that he had seen earlier when looking down from above, Han Xiao sighed. He looked at Herlous and said, "What do you think?"

"I agree." Herlous was firm.

"Ok..." Han Xiao slowly said. "I hope you guys can understand that the nature of this incident has changed. This is a war hire; I will gather more spaceships and mercenaries."

"Marvelous!" The Sunils were overjoyed.

"To ensure the transport of people and resources, I need to build a sub-base on Sunil immediately. Do you guys have any objections?"

"No." The people shook their heads.

Coming to an agreement, Han Xiao walked aside and contacted Phillip.

"Help me to contact the Noriosse and Rossozzi financial groups. I will be building the third sub-base here in the Garton Star System, Planet Sunil. List the resources needed and send them to these two financial groups; we'll use their channels.

"Gather the 200,000 mercenaries on Planet Sunil in Forest City. They are needed to build the base.

"Also, send out an Army Assembly on Planet Sunil, targeting all Black Star mercenaries!"

After accepting a string of orders, Phillip replied, "Orders confirmed, hum..."

Han Xiao did not stop there. Through the faction interface, he directly announced a new mission to all the players.

[Army Expansion—Base No. 3]!

...

Sunil soldiers patrolled outside a certain wild camp. In the camp, some players set up stores and formed teams.

There was quite a number of players in every camp. There were mission points and exploration points around the camps, and the players resupplied in the camps. Hence, they naturally became the players' frequent spots.

Maple Moon sat in a corner with a 'Repair' mark on her head. She had set up a repairing store for equipment, and business was booming.

Back then, she had decided to follow the majority and went to Planet Sunil.

As a casual player, she did not like fighting and killing. She had always felt the Mechanic class was most suitable for her. In Version 1.0, she had followed Black Star for a very long time and benefitted a ton, so she was ahead of the other players. Her ability to repair and build was clearly far above many players of the same class. She was considered one of the top players.

Although she did not receive Black Star's special treatment in Version 2.0, due to her already being ahead, her business had always been popular. Other players were more willing to go to her for repairs and purchases. With the large amounts of profits that she made from that, she had more resources to increase her strength, which formed a cycle.

However, Maple Moon rarely battled. Compared to fighting, she enjoyed the storyline more. The Sunil mission was right up her alley. Saving this race in danger and getting gratitude from the Sunils made her very happy.

There were quite many players who liked the storyline, similar to Maple Moon. To some players, profit was not the priority; what they wanted was a good story. The business plan that Han Xiao had set for the Black Star Army was to let the players experience various storylines through the hiring missions. The Sunil storyline was one of them. This way, their stories would become the army's history.

At this time, Maple Moon realized that the players on the street had all stopped and opened their interface at the same time. This told her that something huge had happened, so she hastily checked the interface.

The mission to build the third base appeared in her eyes.

"Hmm? Black Star came to Sunil? Strange, the mission to save Sunil is not completed yet, and Base No. 3 can already be built?"

"Who cares? It's a good thing that a new base can be built."

The players chitchatted and left in groups, heading toward Forest City. The camp suddenly became empty.

Most players had already immersed themselves in the Black Star Army. They felt that their performance on Planet Sunil had made their faction grow again. They felt a sense of achievement.

Every time the faction developed, the players would feel fulfilled. Han Xiao's method of building a sense of belonging was really working well.

Maple Moon packed up her store and headed to Forest City, too. Other than missions, she had another goal—to learn better blueprints from Black Star. She had stocked up quite a lot of experience over the past few months. She was not the only one; all the Mechanics on Planet Sunil were hoping to do the same.

Chapter 618: Class Advancement!

The chosen location for Base No. 3 was not far from Forest City. All 200,000 of the players that were outside returned immediately after receiving the mission. With the help of spaceships, they gathered in no time.

Outside Forest City, 200,000 players gathered and focused their eyes on Han Xiao. Han Xiao borrowed the Dragon Emperor's style once again, sitting on a mechanical throne that hovered in midair. He was not really trying to look cool. There were so many players, so they would not be able to see him if he was not flying.

It had been a while since Han Xiao had last been in close contact with players. He briefly observed the players. The equipment of the 200,000 players that had stayed on Planet Sunil for a few months had visibly changed. They could roughly be grouped into three types of people. The first type was those that wore heavy armor, mostly Sunil Enlistee Class armor and some Worker Bee Armors. What was worth mentioning was that the Sunil Armors these players wore all came from his army. The Sunils clearly knew that Han Xiao had secretly learned about their blueprints... but it did not matter even if they knew.

The second type of players were those that did not wear armor; these players made up about one-tenth of all the players. The Great Mechanic Han could not figure out whether they were poor... or poor. Be it Pugilists or Espers, buying a set of armor had pros and no cons. Even Bloodshed Land's Vanguard Officials wore specially made armor.

Although these players did not wear armor, they still had some mechanical equipment on them, such as firearms, melee weapons, shield generators, and other sorts.

The third type of player did not use armor, too. What they wore was the Nuclear Flying Backpack. It was clear they were all 'artists'.

In conclusion, all the players were using the Black Star Army's products. Their equipment had been updated from head to toe, and they all looked refreshed. Finally, these players looked somewhat like galactic warriors. However, in Han Xiao's eyes, they looked more like yards of green leeks.

Planet Sunil was the resource ground of NPCs. He had left 200,000 players to grow here for months, and they had stocked up a large amount of resources. Every single leek was looking fresh and nutritional.

Seeing that everyone was staring at him, Han Xiao coughed, put on a serious expression, and said in a low voice, "Due to your hard work, Sunil's troubles have been alleviated. However, a new obstacle has appeared in this mission, and we need more help. Hence, the original plan is being brought forward, and we will be building Base No. 3 on this planet as a stronghold.

"Phillip has sent the exact location to your communicators. Building a new base requires everyone's help..."

Han Xiao explained the situation briefly. The players had no problems with it. They followed him to the chosen location for the base and started to clear out the trees and flattening the terrain.

[Army Expansion—Base No. 3] was a faction mission; it included many construction jobs that needed the players to complete. Every sub-mission rewarded experience and Contribution Points. The players were very motivated, not only because of the reward but also because they were personally taking part in the construction of the base, contributing to the growth of the faction.

The addition of Base No. 3 was beneficial to them. A new base meant that the army would store much more resources there. By that time, the players would no longer have to pre-order faction products and could collect them directly at Base No. 3. Furthermore, as hire missions could only be accepted in the base, the players now had one more place where they could accept hires and rest, other than the Planet Aquamarine and Planet Golden Gate bases. This was the Black Star Army's new stronghold in the vast universe.

Han Xiao notified the galactical construction team that had been working with him from the beginning; they would arrive at Planet Sunil very soon. However, the construction teams could only build the buildings. The facilities still had to be completed by his own people. With 200,000 players, the construction speed of Base No. 3 would be tremendously increased.

The Noriosse and Rossozzi financial groups provided some help, too, and sent a large amount of supplies through their channels.

Han Xiao made a rough calculation. These two investors saved him about 600,000 Enas. This time, he planned to put in 2,700,000 Enas to build Base No. 3. His account had close to 50 million Enas saved up, so he could easily afford this expense.

One and a half years ago, he had only had the three to four million Enas that he had borrowed, and it had taken him more than half a year to build Base No.1. Less than two years later, his assets had multiplied more than ten times. It was a very remarkable increase.

The players were very efficient. Not long after, a huge, flat area appeared in the forest. As the construction materials that he had bought had yet to arrive, the players could not start working for the moment.

The tens of battleships that were on standby around Planet Sunil were all moved there, forming a temporary camp. Players were gathered there, as did Han Xiao.

Making use of this great opportunity, the players all approached Han Xiao, wanting to learn abilities. Most of them were Mechanics. After not seeing Han Xiao the Mechanic Mentor for a few months, they had all been looking forward to this moment.

This was exactly what Han Xiao had expected. He had planned long ago not to sell knowledge but blueprints this time.

He had a talent from his Scholar subclass—[Research Theory].

The effect of that talent was one bonus Intelligence point for every three abilities, which now gave Han Xiao about three hundred Intelligence points. This meant that Han Xiao now had close to a thousand blueprint abilities, which had cost him countless experience. This was an unimaginable number for the players.

Selling some low-level blueprints had a very limited effect on him. Han Xiao put up tens of low-level machinery blueprints at the same time.

The players were mostly above level 70. At this level, low-level blueprints were no longer rare; the players could fuse these themselves. However, due to the variety of knowledge combinations, hardly any Mechanic players could fuse the blueprints they wanted. Hence, the blueprints that they had were all very different.

He, however, sold blueprints directly, helping the players to escape the bottomless hole of gambling on blueprints.

Seeing so many blueprints, the Mechanic players' eyes were all sparking.

After working on Planet Sunil for a few months, those players were not short of experience. Although the blueprints that Han Xiao was selling did not involve very high-level technology, they covered all kinds of things. There were firearms, explosives, mechanical soldiers, shields, mechanical suits, energy sources, carriers, and many others. Gambling blueprints relied on luck. Therefore, every player could find useful blueprints for themselves and make up for their weak spots.

Han Xiao was not worried about Mechanic class players affecting the sales of the Black Star Army after learning those blueprints. From a cost perspective, the players definitely could not compete with production lines and had no chance of selling things at the same low price. Furthermore, spending in the faction store rewarded players with Contribution Points. Besides, Han Xiao did not sell blueprints of the faction products; what he sold were the blueprints of the same type of machines but half a standard lower.

Han Xiao's development plan also included partnering with material industries and selling players raw materials to make more money, expanding the Black Star Army's business range while at the same time bringing convenience to the players so that they could buy the materials that they needed in the faction store without having to collect them themselves.

Of the 200,000 players, there were about 50,000 to 60,000 Mechanic class players. They bought blueprints joyfully, and most of them bought more than one.

Han Xiao's experience quickly increased, shooting past the one billion mark, and continued to grow.

The players shockingly noticed that other than the low-level blueprints, there was also an extremely tempting high-level blueprint!

The Void Dragon Mechanical Suit!

"Thi—This is a god-tier blueprint!"

"Holy, now this is something!"

The Mechanic players were extremely tempted. Looking at the price—600,000 experience and 2,000 Enas—many felt a heartache. However, the impressive stats on the Void Dragon mechanical suit were like an erotic dancer in revealing clothing that kept telling the players, "Come and play."

In the eyes of the players, Void Dragon's stats were undoubtedly in the 'god tier' range. Some players that could afford it hesitated before clenching their teeth and buying it.

Seeing this, Han Xiao faintly smiled. Although this blueprint was high level, he had Berserk Ape now and had no use for Void Dragon anymore, so he sold it to the players.

The difficulty of making the Void Dragon mechanical suit was very high. The players would only be able to build it after level 90. Plus, its core material were Void Dragon bones; this was the most important factor to Han Xiao. Even if some players really built it, it would be impossible to replicate.

What, you want to build in bulk? Sure, go to Ames and ask to have her Floating Dragon. You should be able to experience what it's like to die from pressure.

Within one to two versions, the chance of a player being able to build it was very slim. They could at most look at it and feel good after they bought it. What if they wanted to build it? Not going to happen!

From the players' perspective, the mechanical suit blueprint that suited their current situation the most was actually Amphiptere, which Han Xiao had gotten rid of long ago.

With the Mechanic players' current ability, they would be able to build Amphiptere and keep its cost within an acceptable range. If he sold the Amphiptere blueprint, this Single Unit Mechanical Suit would quickly become popular among the players. The average combat capability of the players would be hugely increased... which was exactly why Han Xiao was not going to sell Amphiptere.

If the players got what was most suitable for them, how was he going to use the Sunil series armor to harvest those leeks time after time?

Thus, the Great Mechanic Han decided to sell the Void Dragon blueprint, giving the players a dream to chase. A man without a dream was no different from a fish, and this 'dream' just so happened to be able to earn him more profits.

Nonetheless, he did not scam the players too much. At the very least, the price of the Void Dragon blueprint was much lower than its value. Mechanical suit blueprints of this level could be sold for at least 100,000 Enas in the galaxy.

After this harvest, Han Xiao's experience rocketed once again, easily surpassing three billion. Han Xiao could not help but smile in satisfaction.

Maple Moon learned the Void Dragon blueprint, too. She quickly browsed through the materials and murmured, "Void Dragon Bone... Hmm, looks familiar... Isn't this Floating Dragon's specialty‽"

As a player who had followed Han Xiao since Version 1.0, Maple Moon had visited Floating Dragon Island personally. She was the only Mechanic player present who had any idea what Void Dragon Bone was.

After about half a day, night came, and only then did the Mechanic players dissipate and return contentedly.

Han Xiao's experience stash had reached 9.4 billion!

The average price of low-level blueprints was about 40,000, and there were about 50,000 to 60,000 Mechanic players, each buying more than one blueprint on average. There were also a few thousand players that bought the Void Dragon blueprint. All in all, he had earned about 9.4 billion experience.

This is plenty. Han Xiao was rather satisfied. Exchanging some blueprints that he had no use for anymore for so much experience was worth it.

Since he had enough experience, Han Xiao did not delay. He returned to the training room on the spaceship, opened his interface, threw in three billion experience, and leveled up three times consecutively.

[Virtual Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.20 (max).

+350 Energy, +3 DEX, +3 END, +6 INT.

You have received 6 Free Attribute Points.

You have received 1 Potential Point.

Main Class level limit achieved. Complete Class Advancement requirements to continue leveling up.

Class Advancement requirements: INT > 1,300, Machinery Affinity > 580%. (Active ability bonus not included)

I got attribute requirements? Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Increasing attributes for regular players was quite complicated; it would usually be difficult for them to achieve the Class Advancement attribute requirements, and they would often have to learn subclasses.

However, to Han Xiao, this kind of Class Advancement was the easiest. The Class Advancement requirements were related to the nature of the class itself most of the time, such as the core attributes, Intelligence and Machinery Affinity. For these things, Han Xiao had always been well above the regular standard for his level.

For his Intelligence, his basic value reached 1,536 after spending all the Free Attribute Points that he had just earned on it, which was already above the Class Advancement requirements. Adding on the ten percent bonus as a Calamity Grade Super, as well as the more than three hundred Intelligence given by [Research Theory], his Intelligence was close to two thousand!

As for basic Machinery Affinity, including his talents and passive abilities, it was 686%, also exceeding the Class Advancement requirements.

This meant that Han Xiao had no need to learn any new subclasses. His attributes had already met the Class Advancement standard.

Huh, I've become lucky recently. Han Xiao rubbed his hands with excitement. Could it be that the effect of touching Feidin is permanent‽

Since he met the requirements, without hesitation, Han Xiao put the experience in and leveled his main class up once more, completing his Class Advancement.

With the regular sharp pain in his head, he suddenly gained insight into many new things.

Class Advancement requirements completed!

You have received a new class [Galaxy Mechanic Lv.1].

+180 Energy, +1 STR, +3 DEX, +3 END, +8 INT.

You have received 6 Free Attribute Points.

You have received 1 Potential Point.

You have acquired ability [Master Machinery Affinity]!

You have acquired ability [Rapid Virtual Intrusion]!

You have acquired ability [Quantum Network Matrix]!

You have obtained talent [Machinery Theory Summary!

Your talent [Virtual Technology Essence] is enhanced!

Your ability [Strengthened Smart Defense] is enhanced!

Your ability [Strengthened Hacking] is enhanced!

Chapter 619: Sunil's Grade A Main Storyline

As a [Galaxy Mechanic], Han Xiao had stepped into the advanced stage of a Mechanic. At this stage, he could already be considered a master. This stage increased the level limit of his main class by five, the maximum being Lv.25. As Han Xiao recalled, most of the Mechanic players in his previous life entered Grade A when they became Galaxy Mechanics.

The new class [Galaxy Mechanic] meant that he could build stronger machines that could now be used in galactic wars, machines that were more advanced and precise.

For example, Carroll was a Galaxy Mechanic, and the Giant Soldier, Ship Destroyer, was a blueprint that he invented at the Galaxy Mechanic stage.

From the players' perspective, the best improvement that this Class Advancement brought was related to fusing blueprints. The class [Galaxy Mechanic] was a prerequisite for more advanced blueprints. The same combinations as before could now unlock more blueprints.

In terms of abilities, [Galaxy Mechanic] strengthened the branch selected during the previous stage, which was Han Xiao's Virtual Technology. The related abilities and talents were enhanced, and he also obtained two new Virtual Technology abilities.

[Rapid Virtual Intrusion], as the name suggested, sped up the speed of Virtual Intrusion. In exchange, the duration of the authority obtained through Virtual Intrusion would become shorter.

[Quantum Network Matrix] was a core ability. It had two effects. One was a huge increase in the range of intrusion.

Range was a very important attribute of Virtual Technology. Clearly, there was an enormous difference between hacking something right in front of it and hacking something an entire Star System away. The quantum network existed everywhere, and the level of Virtual Technology determined the degree to which a Mechanic could make use of the quantum network. Han Xiao's range increased tremendously, but of course, it was still far from being able to use Virtual Intrusion across Star Systems.

Only Beyond Grade A Mechanics like [Mechanic Empire] Manison could do it across such terrifying distances, hacking from Star Systems or even Star Clusters away.

The second effect of this ability was the Virtual Intrusion version of 'splashing'.

For example, if the targets of the intrusion were two independent artificial intelligences but the two of them were exchanging data, if one artificial intelligence was hacked, through its data exchange with the other artificial intelligence, the other artificial intelligence would also be indirectly hacked. It was similar to computers spreading viruses, like an AOE Virtual Intrusion. However, the judging difficulty of indirect intrusion would be higher.

As for [Master Machinery Affinity], it was a very practical ability. It provided +75% Machinery Affinity at the max level.

[Machinery Theory Summary] was a talent. It was considered one of the core abilities of the Mechanic class just like [Machinery Analytical Comprehension]. It increased Machinery Affinity based on Intelligence at a rate of thirty Intelligence to 2.2% Machinery Affinity.

As the main class continued to level up, the core attribute of the class would have a bigger impact on his strength, which was why Han Xiao put all his points into Intelligence.

Level 146...

Han Xiao thought about it and did not continue levelling up. He maxed the levels of the new abilities and kept the remaining billions of experience.

Class Advancement was a new stage, which was why it made him much stronger, but the benefits of continuing to level up were not very high. Leveling up to 160 required an enormous amount of experience, and what he had was far from enough. It was better to keep it and use it to level up abilities, getting some Potential Points. What he was shortest of was Potential Points—they were in single digits.

Energized and refreshed, energy flowed in Han Xiao's body like a stream. Han Xiao could feel his body's changes clearly. His senses were clearer. He gently touched a compressed orb, and his brain subconsciously presented its structure. His understanding of machines was now deeper.

After enjoying this feeling for a while, Han Xiao left the training room satisfied. Only now did he see the message that Herlous had sent him, inviting him to attend the meeting before the battle, to discuss how to deal with the Subterranean Mutants together.

Han Xiao could not help but shake his head.

Sunils had hired the Black Star Army to get rid of the Subterranean Mutants, so they had most likely formulated a rough plan long ago. Instead of calling it a discussion, it was more like the Sunils introducing their plan.

Han Xiao went to the military conference room, and he could hear the heated argument even through the door. Han Xiao opened the door and walked in. Everyone looked at him, and the discussion suddenly stopped. The Sunil superiors all stood up to welcome him. Herlous and Sehrinde were there, too.

Han Xiao placed his fist in front of his mouth and coughed. "How's the discussion going?"

"Your Excellency Black Star, we are waiting for you to make the decision," a bold Sunil superior said respectfully. Han Xiao recalled that this superior was called Otis, the right-hand man of the Sunil leader. His position was very high.

"I'm just the executor, only responsible for carrying out the plan. The overall strategy is up to you, not decided by me." Han Xiao waved his hand. As a mercenary, he did not like to cross boundaries.

"Oh... okay. Then I shall talk about the strategic goal—eliminate Subterranean Mutants or shrink their number down to a safe standard, at least allowing us to safely destroy the Prophecy Stone mines underground. We now have three possible ways to deal with them..."

Otis turned on the projection and explained the plans in detail.

"The first plan is to send soldiers underground and destroy Subterranean Mutant's nests one after another. This plan will need a lot of manpower, and the casualty number is difficult to estimate. The underground world is their stage; we can't fully make use of our strength. We will also meet all sorts of difficulties like getting lost, being caved in, and so on. This is considered the last resort.

"Second, lure the Mutants up the surface in groups, then use war weapons such as spaceships and missiles to bombard them. This would be much more efficient, killing tens of millions at once. The problem is how we are going to lure them out. Also, it's best not to use nuclear weapons. We don't want to cause too much pollution.

"The last plan is to capture some Subterranean Mutants alive. Study their body structure, invent specially made bioweapons, and drop them underground. Eliminating them en masse without combat. However, the difficulty, cost, and time of inventing such a thing are all unknown. The level of uncertainty is too high."

This time, Han Xiao's interface suddenly popped up.

You have triggered Grade A Faction Mission [Eliminate Subterranean Mutants]!

Mission Introduction: An ancient species lives under Planet Sunil's surface. They're the natives of this planet, but they have become enemies that obstructed the Sunils' development. You accepted Sunil's request to completely resolve this hidden threat.

Reminder: This is a Faction Series Mission. You can complete the requirements stated below during this mission.

Research Sample I: Capture 1 Subterranean Mutant alive. Reward: 20,000 experience

Research Sample II: Capture 10 Subterranean Mutants alive. Reward: 200,000 experience

Research Sample III: Capture 50 Subterranean Mutants alive. Reward: 1,000,000 experience

Slaughterer I: Kill 10 Subterranean Mutants. Reward: 50,000 experience

Slaughterer V: Kill 1,000 Subterranean Mutants. Reward: 5,000,000 experience

Mine Destroyer (Repeatable): Destroy a Prophecy Stone mine. Reward: 200,000 experience

8 targets remaining... [Expand/Collapse]

When the mission ends, based on the number of targets completed, a rating and bonus reward will be given.

A new Grade A mission?

This appeared to be Planet Sunil's main storyline. When the plan officially started, the players would be able to trigger it as well.

Different planets all had their own main storyline missions, which was why Han Xiao always took NPC resources very seriously, using them to make up for the Black Star Army's 'storyline'. Not only were there missions, but there were also main storyline missions. Double the rewards, double the happiness.

The people stared at Han Xiao, and Herlous asked, "Black Star, which plan do we use?"

Han Xiao knocked on the table, pondered, and said, "All of them."

With joy written all over his face, Otis nodded rapidly and said, "That's the best. We Sunils will deploy soldiers as well to fight together with the Black Star Army."

After discussing the details of the plan, they agreed to first capture some Subterranean Mutants and study their bodies.

It was a task better done sooner, so Han Xiao did not waste any time. After the meeting ended, he took Herlous and Sehrinde in a spaceship, heading toward one of the Subterranean Mutant nests' entrances.

The three of them were strong enough to not worry about any danger, so it was most efficient for them to do the job. This was also why Han Xiao did not bring along any players. If not because the task of capturing them alive was more troublesome, he would rather have worked alone.

The spaceship arrived there very quickly. This place was in the middle of being dug up, so many drilling machines were scattered around the place. There was a huge hole in the ground, dark and extending to the underground.

This had initially been a cave for the Prophecy Stone mine underground, but it had become the first place to discover Subterranean Mutants. There were a lot of armored Sunil soldiers stationed there. Since they had very limited knowledge of the Subterranean Mutants, this was to prevent them from coming up to the surface.

The spaceship landed, and Han Xiao notified the camp commander. The commander welcomed the three of them, and the patrolling soldiers looked at them with respect.

It was late at night, and the sky was dark. The illuminating devices around the camp were the only sources of light. The three of them stood at the edge of the cave and looked down. Even the strong light could not reach the bottom.

Han Xiao was about to go down. This time, Herlous suddenly said, "Black Star, do you think this is... unethical?"

"Oh?" Han Xiao paused and turned to Herlous. "You mean eliminating the Subterranean Mutants?"

"Yes." Herlous' tone was anxious.

The appearance of Subterranean Mutants changed the nature of the issue. No one had expected to discover Planet Sunil's natives. The Sunils was outsiders. If they wanted to resolve the Catastrophe, they had to deal with these native Subterranean Mutants. In a way, this had become an invasion.

Without the Black Star Army's help, the Sunils would not have had the ability to deal with the Subterranean Mutants. They would have had no choice but to coexist with them in terror. Only with Black Star did the Sunil have confidence in eliminating them.

Comparing the power between the two sides, it was clear that as soon as the battle started, it would be a single-sided slaughter of the Subterranean Mutants.

Herlous was a Sunil, and he stood on the Sunils' side. Even if this was not very ethical, he had to do this for the future of his race, but Black Star was different.

Black Star's home, Planet Aquamarine, had once been invaded by DarkStar. Their situation was similar to that of the Subterranean Mutants, both victims of a higher civilization. Would Black Star stand on the Subterranean Mutants' side and be unhappy with the Sunils' actions?

Herlous was very worried about this and wanted to know what Han Xiao was thinking.

Chapter 620: Budding Civilization

Han Xiao looked into Herlous' eyes and saw nervousness and hesitation in them. It seemed like Herlous cared a lot about what he was going to say next.

Ever since Han Xiao became Calamity Grade, the Grade B officers had started to respect him more and more. He had known Herlous for many years and knew him well. Herlous had wasted many years before starting to help his race. Compared to these Sunil warriors who had been suffering for a long time, he was not as decisive and thought more about things.

In the previous life, Herlous had been willing to die while stopping the Catastrophe; he was very heroic. Now that his experiences were different, naturally, his mindset was different as well.

"You're overthinking it. There are no ethics or morals in the battle of survival, just different sides. If I don't help, the Sunils will be the ones that meet their end. Isn't this what you guys hired me to prevent?"

Han Xiao patted Herlous' shoulders and said, "Indeed, Sunils are outsiders, and the Subterranean Mutants are innocent. They've done nothing wrong. However, the rules of the jungle apply everywhere; the Subterranean Mutants are an obstacle to the survival of Sunil. Since you have no choice, don't empathize with your enemies..."

"I know that, but how are we different from DarkStar if we do this?" Herlous replied.

Sunil's mother planet had been invaded and destroyed by DarkStar; they were the victims. Now, they had become the invaders like DarkStar. Herlous did not know how to feel about this change of character.

"Sunil isn't DarkStar. DarkStar destroys for the sake of destroying, but you people are trying to ensure your race's future. The motives are different. This is a battle for survival between races. Since you Sunils can't migrate again, the only thing left to do is to eliminate your enemies. There's only the weak and strong, no wrong or wrong. Don't feel too guilty about it..."

Han Xiao paused and added, "If the Subterranean Mutants paid to hire me and told me to chase the Sunils away, I might be on their side. You wouldn't hope for me to chase away your race, would you?"

As a chaotic neutral and a professional mercenary, this was not an issue at all. He had no intention of interfering with Sunil's decisions.

Battles of survival happened every day around the universe. A large number of species were being killed every second while many were being born.

Han Xiao's attitude toward this made Herlous feel relieved. At least Black Star did not dislike him because of this.

"Stop chatting, let's start," Sehrinde said coldly and impatiently before jumping right into the cave.

Herlous sighed and jumped down, too.

Han Xiao activated Berserk Ape and followed behind.

...

The three of them descended for a while, and the cave entrance started to become hard to see. Their vision was filled with darkness, and there was not a single light source. Han Xiao turned on night vision.

About a few thousand meters underground, the three of them finally arrived at the bottom of the cave and stepped on solid ground.

In front of them was the pitch-black underground, the tunnels were twisted and complex. There were quite a few Prophecy Stone mines around there, which meant there were also many Subterranean Mutant nests. The Sunils had first discovered the Subterranean Mutants' existence when they drugged till here. They had lost some exploration teams, so the digging had been stopped.

There were only marks of mining near the cave—any areas further in were the world of Subterranean Mutants. It was enormous; just the discovered area was already much bigger than Forest City. The Subterranean Mutants had probably reproduced for many years to be able to build such a magnificent underground world.

The temperature this deep under the ground was very high and contained rich heat energy. Han Xiao opened the vital sign detection radar. On it, a nest far away was filled with dense dots. Each dot represented a Subterranean Mutant, so their numbers were terrifying. In just one nest, there were tens of millions of Subterranean Mutants.

Sunil numbered these nests. The one that they were going to was the nearest Nest No. 1.

This was just the tip of an iceberg of the underground world. With how large Planet Sunil was, there was still an unknown number of nests that they had yet to discover. There were hundreds of millions of Subterranean Mutants. They were undoubtedly the owner of this planet.

The nests spread out from the Prophecy Stone mines. The dots were most dense right around the nests, like a city center.

After following the radar for a while, the three of them got closer to the nest. The corrosive slime from the Subterranean Mutants started to appear on the ground and the walls. From years and years of the Subterranean Mutants living here, the slime had turned into a thick and rubber-like layer. It felt dense and tough to the touch.

Beep beep!

This time, the radar suddenly rang. More than ten Mutants passed by in front of them. Han Xiao turned on the binoculars and locked onto the Mutants.

With one acceleration, Han Xiao instantly closed in on them. His movements left a series of afterimages, and in the blink of an eye, all the Mutants were beaten to the ground. In the face of Han Xiao's Calamity Grade strength, the battle was completely one-sided.

Herlous and Sehrinde approached and secured the Mutants. Their mission was just labor work.

The Subterranean Mutants were more than one meter long, and they had certain characteristics of insect species. Their carapace protected their muscles, and hair extended from the gaps in between their carapace, secreting slime from the inside. Their head was very small, and they had yet to develop eyes, only four agile antennae on their head. Their mouth was filled with sharp teeth to aid them in consuming rocks. They had four very lean legs with backward joints, allowing them to sprint and jump. They had a spine and a tough tail covered in carapace with a shovel-shaped end. Their overall appearance was rather vicious.

"We've caught the samples. Shall we return now?" Herlous asked softly.

"You guys go first, I'm going deeper into the nest to take a look." Han Xiao waved. The two of them did not object; they had no reason to worry about Han Xiao, given how strong he was. They took the ten or so Subterranean Mutants and returned the way they came from.

Han Xiao was the only one left. He looked at the battle information from earlier, and the attributes of the Subterranean Mutants popped up. Their total level was about thirty to forty, and they were beast type beings. They all had the Psychic Resistance talents. Other than that, there was nothing special.

Their psychic resistance is quite high indeed; they won't be affected by the Prophecy Stones. Han Xiao nodded. Now, he had to find out the reason these Subterranean Mutants lived near the Prophecy Stones.

Activating the stealth function, Han Xiao moved deeper into the nest. He started to meet Subterranean Mutants more and more frequently. However, Berserk Ape's stealth function was definitely not something that the Subterranean Mutants could discover. It was a smooth journey.

The closer he got to the center of the next, the bigger the Subterranean Mutants got. From over one meter long to more than four meters long, their carapace was also thicker.

Han Xiao suddenly realized that there were some skew slash marks on one of the stone walls that formed images with unknown meanings. He looked at it carefully and confirmed this was a drawing made by Subterranean Mutants using their tails.

"Is this a type of recording? The Subterranean Mutants' language?"

The creation of words usually meant that civilization was sprouting.

Are the Subterranean Mutants in the transition from beasts to an intelligent species?

This thought flashed past, and Han Xiao continued forward. Very soon, he came to a Prophecy Stone mine. He noticed that there were not any signs that it had been mined before, as if the Subterranean Mutants had never used the Prophecy Stones, only guarding the mine.

Do the Subterranean Mutants just like the radiation from the Prophecy Stones? Han Xiao was curious. Suddenly, he thought of destroying a part of the mine so that he could test what the Subterranean Mutants' reaction would be.

Han Xiao deactivated his stealth mode, took out the Watcher Instrument, and ruthlessly bombarded this small mine.

Boom!

The explosions made this part of the tunnel tremble.

The next moment, the radar showed that the Subterranean Mutants in the entire nest were gathering toward this place as if they had gone crazy.

The Subterranean Mutants sprinted over from all directions. Han Xiao casually set the Watcher Instrument into explosive attacks and free fire mode. Beams of light exploded within the beasts as its power easily tore many Subterranean Mutants apart.

The Subterranean Mutants came nonstop, but not even one could get close to Han Xiao without turning into shattered meat and becoming a part of the carcass pile that kept growing taller. Han Xiao strolled about casually. The huge difference in strength made the Subterranean Mutants' advantage in numbers meaningless.

Although there was no danger, this phenomenon made Han Xiao realize one thing.

Why is that when I caused damage to the Prophecy Stone mine, this entire nest went haywire and they all came toward me?

This feels like the reaction a being will have when its weakness is attacked... Han Xiao started to speculate.

This meant that this nest had a collective mind. Maybe their communication method was psychic waves and there was a psychic network around the nest. The Prophecy Stones then happened to possess psychic radiation, which had affected these Subterranean Mutants for many years, causing their psychic abilities to evolve. Maybe the Subterranean Mutants were using the Prophecy Stones to maintain their psychic network.

Therefore, the Subterranean Mutants were using the Prophecy Stone mines as tools. It was a 'communication base station' for them!

That would explain why the Subterranean Mutants had set up their nests around the Prophecy Stone mines, or tribes might be a more suitable term. One mine could only be used by one Subterranean Mutant tribe, each tribe had no connection to the others, and the Prophecy Stone mines could be considered a part of these Subterranean Mutants.

This type of race specialty... why is it somewhat similar to the World Tree Civilization?

Suddenly, Han Xiao felt slight dizziness. Notifications popped up on his interface continuously like he was being spammed.

_____________________

You have received a psychic attack. Due to the high difference in level, you are immune to its damage. Judging debuff... passed. You are immune to the [Confused] status!

_____________________

Psychic attack? Han Xiao was shocked. He quickly looked at the battle information and noticed that the usual Subterranean Mutants did not have this ability, but these three- to four-meter elite Mutants all had the [Psychic Confusion] ability.

The level difference was too large. Plus, Han Xiao had [Advanced Psychological Resistance]. Most of the psychic attacks from the elite Mutants had no effect on him, but there were also very few of them that did pass the judgment out of luck and disrupted his mind.

Han Xiao became alert. Psychic attacks were a counter to his mana to health cycle. He did not remain in place anymore. The Berserk Ape activated in an instant and turned into a stream of black light, opening a bloody path in the wave of beasts.

Going back the way he had come and arriving at the cave entrance, he killed thousands of Subterranean Mutants in a short period. As long as Han Xiao had enough time, slaughtering all the Subterranean Mutants would be a piece of cake to him. However, the level difference was too huge; killing one Subterranean Mutant only gave one experience point. Even if he killed ten million Subterranean Mutants by himself, it would only give him the same number in experience. It was far from harvesting his leeks.

However, to the players, killing was a path to leveling up fast. There were players who did exactly that in Han Xiao's previous life. In the end, they were wanted by countless organizations and used up all their revives every single day. These were even more fearless than the Great Mechanic Han.

Having collected quite an amount of intelligence, Han Xiao went out of the cave and returned to the surface. As soon as he came up, he saw Herlous and Sehrinde waiting for him. The ten or so Mutants that had been captured alive were all in cages and secured.

"Black Star, what did you discover?" Herlous smelled blood.

"Hmm, quite a lot of interesting information. We'll talk when we get back."

The three of them boarded the spaceship and returned to Forest City. The Sunil Research Department was already waiting. They smoothly handed over the Subterranean Mutants that they had captured.

Han Xiao shared his discoveries with the Sunil Research Department, regarding signs of Subterranean Mutants becoming a civilization, the use of the Prophecy Stone mines, and so on.

He easily completed many small goals from the Sunil Main Storyline missions. All the goals under 'Slaughterer' were completed, which gave him a few million experience. The Mission Rating increased visibly, too.

Next, he needed to wait for the Sunil Research Department to finish their study on the Subterranean Mutants, as well as wait for the galactic construction team to arrive and build Base No. 3. After these two things were done, the elimination of Subterranean Mutants would officially start.

...

Right after Han Xiao left, the Subterranean Mutants in Nest No. 1 collected all the carcasses and piled them up together. It was very bloody. If a normal person saw this, they would most likely vomit.

Countless Subterranean Mutants waved their antennae as if they were communicating silently.

After quite some time, all the Subterranean Mutants seemed to have come to an agreement. They all gathered around the mine area and lowered their bodies as if they were worshipping the mine, similar to worshipping ancient totems.

Right after that, all the Subterranean Mutants suddenly started to use their shovel-shaped tails to mine the Prophecy Stones, digging them up, and piled them together under tight protection.

A few hundred Subterranean Mutants wanted to eat the Prophecy Stones but were attacked by the others and quickly bitten to death.

The Subterranean Mutants dug very quickly. With their large numbers, not long after, the huge mine was entirely harvested. All the Prophecy Stones were dug out.

The tall, elite Subterranean Mutants moved the large Prophecy Stones and formed an enormous group, protected by countless other Subterranean Mutants that surrounded them. Then, this Subterranean Mutant tribe with tens of millions of members gave up their original nest and moved to further away.

During that, there were some that took a bite at the Prophecy Stones. Like the others, they were killed. Their bodies were torn apart, and the Prophecy Stones were dug out from their stomachs to continue to be transported.

This Subterranean Mutant tribe started to migrate, going further away from the nest that Han Xiao and the others had entered.

Chapter 621: The Race with the Highest Potential

A few days later, the interstellar construction team finally arrived on Planet Sunil, and the temporary camp of the players completed its gorgeous transformation into a construction site. The structure of the buildings in Base No. 3 was created based on Base No. 1. In order to demonstrate their capabilities, the engineering team used their advanced equipment to quickly lay the foundations, allowing houses to be built.

The players also came in handy, being highly enthusiastic about their work. They were able to endure hardship for the sake of success, working hard to contribute to the expansion of the Black Star Army. Coupled with the efficient engineering team, the construction efficiency of Base No. 3 was surprisingly high.

More members of the Black Star Army responded to the call, gathering on Planet Sunil. All the officers such as Aroshia, Reynold, Sylvia, Harmon, and Ginette brought thousands of mercenaries with them. As for the other mercenaries, they arrived in streams one after another. So far, the number of players on Planet Sunil had increased to 280,000.

The Sunils shared a Grade A Ranked mission, generating a high degree of enthusiasm from the players. So far, all Grade A missions that players had seen were main storyline missions, and the upcoming war between the Sunils and the Subterranean Mutants was also seen as a new main storyline by the players.

Ever since the players entered the interstellar region, they had not experienced an incident that could be considered a main storyline. Because they all belonged to Black Star's faction, they saw it as their core. Everyone believed that the Black Star Army was the main point to start the next main storyline, and the current situation only confirmed their line of thought.

Because of the Black Star Army, the players could obtain the main storyline of Planet Sunil. This was the storyline brought by the faction. The players could clearly distinguish between their primary and secondary relationships, and they could see the potential of being in the Black Star Army.

This meant that they would be able to grow with the faction and trigger more main storylines due to the nature of their work. The future would be bright for them!

Recognizing this, the players got extremely excited. Just fantasizing about the future of their faction would result in their hearts feeling as though there was an itch to be scratched. Maybe, the true advantage of being born on Planet Aquamarine was being able to join the Black Star Faction.

Han Xiao had always paid attention to the players' dynamics, and such collective activities helped to improve cohesion. Main Storyline missions like the Sunils' would make the players feel more at home. In his memory, Han Xiao could remember many Grade A missions, and this was part of his plan. Using the Sunils' main storyline as a gauge, he would occasionally release a 'main storyline' mission to the players.

In the conference room, the officers gathered. This was the first time in many months that many of them had been present. All officers had been recruited to participate in this employment task. They had also brought out most of the army's spaceships as well as a large amount of supplies.

Han Xiao sat at the head, projecting the data on the table as he explained the situation.

"The Sunils have studied the physiological structure of the Subterranean Mutants and have produced results. The Subterranean Mutants have some level of wisdom, and the antennae on their heads are important organs for perceiving the outside world. They release weak signals to detect their surroundings, which will feedback to the brain. In other words, the antennae can be said to serve as their eyes..."

Reynold nodded as he added, "It is a biological creature with awareness. This race has great potential."

Everyone glanced at him but said nothing.

Han Xiao then continued. "The Subterranean Mutants have two ways of communicating with each other. The first method is to have their antennae in contact, and they can communicate spiritually. The second involves being in contact with a certain amount of Prophecy Stones. They will then be able to perform wide-area spiritual connection and communicate with all in the range at the same time. The number of Prophecy Stones determines the range.

"Other than this, the Subterranean Mutants have a weakness. They seem to be afraid of ultraviolet rays. Research has shown that normal sunlight can give them burns. This is both good news and bad news, as it means that we are unable to lure them up to the surface.

"Thus, we currently have two countermeasures. The first is to send the mercenaries underground to fight, clearing the mutant species out step by step. The second is to attempt to create a large-scale biochemical weapon against the Subterranean Mutants. Emerald Grass, this mission will be left to you."

Han Xiao speedily explained the situation and began to assign tasks. Since he had a Pharmacist in his team, he could not be bothered to spend money on consulting various drug research facilities.

"Humph, only thinking of me when you have a problem and not looking for me when you are fine. Let me tell you, right now, I love to save people. As for researching whatever poison gas, don't look for me. I only want to be a good person."

Emerald Grass crossed her arms and turned her head sideways to express her dissatisfaction.

Han Xiao only shot a glance at her before saying, "The research funding that you applied for has been approved."

"Relax, I'll definitely research the poison out for you!" Emerald Grass immediately changed her tone without any shame.

Rolling his eyes, Han Xiao turned to look at Feidin, changing into a smile. "Feidin, I also need your help this time. I need you to help me detect the mental networks of the Subterranean Mutants and help us understand their communication status. Try and see if you can mislead them."

Because the Subterranean Mutants utilized mental communication, this was where a Psychic would come into play.

"Is that why you called me over?" Feidin had on a helpless look, shaking his head. "I refuse."

He was not a mercenary but a client. Thus, he did not wish to participate in the slaughter.

"Alright then..." Han Xiao did not press the issue. After all, he still had the Volga brothers. As he was about to address them, he suddenly recalled something and asked, "That's right, how are things going on between you and Chen Xing?"

He still remembered his personal mission with Feidin.

"I'm chatting with her every day. Our relationship is still okay, I guess..."

Feidin scratched his face, looking a little embarrassed.

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

What are you embarrassed about? Are you sure your relationship is only okay?

Han Xiao felt his scalp turning numb. He felt that the result that he had foreseen seemed to be coming into reality...

This is too scary. Would I really see what soul partners look like in the flesh?

Coughing, Han Xiao knocked on the table, returning to the original topic.

"At the moment, we have only found seven nests, all of which are built near the Prophecy Stones underground. Reynold, capitalize on the high radiation nature of the Prophecy Stones and create an equipment that can detect the veins in a wide range. It would be best if it is detectable from the surface level. Configure it on a spaceship and have the spaceship search for the veins throughout the entire planet to find all their lairs."

Reynold was seated on the edge of his seat, and he calmly nodded. "It shall be done."

At this time, Herlous scratched his head before suddenly interrupting. "I have a question."

Han Xiao turned to look at him. "What's wrong?"

"Actually, I wanted to ask this since just now..." Herlous pointed at Reynold. "But who is he?"

Reynold had joined less than a month ago, and other than Sylvia and Aroshia who always stayed at Base No.1, the rest of the Officers present were not aware of him. However, they could feel the imposing aura released by Reynold, which was probably the strongest other than Black Star himself. Thus, Herlous asked the question that was in everyone's hearts.

"My name is Reynold. I'm a Mechanic. Because I admire His Excellency Black Star's style and grace, I specially came to join the Black Star Army and to learn from him. Black Star is now my teacher, and Sylvia my Senior Sister. I'm currently handling the post of Logistics Manager in the Black Star Army and look forward to working with all of you."

Reynold's tone was solemn and serious.

"Senior Sister‽" Everyone present was shocked, staring at Sylvia with wide eyes. Every one of them had their suspicions carved directly on their faces.

Sylvia shivered in response, shrinking back as she exclaimed, "I've said it hundreds of times already, don't... don't call me that!"

With this episode, everyone now knew who Reynold was and accepted this new colleague.

After finishing this matter, Han Xiao stood up and simply said, "Get to work."

Two days passed.

The sun shone brightly overhead.

The players gathered at the military camp that was situated beside the burrow. There was also a fully armored squadron of Sunils, ready to set off.

It was the day on which they would act officially. Due to the fear of ultraviolet rays, the plan to lure the Subterranean Mutants out of their holes had been abandoned. It also took time for the development of poisons and the detection of more burrows, so all that could be done now was to forcefully attack.

Unlike the serious and silent atmosphere on the Sunil side, the players were excited and raring to go.

"With so many people moving, this will be a big scene!"

"Hehe, the more the merrier."

The Main Storyline mission officially started, and a large portion of players had arrived. The majority were basically battle hungry people. With this mission being a war between races, to participate personally in such a battlefront with over 100,000 people would rouse the blood in most people.

However, most of the players did not care about the ethnic status of the Subterranean Mutants. They only cared about the task requirements. He just had to tell them where to go, who to kill, and how much they would get in return.

Hundreds of thousands of players as well as the squad from Sunil faced the commander of this operation, Herlous. Behind him stood Sehrinde and a batch of Sunil warriors, and beside him was a portion of the Black Star Officers, mainly Aroshia, Ginette, Harmon, and the Volga brothers.

Han Xiao did not move out with them. He was busy supervising the progress of Base No. 3, preventing any deaths as well as preventing the engineers from cutting corners.

In order to allow the huge number of troops to enter the ground, the Sunils had widened the diameter of the cave's entrance over the last few days. The yawning black hole of the cave's mouth resembled the mouth of an abyss.

Herlous faced the crowd and started to speak. Using his Pugilist energy, his voice was amplified into surging waves, spreading to the whole army.

"Warriors of Sunil, our race has suffered too many hardships. The last enemy is now hidden underground. Only by getting rid of them can we end it all and lead Sunil to a brighter future. My comrades, let us battle!"

Every Sunil soldier's breathing turned heavy. Every person who was willing to become a soldier had long decided to sacrifice their life for their race. Now, there was hope. Everyone was full of zeal, and the Subterranean Mutants in the ground seemed to have suddenly become the enemies in their eyes.

"Let's go!"

Herlous led the charge into the cave, and the huge expeditionary force followed close behind him, entering the hole with a mighty roar.

The long, arduous march failed to obliterate the high morale of the Sunils, and many players were also affected by the atmosphere, feeling that they were saving Sunil and developing a sense of pride.

Finally, the vanguard reached the bottom and quickly took out various lighting equipment, brightening the dark underground world. Unexpectedly, the troops did not continue to move forward but rather stayed around the entrance to construct a camp.

Because the subterranean world was too large, there were several nests around them that would not be able to be eliminated overnight. Therefore, their tactic was to build a camp step by step in the subterranean world to serve as a bridgehead and supply point for both the soldiers and the mercenaries.

After arranging the teams, Herlous turned on the life detection radar. A glance at it gave him a huge surprise.

In the area of the first nest that they had explored prior, all life signals had already disappeared!

This time, their target was Nest No. 1, but their target had vanished.

Herlous' surprise showed on his face, and he even wondered if the radar had malfunctioned.

Herlous started to become alert. Because they did not know much about the Subterranean Mutants, this lack of knowledge meant danger.

At this time, the rear troops entered one after another. Herlous quickly passed down the order to have the construction of the camp passed over to the main force before taking the vanguard to Nest No.1.

As they penetrated deeper underground, Herlous grew more vigilant, preparing to be attacked at any time. However, he went unimpeded all the way to the depths of the lair.

The Subterranean Mutants in Nest No. 1 seemed to have vanished into thin air.

"Where have they gone?"

Herlous could not wrap his head around it, and without being stopped, he quickly reached the location of the Prophecy Stone Mine.

Upon seeing the condition of the stones, everyone present was stunned.

The veins were all empty, and there were obvious traces of mining left by the Subterranean Mutants, as if they had dug out all the Prophecy Stones.

Herlous hurriedly asked the team to investigate the entire lair. Before long, he came to the conclusion that the Subterranean Mutant tribe had left the lair with the Prophecy Stones.

"Why would they do this? The other nests have obviously not changed, but the nest we last explored disappeared..."

Herlous suddenly opened his eyes wide in realization. Could it be that their appearance had caused the Subterranean Mutants to relocate?

The level of wisdom displayed by them had gone beyond his imagination.

And there were tens of millions of such Subterranean Mutants! It had only taken them a few days to withdraw completely—this efficiency was too frightening!

"What do we do now?"

Everyone gazed at each other. They had come over with high morale, only to find out that the enemy had disappeared. It felt as though they had taken a full swing on a cotton bed. Their hearts were empty, full of disappointment.

Herlous hesitated a moment before replying, "We'll set up camp first. The situation is now beyond our control. I'll first report back to the upper echelons."

"What, you said that the Subterranean Mutants are showing incredible wisdom‽"

The Sunil superior Otis sucked in a breath of cold air when he received the report.

The Prophecy Stones were something that the Sunils had to destroy. They had thought that the Subterranean Mutants were confined to the Prophecy Stone veins, but they did not expect that they would be able to actively dig out the stones and move around.

Even though the veins would go, the Prophecy Stones produced by the veins would still exist. To have the Prophecy Stones follow the Subterranean Mutants as they moved around would undoubtedly make it harder to destroy.

Furthermore, the potential shown by the Subterranean Mutants raised warning bells in Otis' heart.

"With time, the Subterranean Mutants will surely grow into an intelligent race, and sooner or later, they will form a new civilization, competing with us for the resources of the planet. They must be smothered while they're still in the cradle!" Otis clenched his fists tightly.

"Ah? They took the Prophecy Stones and ran? What nonsense is this?"

Han Xiao had also received the report, and his expression was thoughtful.

He suddenly thought of a bold idea.

Chapter 622: Plan B, Migration

Han Xiao had originally thought that the Subterranean Mutants needed to set up their nests near the mines and would not move. However, Herlous' report had completely refreshed his understanding of these Subterranean Mutants. They could actually move house as well!

They had just gained the high ground and were about to extract all the crystals but found out that the other party had run away with all the crystals!

"They actually took the initiative to escape? Could it be because of our last raid on their nest?" Han Xiao tried to work out what was going on.

The entire nest had surrounded him back then, but he had still been able to escape while killing many of their brethren. Although he had only killed a few thousand Subterranean Mutants, all the other mutants who were telepathically connected could clearly feel the pain of death. As such, he single-handedly terrified the tens of thousands of mutants.

Fearing the strong was an innate instinct. As such, the mutants of the first nest treated him as their natural enemy and decided to all migrate away. Their telepathic connection provided the mutants with an extremely efficient way to make such a decision.

"That should be the case." Han Xiao rubbed his head and felt that his guess was probably right. The Subterranean Mutants behaved just like animals. They would retreat if they faced a danger that they could not resist.

Such a situation immediately gave him a new plan.

The Sunils wanted to get rid of the Subterranean Mutants mainly to wipe out the Prophecy Stone Mines that the Subterranean Mutants were protecting. However, recent events had proven that the Subterranean Mutants were capable of digging up the mines and shifting them away. Since those mines were able to be shifted, the contradiction had been resolved.

As long as these Subterranean Mutants left the planet with the Prophecy Stones, the problem would immediately be solved. This way, the Sunils would not need to wipe out the Subterranean Mutant race, and it was a win-win situation for both parties.

Han Xiao immediately frowned and understood the difficulty of such a task. While this is a great idea, it was not a very feasible one. He would have to catch the Subterranean Mutants that numbered in the billions one by one and choose an uninhabited planet. He would then have to prepare a large number of spaceships to transport them all. This would require much more manpower and resources.

If they could migrate, the Sunils would have left by now.

Obviously, the Sunils did not have such strength and were not willing to abandon their homeland.

Thus, the likelihood of exterminating the Subterranean Mutants seemed higher, and it would get rid of their problem once and for all. To the Sunils, protecting the Subterranean Mutants was just a waste of resources, and destruction was the simplest.

"If I want to use migration as an alternative to elimination, I will need an external force like a large financial group to step in..."

Han Xiao's brows were furrowed. Just what was the meaning of migrating all the Subterranean Mutants? Could the benefits of an undeveloped race exceed the cost to migrating them? If the benefits did not outweigh the costs, the value of saving them would reduce greatly.

According to their employment terms, protecting the mutants was completely unnecessary.

Furthermore, Han Xiao knew that the Sunils would definitely favor extermination.

Thus, this meant that the survival and death of an entire race would be determined by a thought of his.

Should he save them or not?

Han Xiao began hesitating. Even if the Sunils detected this other possibility, they definitely would not take the initiative to mention it. Thus, as long as Han Xiao did not suggest this alternative, the Subterranean Mutants would definitely be exterminated.

Originally, he had been no more than an executioner to complete the employment contract, but after realizing this alternative, his role had changed. He was no longer a simple mercenary but the individual who could decide the fate of an entire race. The pressure of the decision lay squarely on his shoulders.

When he had no other choice, Han Xiao would not feel the slightest bit of guilt. However, things were different now. A weak race did not have the ability to control their own life or death, but he had the authority to determine the fate of an entire race.

After pondering for a long while, Han Xiao let out a long sigh and ordered, "Herlous, continue the operation and attack another nest."

"Understood." Herlous hung up the call.

Han Xiao then called Sylvia over. He got her to overlook the construction team and left the construction site to find Feidin, who was enjoying nature in the forest.

In the lush forest, Feidin was seated underneath a tree with his formless psychic energy creating ripples in the air. This was the phenomenon of a Psychic cultivating.

Psychic energy was the combination of both energy and mental energy and there were some Espers who had such abilities. However, the Psychics were ranked as one of the top five Super systems because they had a complete training system. As long as one had the talent, one would be able to grasp psychic energy through training alone and didn't require the mutation of genes.

"Why are you here?"

Upon hearing Han Xiao's footsteps, Feidin opened his eyes and revealed a courteous smile. However, a distant look could be seen in his eyes.

Feidin truly felt disgusted with the current employment mission of the Black Star Army. Wiping out an entire race had touched his bottom line, and his attitude toward Han Xiao had changed because of this.

"I wish to seek your help. It is the same request as before. I hope that you can attempt to communicate with the Subterranean Mutants," Han Xiao said slowly.

"Didn't I reject you already? My answer is the same," Feidin replied without even thinking. He knew that this war was not wrong, but he did not wish to be the accomplice of a massacre.

Han Xiao was not too surprised. Based on his understanding of Feidin, he knew that Feidin was a kindhearted individual.

"You misunderstood me. The same reason isn't the same as before..." Han Xiao then briefly described his idea of a migration before saying with a smile, "If we can establish a bridge of communication, this hypothetical situation may become reality."

Feidin's eyes brightened up, and he stood up abruptly. "Are you serious‽"

"You know my reputation." Han Xiao smiled.

Feidin looked at Han Xiao and revealed a warm smile that would cause youthful girls to shriek in excitement. "I didn't misjudge you after all. Let's go. I will do my best to help you."

They smiled at each other.

Seeking help from Feidin was Han Xiao's decision. He had decided to protect the Subterranean Mutants.

It was not out of the kindness of his heart but his desire for growth.

The benefits of the Sunil employment would be gone after the completion of the mission, but migrating the Subterranean Mutants would leave him with future benefits. This was akin to planting two different kinds of crops in the same piece of land.

The Subterranean Mutant race was a race with great potential, and there was a chance for them to develop into a new NPC resource. There was value for Han Xiao to make such an investment. While the initial investment would not be a small amount, Han Xiao had the capital at the moment to have a few additional investments.

Telepathic communication would resolve the problem of communication. If the Subterranean Mutants could come to an agreement with him and willingly leave Planet Sunil, he would not need to capture them one by one, and it would save him a lot of trouble.

However, the Subterranean Mutants might not be able to understand the concept of the galaxy and planets. They had not even explored the entire planet before. Thus, the only solution would be to let those Subterranean Mutants feel the threat of death and control them with fear.

Thus, massacres still could not be avoided.

Apart from this, there was another reason. The accomplishment of saving an entire race was much greater, and the players would enjoy playing the role of being saviors much more. Thus, this would help create a better sense of belonging to the Black Star Army.

Of course, his Favorability with Feidin was also another reason. Han Xiao did not want the crops planted in his backyard to escape from him.

Half an hour later, the expedition forces set up a temporary camp, and their illumination equipment lit up the dark underground world. The Sunil armed forces were currently on guard outside the camp.

Herlous had already received his next order and led the army to the coordinates of the second nest.

As they approached the nest, the vanguard forces met a large group of around three hundred mutants.

"Woah, they are much uglier than in the pictures."

Many players revealed looks of disgust with some players turning pale. The Subterranean Mutants that had the appearance of bugs looked like monsters with unpardonable sins in this superficial generation.

These Subterranean Mutants also spotted the expedition forces and gathered together as though they were curious about these creatures that they had never seen before.

Tuk tuk tuk!

The next moment, the cannons were fired!

The Sunil soldiers remained expressionless as they fired their cannons without any hesitation. The cannon fire broke the silence of the underground world and illuminated the darkness. The dense wave of cannon fire landed on the bodies of the Subterranean Mutants and reduced them to meat paste.

"Advance!"

The sergeants of the various squads roared, and the Sunil force marched forward in neat rows and synchronized steps.

Rumble!

Right at this moment, a rumbling sound could be heard from the direction of the nest, and the ground began to tremor. It was the sound of thousands of beasts approaching them.

"Defensive formation! Hold your ground!"

The Sunil forces adjusted their formation swiftly and prepared themselves for the impact.

Boom!

A black wave flooded over from all the different tunnels. The second nest was also home to millions of mutants.

Right at this moment, Herlous' voice thundered.

"Black Star mercenaries, all weapons free!"

The army of players charged out, and rainbow-colored lights covered the entire battlefield.

Boom!

Both waves collided with each other, and war broke out!

At the same time, Han Xiao arrived at the Sunil research facility with Feidin and borrowed the few Subterranean Mutants that they captured alive previously.

The ten or so Subterranean Mutants were locked up separately and were not allowed to come into contact with each other. A small pile of Prophecy Stones was placed in the middle for them to establish telepathic connection.

"You are the expert; I shall hand them over to you," Han Xiao said.

Feidin smiled and released his psychic energy.

The Subterranean Mutants used the Prophecy Stones as a communication hub. As long as a Psychic could tune his psychic energy to the same frequency as the mutants, he would be able to communicate with the mutants.

After a period of adjustment, Feidin's eyes lit up. "Success!"

Just as he said that, his expression immediately became weird.

"What's wrong?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Er... things are slightly different from what I expected," Feidin said with a weird tone. "Accept my mental connection. I will pull you into the conversation."

Han Xiao nodded and did not reject Feidin's mental connection.

The instant he accepted the connection, his vision was split into two. One was the real world, and the other was a vast white colored space without an end in sight. This was the telepathic space, and he could cut off the connection at any time.

The Subterranean Mutants and Feidin were also in this space, and their locations were the same as in reality. They all took on the appearance of glowing bodies, and only their silhouettes could be seen.

Before Han Xiao could even react, he could hear the mutants chattering away.

"Eh? Another one of our brethren."

"Why do they look slightly different? They're too ugly."

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment and never expected the Subterranean Mutants to treat him as one of them. The mutants must have thought that the only ones who could enter this telepathic world were their own kind.

These Subterranean Mutants then changed the topic and began to chat among themselves.

"Why are we locked up?"

"I don't know. Also, you asked this question before."

"Those long creatures look so strange. They actually feed us food and take away our feces."

"Haha, I understand! Our feces must be their food!"

"I see! I understand too! So, the more we excrete, the more they will feed us!"

"How sick, there are actually those who eat feces."

"Hehe, I just had a nice, big sh*t. They will definitely have a full meal."

"Woah, how amazing."

Just what is this nonsense... Han Xiao listened until his mouth cramped up. However, this conclusion was truly sensible from the perspective of the mutants.

He had thought that these mutants would be filled with hatred but never expected their conversation to be so casual and light-hearted...

Chapter 623: One Batch at a Time (1)

While the picture was completely different from what Han Xiao had expected, Han Xiao received quite a bit of information from their conversation.

The Subterranean Mutants had the ability to think logically and had a certain level of intelligence. However, their ability to recognize and differentiate the different races was not fully developed yet.

After knowing that Feidin was able to communicate with the Subterranean Mutants, Han Xiao terminated the mental link.

"We can definitely communicate with them through the Prophecy Stones. If we make use of the mine, we should be able to communicate with the entire nest," Feidin said.

"Then let's find a nest to try."

Han Xiao nodded and had a target in mind.

A thick bloody smell filled Nest No. 2, with puddles of blood all around. This was the scene after a massacre.

The faces of many players turned pale as the scene before them was truly too shocking. Even after completing a small part of their mission, the players could not be happy. Many of them could not help but turn on the green filter mode.

Only the Sunil warriors were completely calm. They were far too used to seeing such a sight and were completely indifferent toward it. Furthermore, they had lost some of their soldiers in the previous battle, and their armor was full of cracks.

Herlous led the vanguard troops ahead and destroyed the entire nest. He killed millions of mutants, and the remaining few escaped in fear, taking with them a portion of the Prophecy Stones.

The logistics troops began to mine the Prophecy Stones, and the main troops reorganized their formation on the spot. They used flamethrowers to burn up the corpses of the Subterranean Mutants.

Herlous held onto his Battleship Slicing Blade and was resting by the side. Previously, he had been the tip of the spear and was like moving meat grinder, single handedly killing tens of thousands of Subterranean Mutants. His strength was far from Han Xiao's, and he consumed a great deal of stamina in the battle.

After a while, a soldier ran over and gave a military salute.

"The mining is complete. Commander, please give us your next order."

"Return to the temporary camp and replenish our ammunition."

While the Subterranean Mutants were not strong, their numbers were frightening. Cleaning up a single nest had exhausted over sixty percent of their ammunition, and almost all the players had some injuries.

If they continued to attack the nests, the number of casualties would definitely increase. Thus, Herlous decided to return to camp and rest for a few hours first.

The troops marched back to their temporary camp, and Herlous saw two figures appearing in the camp—Han Xiao and Feidin.

"Why are the two of you here?" Herlous welcomed them with a questioning look on his face.

Han Xiao did not reply to the question and looked toward the troops. "How are the casualties?"

"There are very few casualties, but..." Herlous brows were furrowed. "This is only the first battle, and there are many nests all around the planet. The number of casualties isn't ideal. The deaths of the Sunils will be too severe, and we can only rely on our mercenaries."

The mine detector that Reynold had developed was already in use, and Han Xiao had deployed a few dozen spaceships to scan the entire planet. In just a short few days, they had already found a few dozen underground mines all over the planet.

Some of the nests were large and some small. The largest had a population of a few hundred million while the smallest had millions at the very least. The total number of Subterranean Mutants underground had reached a staggering few billion.

The moment he thought about the staggering number of enemies, Herlous' heart sank.

Furthermore, the positions of the other nests were different, and new underground tunnels had to be made in many locations. Without the undying Black Star Army, it was no more than a dream for the Sunils to wipe out the mutants. Only the Black Star Army would be capable of such a feat.

Han Xiao knew what Herlous was thinking about and briefly explained his plan of migrating the mutants. "I am here to communicate with the Subterranean Mutants. If I can convince a portion of the mutants to submit to us and get the mutants to convince other mutants, we will be able to greatly reduce the number of enemies."

Herlous' eyes lit up. He would naturally be willing to do so if it would reduce the number of casualties when cleaning up the mutants. "Do we have to change our strategy?"

"No, continue to attack the nests of the mutants, but there isn't a need to chase those who escape. I want to plant a seed of fear in their hearts as it will make it easier to persuade them," Han Xiao said slowly.

Compared to killing, this was a much more efficient method.

After leaving the camp, Han Xiao and Feidin paid a visit to the second nest and caught up to the mutants that had escaped.

The number of casualties in this tribe was disastrous, and upon discovering Han Xiao and Feidin, a fight could not be avoided. However, they could not threaten Han Xiao in the slightest.

Han Xiao summoned his Mechanical Army and killed a path toward the Prophecy Stones that these mutants were moving. They then infiltrated the mental network of the mutants.

The next moment, all the attacking mutants suddenly paused. If they had expressions on their faces, they would surely have looked dumbfounded.

In their knowledge, only those of their kind were capable of connecting to them mentally. However, Han Xiao had just killed them and was obviously not their kind. This situation confused the Subterranean Mutants, whose intelligence was not fully developed.

"Who are you?"

In the mental network, many of the mutants revealed emotions of shock.

"I am Black Star, an emissary from the galaxy..." Han Xiao then briefly explained what was going on with 'appropriate' changes.

He threw the entire blame of massacring the Subterranean Mutants to the Sunils, and Han Xiao described the Sunils as though they were demons. He then described himself as someone willing to help their race and a friendly emissary who was convincing the Sunils to stop their massacre. He then promised that he could stop the slaughter on the condition that they surrendered and moved out of this planet.

To allow the mutants to understand what was going on, Han Xiao had also briefly mentioned some basic knowledge of the universe and some of the benefits that they could receive.

The efficiency of a mental connection was extremely high, and the entire race fell into deep thought. It was as though they had just listened to the preaching of a heavenly book.

To the galactic residents, what Han Xiao had just said was no more than common sense. However, it completely changed the view that the mutants had of the world. In their eyes, the underground world was their entire world, and the planet and galaxy were completely new concepts.

The Subterranean Mutants viewed those who came from above ground as their enemies, and the Sunils treated them the same.

A mutant that seemed to be the leader of the tribe then took the initiative to communicate with Han Xiao.

"We are willing to surrender. Please do not hurt us anymore."

Almost all the mutants knelt down on the ground and displayed their intent to submit.

The tribe leader treated Han Xiao extremely respectfully. The words that came out from Han Xiao's mouth far exceeded the boundaries of his knowledge and was far too shocking to him. Because of their undeveloped intelligence, they treated Han Xiao as a god-like figure and began worshiping him.

The persuasion process was far easier than he had imagined.

But thinking back, it was not too surprising. The intelligence of the Subterranean Mutants was no different from children. They did not understand any complex feelings such as glory or humiliation, and their view of hatred was also extremely basic.

The Subterranean Mutants had not grown out of their bestial nature. Beasts that were afraid would reveal signs of submission. This tribe that had been massacred by Herlous was already thoroughly frightened.

The Subterranean Mutants did not have any natural predators, and they could feed on the rocks underground without fighting with each other. Thus, they lived in peace and rarely experienced battle. At the very most, they would have small conflicts with other tribes. As such, their race was extremely simple.

The only downside was that they were far too ugly. It was probably because the underground world was far too dark, and no one could even see their appearance. Thus, they just grew as they wished.

With the ability to communicate, Han Xiao could now understand the structure of their civilization. After a series of questions, Han Xiao finally had a clear understanding of the Subterranean Mutant race.

The Subterranean Mutants knew that there were other nests near them, and they would occasionally fight each other to snatch Prophecy Stones. The structure of their society was at the caveman stage, and every tribe had a tribe leader with the development of every tribe being different. There were some with more intelligence and others that were more boorish. Their culture was starting to sprout into many different kinds of flowers.

If they developed according to their original path, the Subterranean Mutants would take many more years before the various tribes combined into a civilization with intellect and began forming kingdoms. With his interference, their development speed will be shortened by thousands of years.

"What do we need to do?" the tribe leader asked obediently.

Han Xiao thought for a while before saying, "Convince the tribes in this region and disseminate my intention. From now on, you will be my emissary, and if you complete my mission, go to the cave nearby to find the guests from the surface. They will not harm you."

"Woah, this is great!"

"They won't attack us anymore!"

The entire tribe broke out in cheers.

After giving a series of instructions and ensuring that the tribe knew their mission, Han Xiao was prepared to leave. He then realized something and asked the tribe leader, "Right, what is your name?"

"What is a name?" The tribe leader was puzzled.

Han Xiao could only helplessly explain, "It is a way to address you to allow others to know that this word represents you. For example, I am Black Star, and Black Star is me..."

The tribe leader nodded, looking as though he understood what Han Xiao said.

"Sigh, alright. I shall give you a name..." Han Xiao then looked at Feidin beside him and immediately had an idea. "Since you are so good looking, you shall be called Chen Xing."

Feidin's mental energy immediately began fluctuating wildly, and Chen Xing who was inside him began roaring, "I will definitely kill you! Do you hear me‽ I will definitely kill you!"

The ugly Subterranean Mutants sharing the same name as her was something that Chen Xing would never be able to accept.

Feidin had a helpless look on his face. "Black Star, don't tease her so much."

"Tsk tsk, the two of you are indeed of one body. You are so protective of her." Han Xiao clicked his tongue before saying to the tribe leader, "Okay, ignored what I just said. You shall be called Germinal."

There should not be anyone jumping out from their graves to disagree with him.

"Germinal..." the tribe leader muttered to himself before suddenly crying out with joy. "I have a name!"

"As for your tribe..." Han Xiao stroked his chin. "Let's just call it the Germinal Tribe."

Wait... does this mean that this fellow is the Germinal Leader?

Seeing the overjoyed tribe leader, Han Xiao had a strange look on his face.

Chapter 624: One Batch at a Time (2)

It was much more effective for the Germinal Tribe to persuade their own kind.

This region had five nests. One had been scared away by Han Xiao, and the Germinal Tribe had surrendered. Over the next few days, Herlous would first cripple the final three tribes before sending the Germinal Tribe to persuade the remnants of the tribes.

This method was far more effective than purely massacring, and the region was cleared out very quickly.

This truly surprised the Sunil soldiers. They had never imagined that the legendary Black Star would have such a brilliant strategic mind, and they were truly convinced by his abilities. They did not need to waste any time chasing after the mutants that had escaped, and the escapees of the three tribes had been convinced by the Germinal Tribe to submit. These mutants then brought their respective Prophecy Stones Base to surrender. This saved them a great deal of effort and prevented many casualties.

The players who participated in the battle were locked in a fierce debate on the forums. After learning that the Subterranean Mutants had intelligence, a portion of the players began to disagree with the action of 'massacring' them. As such, Han Xiao's action of persuading the mutants to submit had gained the approval of many players. However, such players formed the minority, and they were players who were extremely emotional.

In the beginning, only a small portion of players discussed such an issue, and the majority of the players were only bothered about completing their mission and did not think so much. But as more and more threads related to this matter were created, many players could not help but input their opinion and choose a side.

Most people were used to feeling empathy for the weak and after seeing the cruel massacre, many players started to feel apprehensive about massacring the mutants. While the Subterranean Mutants look pretty disgusting, after looking at them for a long time, they were still pretty pleasant to the... what bullsh*t! They aren't pleasant looking in any way at all!

In any case, despite feeling compassion toward the mutants, the players wouldn't hold anything back when carrying out their mission.

However, the name of 'Germinal Tribe' had truly made all the players laugh until their sides ached.

All these players had been through the events of Version 1.0 and had a deep impression of the Germinal Organization. Thus, they could not help but joke about it on the forums.

"Germinal: Coach, I want to eat a boxed lunch!"

"Germinal: Now that things have developed to such an extent, I shall not hide matters anymore. It is time for me to reveal my true self! Are those of noble birth worth more than us‽"

"Shock! Germinal is actually the true boss. It is a mysterious force in the universe with their alternate accounts all over the galaxy. The Germinal leader that we saw on Planet Aquamarine was no more than one of its doppelgangers. Such a powerful organization has been hidden for billions of years, and we have only seen the tip of the iceberg..."

"Germinal: Hmm? Has my alternate account been exposed?"

"I understand now. This is the legacy of one's faith and beliefs. I must spread the seeds of revolution throughout the entire universe. Germinal shall live forever! Our spirit will live forever!"

"The Germinals up in the heavens are watching all of you and have given you a like."

"Continue bragging. The Germinals are extremely pleased."

The presence of the Germinal Tribe lightened the heavy mood considerably.

In this region, only the final tribe that had escaped was left. Herlous personally led the troops and gave chase to the escaping tribe. All the surrendered mutants led the way with their superior digging abilities. Under the guidance of the radar, they very quickly found the new nest that had been dug by the final tribe.

This time, a battle did not break out, and the Germinal Tribe Leader communicated with the leader of the escaping tribe to convey Han Xiao's message.

This escaping tribe did not fight back at all. When Germinal displayed Han Xiao's figure, this tribe immediately recognized him.

Han Xiao was the one who had scared them into escaping and left a shadow in their hearts. This tribe was extremely timid, and the moment Germinal mentioned Han Xiao's name, they did not even hesitate in the slightest and instantly came to an agreement in their mental network to surrender.

This was the first time that the problem had been taken care of without fighting. From the depths of his heart, Herlous truly felt that Han Xiao's decision was extremely wise.

The five nests in this region had been completely cleaned up, and Herlous pulled back all of his troops from the underground world. There were many more regions for him to clean up, and dealing with these surrendered mutants would be another problem.

Herlous sought instructions from Han Xiao, and Han Xiao's reply was simple. Since there were too many Subterranean Mutants and they were not willing to come above ground, together with the fact that it was too expensive to watch over them, the Subterranean Mutants would temporarily remain in their region with the five tribes living together. Han Xiao would then set up some monitoring devices to monitor the actions of those surrendered tribes. Following which, the expedition force would take the Germinal leader and a few tribe members as a diplomatic team to persuade the other tribes.

After seeing the effectiveness of Han Xiao's plan, Herlous had no disagreements with his arrangements.

In the following days, the expedition force adopted the same strategy again.

All the underground mines on Planet Sunil had been detected by the radar, and there were 127 Subterranean Mutant nests in total. They were divided into 41 different regions, and the expedition forces cleared up almost half of the mutants all across the planet. The number of surrendered Subterranean Mutants reached a staggering 1.7 billion, and the number slaughtered would only be higher.

However, the persuasion method did not always work. Every mutant tribe had developed independently, and the level of development differed from region to region. There were certain regions that had not even developed intelligence and were not able to understand words at all, only capable of unintelligible grunts. Without any way to communicate at all, the only way to take care of them would be to slaughter them all.

All the players received great rewards from the [Eliminate Subterranean Mutants] quest, and Han Xiao was extremely pleased as well.

With the players joyfully earning their reward, Han Xiao did not remain idle and continued to harvest the wallets and experience of the players as well. His experience stash slowly approached the one billion mark.

The amount of experience points he would require in the future to level up was a sky-high figure. He had no choice but to work hard and harvest them now.

The expedition force was on track, and Base No. 3 had been fully constructed. A new and majestic Black Star base had taken root on Planet Sunil.

All the players gave a good review and shared its glory.

Everything went smoothly for Herlous, and Han Xiao did not have to personally take action. He had more than enough time to perfect Base No. 3, and this time, he was no longer alone. With Reynold as his assistant, everything went as planned, and both of them very quickly completed the factory for Base No. 3.

Reynold's personality was far too serious, and he was extremely unbearable normally. But when it came to work, his serious personality was perfect. Han Xiao was extremely pleased with Reynold's efficiency, and his [Perfect Mechanical Sense] came in extremely handy.

Han Xiao had been eyeing this talent for a very long time already. With both of them working together for a long period of time, Han Xiao tried every possible method up his sleeves to try and activate Reynold's mission but failed miserably. When facing the blockheaded Reynold, Han Xiao truly did not know how to obtain the [Perfect Mechanical Sense] Molding Ability.

However, Han Xiao did know about other Mechanic talents that were not Molding Abilities, such as [Elementary Grade Mechanical Sense], [Accurate Mechanical Sense], and so on. Their effects were naturally far from being compared to [Perfect Mechanical Sense], but something was better than nothing.

He was a Mechanic after all, and it was truly depressing that he did not even have a Mechanic talent. Looking at all his talents on the interface, those who did not know him would think that he was a main tank.

It was a pity that the Mechanical Sense talents were pretty far away. They were not in this Star Cluster, and Han Xiao did not have time to go right now.

Emerald Grass finally had some progress with her research. She managed to develop an infectious biological weapon that targeted the Subterranean Mutant's body structure and genes. After being infected, the Subterranean Mutants would slowly become weak with their outer shell slowly shedding. Their appetite would gradually be reduced to the point they were not able to consume anything. They would then die from either sickness or hunger in about ten days.

According to current circumstances, there was no need to make use of this biological weapon. After all, the mission was no longer to exterminate but migrate.

However, since the research had already been completed, Han Xiao still gave some of it to Herlous and instructed him to use it carefully. At the very least, this would greatly increase his efficiency.

On the second day after the development of the biological weapon, the upper echelons of Sunil came to visit.

In the guest room of Base No. 3, the two were seated opposite each other.

"This is truly a magnificent base."

Otis took the initiative to speak. His words were said with a fawning tone, and the envy in his eyes could not be concealed.

In just a short period of time, Black Star had created an astounding base. The wealth that Black Star had displayed truly made the Sunils feel their inferiority.

"It's fine." Han Xiao sat with his legs crossed and slowly said, "The expedition is going smoothly. Is there another reason behind your visit today?"

"Your Excellency Black Star, we wish to make a suggestion," Otis replied in a deep voice.

"You guys are the employers and have this right."

"Your plan is remarkably effective, and many of the Subterranean Mutants are gathered together. I think that this is a good opportunity to make use of the biological weapon and kill them all."

Han Xiao suddenly paused and studied Otis' expression carefully.

Otis instinctively avoided Han Xiao's gaze, but then, he felt that there was nothing to be afraid of. After all, Black Star was a mercenary who they had hired, and they naturally had the right to make such a request as the employer. He then mustered his courage to meet Han Xiao's gaze.

"Those Subterranean Mutants have already surrendered, and I will shift them to another planet. Are you requesting that I give up on this plan and wipe out their race instead?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Yes." Otis nodded heavily.

"Interesting. I am the one paying the cost for the migration, and you guys do not need to come up with a single cent. So, please give me a reason."

Otis fell silent for a moment and skirted the question. "I think that this is a very reasonable request. We are the employers, and we hope that you will carry out the mission according to our request. You will also be able to save the migration fee this way."

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and he said with a smile that did not seem like a smile, "Indeed, the mercenaries are supposed to complete the employer's request. However, we have the right to decide how to carry out the request. You guys only want to control Planet Sunil, and in my eyes, extermination isn't the best option. While we are mercenaries, we do not have to obey the orders of our employers. I have the right to reject any request that I deem to be inappropriate. If you do not have a reason for this request, this matter shall be put to rest."

Upon seeing Han Xiao's stubborn attitude, Otis grit his teeth and revealed his true intentions.

"If we do not remove all future troubles, what should we do if the Subterranean Mutants attempt to snatch Planet Sunil back after they develop on another planet? If you do not exterminate them all, can you ensure that such a thing won't happen‽"

Heh, they indeed want us to uproot the Subterranean Mutants entirely. Han Xiao then folded his arms and said, "Indeed, I cannot ensure that the Subterranean Mutants will not be a future trouble."

Otis heaved a sigh of relief. "Then, please..."

Han Xiao then interrupted him and chuckled. "Even if they will be trouble in the future, this is completely irrelevant to the current mission. So what if they come back to attack Sunil? What has that got to do with me?"

Otis was taken aback and almost flew into a rage. However, upon remembering that Han Xiao was not someone whom he could afford to provoke, he could only suppress his rage and reply with a stern voice, "Since all of you are mercenaries, you should have some professional ethics, right? How can you say something like that? We are hiring you to resolve our present circumstances."

"That's right. Isn't the Black Star Army resolving your problems? What else do you think we are doing?" Han Xiao said with a provocative smile. "We mercenaries are not nannies. You guys pay us for our services, and this is a one-off transaction. It does not mean that we will have to take responsibility for your future. Even if the Subterranean Mutants do fight back, that is another issue entirely."

"How many years will it take for the Subterranean Mutants to gain sufficient strength to retaliate? Without any obstructions, can't you develop? If both of you really end up fighting... you can just hire us again!"

Han Xiao then folded his arms and gave a 'what can you do if I want to be unreasonable' expression.

Otis' eyes widened, and he was angered to the point he did not know what to say.

To think that there would be such a shameless person!

"Of course, it isn't impossible for me to wipe out the Subterranean Mutants," Han Xiao suddenly said.

Otis could see some hope again.

"However..." Han Xiao smiled like a crafty merchant and rubbed his fingers. "You have to add money."

Otis clenched his fists in anger.

He would definitely have flipped the table in front of him if not for the fact that he could not afford to provoke Black Star.

He was too damn shameless!

Chapter 625: The Strongest Tribe, Launching of Biochemical Weapons

"Since you Sunils believe that the Subterranean Mutants are a blight, you have to pay the respective price to resolve it." Han Xiao waggled his finger. "Let me remind you, strictly speaking, these Subterranean Mutants are now technically our captives and war loot. If you want me to abandon the war loot, you must at least pay me the equivalent price."

He had long suspected that the Sunils would not be able to pay more, which allowed him to use this as a form of rejection.

Now that they had already decided on migrating the mutants, it would be impossible to change the plan to slaughtering them, otherwise it would be equivalent to deceiving Feidin. The pretty boy raised by the Goddess of Fortune would be frustrated and angered, and his Favorability would decrease.

Furthermore, going back on his word would also affect the image of the Black Star Army in the hearts of the players.

Otis' expression alternated between white and green for a while. He very much wished to eradicate the Subterranean Mutants, but he was reluctant to pay a high price for this.

"Our financial situation is not optimistic. We've spent a lot of savings just to hire you for this mission. Our people are suffering, and there must not be any more risks. Since it is as easy as raising your hand..."

Otis did not give up. As the right-hand man of the Sunil Leader, he was the buffer zone for communication between the two sides. While he saw the meaning of Han Xiao's words, he pretended not to understand and tried to force his way through.

Hearing this, Han Xiao also lost his patience, and his smile slowly vanished. Staring his Otis, he stressed heavily, "Your finances are not optimistic? Don't forget, if it wasn't for the discount I gave, you would not be able to hire my services."

Otis was startled.

"What does the plight of the Sunils have to do with me? If it was not for Herlous, do you think I would care about the life and death of your people?"

The words stuck in Otis' throat. The present scenario was all credited to Herlous, and he could not deny this.

Han Xiao's eyes were fiery and his voice stern as he warned, "Don't take my kindness for granted."

This was a warning.

The atmosphere quickly turned tense.

"You... you're mistaken..." Otis hurriedly explained, his expression cramped and palms sweating. He did not dare contradict Han Xiao.

"In short, I don't want to hear the suggestion of exterminating the entire race." Han Xiao waved his hand. "Sylvia, please escort him out."

The door opened, and Sylvia stood there with a passive expression.

"Please follow me."

"Your Excellency Black Star, you really are mistaken..."

Seeing the indifferent face of Han Xiao, Otis could only hold his tongue, not daring to explain further. He followed behind Sylvia and slipped away, only gathering his courage to bid farewell when he was at the door.

"I'm very sorry to have bothered you."

"Hmm." Han Xiao waved his hand, seeing Otis off with his gaze. He could not help but curl his lips in ridicule after he left.

"What a dreamer. Not willing to pay the price but wanting to see someone else play the bad guy? No one would accept such a deal."

Because this was a private meeting, Han Xiao was not worried that it would affect the relationship between both parties. Currently, Sunil required his help, which was why they would not attempt to do anything underhanded, but he would not hold any hope toward their government. As long as they stuck to the terms and conditions, he did not care how they looked at him.

Thinking about this matter, he then took out his communicator and contacted the two financial groups.

Since the mission was already more than halfway through, it was time to begin the migration plan. Moving two to three billion Subterranean Mutants was no small task, and there was a need for a large number of spaceships. Thus, it was easier to use the power of the financial groups to double the work with half the effort.

...

Nest No. 77 was by far the largest Subterranean Mutant tribe. This was the new target of the negotiation team.

Based on the statistics provided by the radar, Nest No. 77 had a population of about thirty to forty million. Herlous did not dare act rashly and could only use the old method of having the Germinal Tribe negotiate and attempt to convince Nest No. 77.

The Germinal leader led a few of his tribesmen to approach Nest No. 77. They discovered the presence of guards, who stopped them.

After expressing their intentions, the Germinal Tribe established a mental link, connecting with the leader of Nest No. 77.

"I am Germinal, the emissary of Black Star."

"I am Sulu-Sulu, the leader of New Rock Tribe. Very pleased to be able to communicate with you," the other party replied immediately, displaying friendliness.

Germinal got excited. "That's great, you guys have names, too!"

After persuading so many tribes, this was the first tribe that he had met that was named.

Sulu-Sulu was also happy. "We guessed correctly; the world still has other tribes similar to us."

While there were many tribes within the Subterranean Mutant race, the civilization progression of the New Rock Tribe far outstripped their peers. However, the Germinal Tribe did not understand the meaning within the other leader's words. The two of them started to converse.

Sulu-Sulu started to describe his tribe's history to Germinal.

"This place originally had four lairs. Under the lead of our ancestors, we fought fiercely with the other tribes, finally managing to annex the rest and merge them into our New Rock Tribe. This is the place where we live and thrive, but we've always believed that there are others of the same species as us in this world. Today, we have finally found our own brethren. This is a major discovery..."

Sulu-Sulu was very excited.

The Germinal leader listened as though he was a fool or drunk. This was the first time that he had heard an epic tale. If Han Xiao was present, he would immediately have known that the civilization of the New Rock Tribe had reached a new level. With the concept of history, they knew how to record past deeds, passing down inheritances and thoughts. Both their abilities and emotional performances were beginning to move away from that of the habit of beasts and transform into intelligent species.

If they had left their development alone, over time, the New Rock Tribe would probably have had the opportunity to unify all the Subterranean Mutants.

When it came to the Germinal leader to speak, he did not forget what Han Xiao had told him and transmitted the meaning of surrendering instead of fighting, as well as the basic information about the universe.

However, not only was Sulu-Sulu not afraid after he had finished talking, he was even enraged. "This is our homeland; we will definitely not leave!"

The news brought by the Germinal leader far outstripped Sulu-Sulu's expectations. However, their New Rock Tribe had already developed a sort of consciousness toward their homeland. In the face of a mass slaughter, he chose to resist.

Within the mental network, the members of the New Rock Tribe displayed their unity toward the enemy. This gave the Germinal Tribe a shock; they did not understand why the New Rock Tribe members would flare up so because they still did not understand the concept of hate.

"Emissary of Black Star, I thank you for your kind intentions, but we've decided to resist to the end!" Sulu-Sulu's attitude was firm.

In this matter, Han Xiao's self-acclaimed role played a part. To the Mutants, he was on the good side, there to save them from the evil clutches of the Sunils. As the Emissary of Black Star, the Germinal Tribe was responsible for salvation and had taken it as the mission of their tribe. Thus, Sulu-Sulu did not make things difficult for the Germinal Tribe but rather just sent them away from the New Rock Tribe.

Returning to the temporary camp, the Germinal leader recounted the New Rock Tribe's lack of intention to surrender.

Herlous had no choice then but to lead the army against the New Rock Tribe. Thirty to forty million enemies was a huge number, almost a hundred times the number of their current forces.

Yet another battle happened. The Sunil soldiers and players had long repeated this till they were numb. The difference was that, for this battle, the opposition of New Rock Tribe was fiercer than all the previous tribes.

...

Tuk tuk tuk!

Hot steel punched through the exoskeletons of the Subterranean Mutants. Blood splashed like blooming red flowers as countless Subterranean Mutants fell on the onslaught. However, the members of the New Rock Tribe seemed as though they were endless, like the tide rushing in.

There was a small team of Sunils responsible for this line of defense. Their fingers were tightly wrapped around the trigger, emptying box after box of ammunition at top speed without caring if their barrels overheated. The ground below them was full of empty metal casings.

Just at this point, an elite Subterranean Mutant, two or three times larger than the average, appeared in the area this team was responsible for. It waved the antennae on its head, and a wave of mental pressure quickly crossed the distance, ignoring the protection of the soldiers' armor, directly piercing their brains.

"Argh!"

A number of the Sunil soldiers felt as though their brains had been cut with thousands of knives. Blood sprayed from their every orifice, and they felt their vision spin and their bodies lose control. The defensive firepower stopped immediately.

The result was fatal.

The Subterranean Mutants that acted as the vanguard immediately rushed into this line of defense, swamping the team. Their tails and mouth caused dazzling sparks to appear as they clashed with the armor, and the durable armor was quickly ripped apart.

Swoosh!

A dazzling half-moon-shaped razor swept across suddenly, dismembering hundreds of the mutants in half.

Dragging his ten-meter-long Battleship Slicing Blade, Herlous approached the scene quickly and began to force the attackers back, resolving the dangerous situation.

The original team had been almost decimated by the mutants, but reinforcements quickly came up to replace those fallen.

Herlous wiped the blood and sweat from his face, but he had no time to rest. Just as he was about to return to his original position, he subconsciously looked down at the fallen soldiers. Their armor was riddled with wounds, and the soldiers were mostly ripped open, a mockery of their previous forms.

A glance, and Herlous found someone very familiar. His footsteps slowed down, and he looked carefully.

The soldier was covered with blood, his eyes wide and dagger clenched within his hands. He had pierced into one of the mutant bodies, as if he had died together with them. However, his face looked a bit immature.

Herlous suddenly recalled that this deceased soldier had been one of the neighbors back when he was running his bar in the city. His name seemed to be... Lana.

To think that this child would also choose to enlist.

The memories bubbled up like boiling water. Herlous twitched and ruthlessly removed all excess emotions, bellowing as he rushed back into the fray.

...

The first attack from the Subterranean Mutants was finally repelled.

The scale of the New Rock Tribe was too large, and the enemies were endless. Even if a large number of them were slaughtered, the New Rock Tribe did not choose to escape like the other nests but got even more violent, unafraid of death.

The tactics used by the New Rock Tribe varied and took full advantage of them being underground. This was their home field, and they could dig tunnels from above or at the bottom of the underground, directly entering the enemy camp. Through their mental network, the cooperation of the New Rock Tribe was seamless and difficult to predict.

The casualties on the Sunils' side continued to rise, and even the players died two or three times each. Everyone was exhausted, and Herlous finally decided to make a tactical retreat, returning to their temporary camps.

However, the New Rock Tribe members pursued them all the way, attacking the campsite directly. Herlous led the army to resist for a period of time but was finally unable to withstand the pressure and had to retreat to the surface. They had been forced out of the underground by the New Rock Tribe.

The sun was scorching overhead, and only after they had left the underground did the New Rock Tribe finally stop pursuing. The Subterranean Mutants hated the sun, and many of them were sunburned, so they did not rush to the surface, returning to their nest instead.

The New Rock Tribe had forced the attackers to retreat, and the casualties on both sides were exaggerated.

Because they retreated in a hurry, they did not even manage to retrieve most of their comrades' corpses. Herlous was in a sullen mood, allowing the troops to rest while they counted the casualties. He then contacted Han Xiao, reporting the situation on his side.

"You've been repelled by them?" Han Xiao had a strange look on his face.

"The number of enemies was overwhelming, and we can only slowly clear out their nest by fighting them. However, our casualties will be incalculable..." Herlous gritted his teeth. "Black Star, I wish to utilize the biochemical weapons, preventing more casualties."

"See to it yourself." Han Xiao shook his head before cutting off the communication.

Herlous took a deep breath. In his memory floated up the corpse of the young soldier, and he no longer hesitated.

Calling an officer from the Logistics Unit, he gazed at the other party's blood-covered face and said, "Deploy someone to throw in all the biochemical weapons. Execute it immediately!"

"Understood!" The officer gave a military salute without hesitation.

...

The people of the New Rock Tribe also dragged their exhausted bodies back to the nest and cleared up the battlefield. They stacked up the corpses of their comrades, forming a small hill.

Within the mental network, the tribe members discussed nonstop. The previous battle had a great impact on them, and with the deaths of multiple members, it allowed them to feel even more fear, anger, and desire for revenge. However, they cheered at the same time for their victory as they had managed to repel the enemies and successfully defend their homeland.

Although they had suffered heavy casualties, Sulu-Sulu was full of fighting spirit. His ancestors had passed down the notion that even while the enemy had retreated, they could still attack anytime. If they wished to win, they had to take down the enemy's 'nest'.

The Subterranean Mutants then collected the corpses of the Sunil soldiers. An old Subterranean Mutant slowly hobbled out, and the others bowed in greeting.

This Subterranean Mutant was an outlier in the New Rock Tribe, and it could retrieve the memories of the dead. In the entire New Rock Tribe, only this mutant possessed that ability.

If Han Xiao was present, he would have realized that this mutant was a naturally awakened Esper.

The tentacles on its head touched the heads of the Sunil soldiers one by one, and various memory fragments flashed. It quickly organized the information that it wanted and then shared the memory image in the mental network.

It was a picture of Forest City as well as a map of the Planet Sunil.

"The nest of the surface dwellers is on the surface."

"What a weird nest."

"The enemies live on the surface. How do we get to them?"

The members of the New Rock Tribe started to debate.

At this moment, a thick fog appeared on the edge of the lair and spread.

Chapter 626: Victory

Ten or so days later, the expedition force returned to Nest No. 77 again, and the entire tribe had become a region of death with the corpses of Subterranean Mutants littering the underground world.

Even the hardened Sunil soldiers could not help but take deep breaths upon witnessing the hellish scene before them. Many players felt their hearts tremble and could not help but feel pity.

With a solemn mood, Herlous instructed the mining of the Prophecy Stones to begin and all the corpses to be burnt.

They also began searching for the corpses of their deceased brothers.

After cleaning up the New Rock Tribe, the expedition mission did not meet with any further trouble. They continued to battle and persuade the other tribes with little to no trouble.

After a long period of battling, the final Subterranean Mutant tribe surrendered and Herlous returned to Forest City.

...

Outside Forest City, almost all the Sunils had left the city, and they waited in the rain to receive the victorious return of the troops.

Hu!

Ten or so spaceships flew over from afar and landed outside the city.

As the hatch of the spaceship opened, all the Sunil soldiers disembarked from the spaceship wearing their ordinary uniform with fatigue all over their faces. The players were in a better state, and they still looked pretty energetic.

Herlous stepped out of the spaceship and led the troops toward the crowd.

"Hero!"

All of a sudden, the Sunils broke out into a deafening cheer and rushed forward to surround the returning warriors. Their faces were full of agitation, excitement, and gratitude as they welcomed the return of the victorious troops.

Herlous was surrounded by countless individuals, and wherever he looked, he could see gratitude and reverence in their eyes.

The Sunils knew that the Black Star Army had only been willing to help them because of Herlous. In the eyes of all the Sunils, Herlous' status already exceeded that of the rest; he was the hero and idol of every Sunil.

The crowd cheered loudly and were filled with endless praise toward the expedition forces, including the players.

More accurately speaking, the Sunils were extremely grateful toward the Black Star Army and Han Xiao was like a messiah to them. The prestige of the Black Star Army was also at its peak.

"We are truly extremely grateful to all of you."

"All of you have saved Sunil!"

"Black Star Army, you are our benefactors."

The Sunils surrounded the players and showered them with words of gratitude.

Many of the players were taken aback and had an inexplicable sense of accomplishment in their hearts. The mission this time was truly a meaningful one, and their collective effort had changed the fates of the Sunils.

This sense of accomplishment was truly a different experience for many. They felt both satisfied and enriched. This was something completely unrelated to benefits; it was a sense of satisfaction on a spiritual level.

Many of the young soldiers rejoined their families, and the joy of their families wiped away the fatigue of the soldiers, putting a bright smile on all of their faces.

Parents received their children, wives received their husbands, and children received their fathers.

This warm scene unfolded all around.

Every day, the families of the soldiers lived in fear—fear that they would one day receive a notice of death. Now, everything had ended, and there would not be any more war sacrifices.

There was no need to despair or fear. A beautiful tomorrow awaited them.

The darkness had gone, and the Sunils could see the light.

The day for peace and tranquility had finally arrived.

Upon looking at the smiling faces of their people, all the Sunil soldiers felt comfort. Everything that they had done for their people and family was worth it.

However, not everyone was happy.

With a heavy mood and expression, the officers handed the ashes of the deceased soldiers back to their families.

There were some who were filled with disbelief, others argued loudly, and some cried as they hugged the box of ash.

The cries of these families were a stark contrast to the cheering crowd. The light shower also seemed slightly depressing, and the temperature of the morning seemed to have fallen a bit.

Lana's parents hugged onto his box of ashes and knelt on the ground as though they had lost their souls.

As Herlous saw such a scene, he went forward to help Lana's parents up and softly said, "He was a truly exemplary man."

Lana's parents looked at him and did not say a word.

Upon seeing this, Herlous knew that any words of consolation would be useless. He turned around and walked away silently with his fists clenched tight. The Sunils had been through far too many life and death separations. Thankfully, this would be the last time.

Looking up, Herlous saw Han Xiao standing outside of the crowd with the officers of the army and walked over toward him.

Upon seeing Herlous approaching, Han Xiao said, "It's finally ended. Only the final step is required for this mission to be completed."

Herlous looked at Han Xiao and suddenly bowed deeply. "I thank you on behalf of the entire Sunil race."

"You don't need to have such a big reaction. I have only fulfilled my promise to you," Han Xiao said helplessly and raised his arm out to help Herlous up. However, Herlous refused to budge.

"No, let me finish."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao allowed Herlous to continue bowing.

Herlous then said slowly, "Your name shall be recorded in the history books of our Sunil race. You are not only the benefactor of our Sunil race but also my benefactor...

"In my eyes, this isn't just a promise, transaction, or employment. This is a kindness that I will never be able to repay.

"Your Excellency Black Star, from today onward, I am willing to be your blade and follow you to the ends of the universe."

As those words sounded, all the officers looked at Herlous with many different expressions.

Is he pledging loyalty to me? Han Xiao fell silent for a while before nodding. "Alright."

Only then did Herlous get up and reveal a smile.

"The price of peace is always filled with blood." Ginette shook her head.

"I hope that the Sunil race will always remember this war. I hope that all of them will remember what kind of violence we so-called heroes have committed," Herlous lamented.

"This is natural selection. Every civilization will eventually become demons as they carry history on their backs and carry on their journey," Han Xiao said casually before looking to the side. The upper echelons of the Sunils walked over, and this time, it was not Otis who spoke to him but the leader of the Sunils.

The Sunil leader personally expressed his gratitude, and Han Xiao replied appropriately.

After conversing for a while, the Sunil leader then expressed that the employment would only be considered complete when all the Subterranean Mutants were migrated off the planet.

After seeing the departure of the Sunil upper echelons, Sylvia smacked Herlous on the back and angrily said, "These fellows are so annoying."

Herlous did not disagree. "I also hate politicians."

At this moment, Feidin said, "Black Star, about the migration..."

Just when Han Xiao was about to reply, his communicator rang. Upon glancing at his communicator, he said with a chuckle, "Right on time."

The next moment, their vision turned dark, and a gigantic shadow covered all of them.

The Sunils and players all raised their heads in astonishment.

More than a hundred large cargo spaceships landed from the sky and covered the sun.

"I called the movers."

Han Xiao let out a long breath and smiled.

He had borrowed a large batch of transportation spaceships from the two financial groups to transport all the Subterranean Mutants. As long as these spaceships made a few trips, they would be able to transport all the mutants and Prophecy Stones to a designated uninhabited planet. Since the Subterranean Mutants consumed rocks for their survival, it was pretty easy to find a suitable planet for them.

The players had already been informed about the migration plan, and upon seeing the arrival so the spaceships, many of the players could not help but become excited.

"That should be the migration fleet, right?"

"Helping a population of billions migrate. What a spectacular sight."

"The Subterranean Mutants won't be exterminated. Black Star didn't disappoint me."

Upon witnessing their own faction putting on such a spectacular display, all the players welled up with a sense of pride and collective honor. At the same time, many players agreed with the decision of Black Star to relocate the Subterranean Mutants.

After a long period of battle and witnessing so many tragedies, the players felt that the Subterranean Mutants were the weak party.

Pitying the weak was a habit, and from the moment the players took pity on the Subterranean Mutants, they also began to agree with the plan to migrate. The outcome of this choice was to create a greater sense of belonging toward the Black Star Army.

Han Xiao was extremely clear of this point, and he also intended to make use of their compassion to leave a deep impression in the hearts of the players and increase their sense of belonging to the faction.

The outcome seemed pretty good.

By the side, Feidin also revealed a smile. He felt that this was the best way to resolve the problem for both parties.

Looking at Han Xiao's back, Feidin was deep in thought.

His strength had grown rapidly, and he could already single handedly suppress Chen Xing who was inside of him. Furthermore, his conflict with Chen Xing had already been resolved, which meant that he no longer needed the help of the Black Star Army.

He had originally intended to find a time to say goodbye, but at this moment, he felt that perhaps staying in the Black Star Army would not be a bad choice.

Chapter 627: Black Spirit Race

Galactic migration was a huge project.

All the surrendered Subterranean Mutants brought their Prophecy Stones onto the spaceships. Without these Prophecy Stones, even if Planet Sunil had a few small mines left, it was impossible for a large-scale Psychic Current to form again.

In other words, the calamity was over, and this planet was now suitable for the Sunils to live on.

The amount of resources that the Black Star Army could mobilize had awed the upper echelons of Sunil and made them even more respectful. Upon witnessing the arrival of the transport fleet, they did not dare delay any further and took the initiative to process the payment to the Mercenary Alliance.

Han Xiao received a notification to inform him of the funds entering his account. At the same time, the interface also notified him of the completion of the mission.

[Sunil Rescue Operation: Large Scale Employment Mission]. A large sum was deposited into your account to cover some of the transportation cost. Completing a Large-Scale Employment Mission alone has given the Black Star Army a shiny battle record and increased your credibility rating greatly. The Mercenary Alliance has once again revised their rating of the Black Star Army.

Summary: A renowned super-large army, Floating Dragon's Field Team. Mainly operates within the Garton Star System and is an iconic mercenary group in the Garton Star System. Has a few hundred thousand undying mercenaries with an average strength of Grade C. The Black Star Army has plenty of connections in the mercenary world, a solid financial foundation, and has bases on Planet Sunil, Planet Aquamarine, and Planet Golden Gate. To date, the mercenary group has maintained an extremely high completion rate and has a good reputation. This mercenary group is one worthy of trust.

Army Commander Black Star has the nickname of 'Undying Body' and 'DarkStar Destroyer'. Black Star also has a good relationship with a few civilizations and is the holder of Godora's Golden Gal Badge.

The upgrade of his summary also indicated an upgrade in his status. The happiest bunch about this upgraded reputation had got to be the players, and they all felt a great sense of accomplishment.

Apart from the official employment mission, the Grade A Sunil Mission [Eliminate Subterranean Mutants] had also been completed. The players' pockets were full of rewards, and their faces were full of smiles.

This time, Han Xiao did not pursue the highest mission rating and got a [Good] rating. According to the details of the mission, exterminating the mutant race would give him the highest rating. However, the reward of the mission could not be compared to the future benefits that migrating the mutants could bring him. Thus, Han Xiao chose the option that brought him greater benefits.

Han Xiao did not need this little mission reward anyway. In any case, the experience points that the players received from the mission would eventually become their spending power. All Han Xiao needed to do was harvest them again.

However, the Grade A mission gave him an unexpected reward, a new dungeon.

[Underground Subterranean Mutant War].

A new dungeon? Not bad. Han Xiao's eyes lit up. He had accumulated a few dungeons, but because the players' levels weren't high enough, he did not release them all. However, he would be able to make use of all the dungeons eventually as the players increased their levels.

Over the next few days, Han Xiao stayed behind on Planet Sunil to oversee the transportation of the Subterranean Mutants.

After the end of the employment, he also terminated the Army Assembly.

A portion of the players remained on Planet Sunil. While the employment mission was over, Planet Sunil still had tons to do, and there was plenty of benefits to be gained. Base No. 3 formed the faction headquarters on Planet Sunil, and the missions on Planet Sunil could groom the players as well.

With the crisis of Planet Sunil resolved, the Sunil warriors no longer had to take any more risks on the outside. Sehrinde and the other Sunil mercenaries wanted to return to their homeland and quit being mercenaries. As such, they all approached Han Xiao and requested to leave. All of them felt extremely guilty and felt that they had let Black Star down.

Han Xiao had already predicted such a situation and had prepared a win-win situation for both parties. He allowed Sehrinde and the others to remain on Planet Sunil without the need to go out on missions and train up the mercenaries in Base No. 3 instead.

All the Sunil warriors accepted this proposition. They truly wished to do something for Black Star to repay his kindness. Since there was no danger for them when grooming the newbies on their home planet, Sehrinde and the others no longer mentioned the matter of leaving.

Finally, the last cargo spaceship set off, and Han Xiao left together with the Black Star Army. Countless Sunils looked up into the sky to send the Black Star Army off.

...

The Subterranean Mutants were all migrated to some uninhabited planet suitable for their kind, and Han Xiao followed the cargo ships to monitor the situation.

Because all the Subterranean Mutant tribes were reorganized, they were no longer separated by distance like before. Instead, the development of the tribes was sped up, and the tribes were mixed together to live together. They had skipped an entire phase, and all the various tribes were now united.

From the angle of a civilization's development, this was a truly frightening start.

Because the Germinal leader was Black Star's emissary and the one who had spread the knowledge that Han Xiao had bestowed onto him, the Germinal leader became the undisputed leader of the Subterranean Mutants.

To the members of the Germinal Tribe, Black Star was like a divine being, like a messiah, to them. The Germinal Tribe's respect of Han Xiao was spread to the hearts of all the Subterranean Mutants. After they settled down in their new residences, the Subterranean Mutants treated Han Xiao as a figure to worship.

Because of the uniqueness of the mental connection, culture could spread at an unbelievable rate, and all the mutants began to create names for themselves.

When Han Xiao arrived, the Germinal Tribe were leading the Subterranean Mutants to construct a gigantic nest. Han Xiao was greeted with an extremely warm welcome when he arrived, with the leader of the Germinal Tribe coming out to receive him personally.

"This is our new home." The Germinal leader dashed into the new nest excitedly like a little child running after candy.

"Very good. This planet shall be your land from now on." Han Xiao nodded with a smile. "You are a new civilization and shouldn't be called Subterranean Mutants anymore."

"Are you going to give us a new name?" the Germinal Tribe leader asked excitedly.

"No, this is your own right."

After a simple conversation, Han Xiao left the planet and did not interfere with the development of the Subterranean Mutants. They were still in their infant stage, and Han Xiao planned to let the Subterranean Mutants develop naturally.

His spaceship then left the planet, and a new notification popped up on his interface.

You have received a new Legendary Point.

Star System Legendary Point (Garton Star System): Savior of a Race—You saved a large race and prevented them from facing the fate of extermination, helping them form a new civilization. This is a noble action, and this incident will be spread across the Garton Star System. Many organizations will be friendlier toward you.

Han Xiao was truly surprised. He had never expected to have such a reward.

Furthermore, this was not the only notification

+10,000 Black Spirit Race Faction Favorability

Current Relationship: Worship

Black Spirit Race?

Han Xiao was taken aback for a moment before coming to a realization. The Subterranean Mutants must have given themselves an official name. However, why did the Black Spirit Race sound as though it was related to his nickname?

He did not understand his position in the hearts of the Subterranean Mutants. They had made use of 'Black Star' as reference and named themselves the Black Spirit Race.

Han Xiao immediately became interested.

Interesting, I wonder what kind of civilization the Subterranean Mutants will develop into.

Smiling, Han Xiao piloted the Blacklight Stealth and disappeared into the sky.

...

The result of the migration was reported to the players, and after seeing the Subterranean Mutants begin their new life, many of the players heaved sighs of relief. At the same time, they could not help but feel proud for being a part of the Black Star Army.

On the forums, the Sunil incident became the hottest topic of discussion. The players enjoyed the feeling of changing the fate of an entire race and becoming saviors. Their sense of belonging toward the faction also increased greatly as a result of this incident.

On Planet Sunil, the Sunils were extremely grateful to the Black Star Army, and people went to visit Base No. 3 every day.

Sehrinde and the other 'retired' mercenaries set up an official training camp in Base No. 3 and began to accept disciples to train.

The training camp was an avenue to provide a never-ending stream of soldiers for the army. While the training camp was only starting out, it was filled with great potential. As long as the Sunils continued to reproduce normally, there would definitely be some who were willing to become mercenaries.

It could be said that as the Sunils developed, the benefits of Base No.3 would also increase. The prosperity of both parties was closely related.

After the Sunil mission, the development of the Black Star Army in the Garton Star System was finally on track.

The players who stayed behind on Planet Aquamarine gradually began to complete the test.

Finally, apart from a few new players who joined the game, all the players on Planet Aquamarine had entered the galaxy and become members of the Black Star Army. The size of the Black Star Army had also reached the one million mark.

Even among large mercenary groups, such a number was extremely rare.

The Black Star Army wanted to develop their foundations firmly in the Garton Star System and had begun to expand into many different businesses and construct new bases. Apart from trying to monopolize the mercenary market of the entire Garton Star System, Han Xiao's hands had also stretched out into the nearby Star Systems. His connections provided him with great aid, and the speed of their development astounded Godora.

Han Xiao would occasionally personally lead a couple of high difficulty employment missions or would find some planets with benefits to be reaped with his familiarity of the storyline. Every now and then, he would take on a large-scale employment mission as the Main Storyline Mission to build cohesiveness among the players.

The Black Star Army grew steadily without any outside force interfering with their development. There was almost no risk involved, and everything went according to Han Xiao's plan.

In the blink of an eye, two years passed.

Chapter 628: Two Years Later

Including Godora, there were six Star System level civilizations that wanted to gain control over the Hyde Star System, which was located in the Colton Star Cluster. Their forces were deployed to the respective region that they had control over, and skirmishes were extremely common.

Outside the region controlled by the armies of these six civilizations, the Hyde Star System had many planets that served as a transit station for the galactic travel agencies. Because the territorial borders of the Hyde Star System were blurred, these transit stations became gray regions where dragons and snakes mingled. Not only were there scrap pickers, pirates, and wanted criminals, even the officers of the armies would occasionally visit these transit stations for leisure.

Planet Orange Transit Station was such a gray area, and a group of players were currently operating in this district.

Hao Tian, Sleepy Winter, Twinkle Fried Rice, and the others were walking down the bustling streets. Of the ten or so players in the group, a portion of them were the pro players of Club Long Sky, and the others were the players of the club. Frenzied Sword, together with his teammates, were currently working together with Long Sky.

Both parties had accepted the same Hidden Chain Mission, and the final portion of the mission was located on Planet Orange Transit Station. Hao Tian and Frenzied Sword had immediately clicked, and thus, both the parties traveled together.

Because of Frenzied Sword's spectacular performance in the first Pro League, Club Rivervale had built a new team with Frenzied Sword as the core. The majority of Frenzied Sword's teammates were newbies, and they were currently warming up to each other.

Preparations for the second Pro League had already started, and it was a hot topic at the moment. Galaxy Times had revealed that there would be changes to the tournament format this time, and all the teams were currently preparing for the Pro League.

More than a year ago, the players of the other novice planets had also stepped into the galaxy and hit the level limit of the current version, level 90. Their skills, equipment, talents, and special tools were the main focus for all the players.

Both Long Sky and Rivervale worked together because they were eyeing the reward for this hidden mission.

As the core of the team, Frenzied Sword felt immense pressure and wanted to obtain good results to prove himself. He did not wish to disappoint the club and would not let go of any opportunities.

"Captain, the person we are looking for is on this planet, but how should we find him?" Evil Sword asked Frenzied Sword.

Evil Sword was Frenzied Sword's teammate and an extremely talented newcomer. In the entire Rivervale team, only Evil Sword's skill had caught his eye, barely making him Frenzied Sword's assistant. As for his other teammates, they were no more than ordinary players who did not make mistakes to Frenzied Sword.

"The last phase of the mission will definitely be extremely difficult. The mission hint asked us to find clues on our own. According to my experience, the entertainment centers of these gray districts are the go-to places for information. We can start there," Frenzied Sword said with a deep voice.

At this moment, the captain of Long Sky, Hao Tian, said, "We can find the clues later. We should first worry about our safety."

Upon hearing that, the players began to look around, only to see groups of pedestrians dressed in tattered battle suits staring at them greedily. Their gazes were fixed on the exquisite battle suits and weapons of the players and seemed intent on snatching them.

The majority of the pedestrians around them had red colored names, and the others had neutral yellow names. Not a single green could be found.

"Pirates or scavengers?"

Everyone remained calm. As members of the Black Star Army, they had killed an uncountable number of galactic pirates over the past two years.

Yellow Mechanical Force covered Frenzied Sword's body, and his helmet appeared to cover his head. Following which, his armor began unfolding with the various components of the armor appearing to form heavy armor that looked like a luxurious knight's armor.

This was weakened Commander Class armor called [Mountain]. It was a pink grade equipment that the guild had obtained after paying a sky-high price to Han Xiao to custom make. With the players' current level, [Mountain] was the best equipment currently available.

He took off the long box on his back and activated it with his Mechanical Force. The box rapidly changed shape and transformed into a long, heavy close combat weapon that had both the blade of an axe and a cannon barrel. This was a modified Strike Cannon, and it was almost half the size of a person.

All the other players entered their battle mode with a myriad of different weapons. Even the weakest piece of equipment in the group was purple grade. The function of a club guild was to serve the professional players, and thus, it was impossible for these professional players to be lacking in equipment. All their equipment was of the highest tier among the players currently.

The atmosphere grew tense and both parties were locked in a standoff.

Just when the pirates were about to take action, one of the members suddenly cried out, "Stop! Don't move! They're Black Star's men!"

The moment the words sounded, the menacing gaze of the pirates disappeared, and their expressions drastically changed. A second ago, they had wanted to pounce forward, but the next moment, they had all retreated in fear with their eyes widened as they studied the equipment of the players carefully.

On a hidden location of the players' equipment, an insignia could be seen. The insignia was a black round gear with white borders and four straight lines extending away from the gear to represent light beams. It was like a black star that was emanating light.

All the pirates understood what this insignia represented.

This was the insignia of the Black Star Army!

All the pirates revealed looks of horror and did not dare move.

Right at this moment, a deep voice sounded from the other end of the street.

"Humph, this place seems extremely lively."

Everyone turned around only to see a couple of Godoran officers walking over slowly with their cold gazes fixed on the pirates.

In the player's vision, the only green that they could see came from the sudden appearance of the Godora officers.

The officer in the lead cracked his neck and said with a chilly tone, "Our friends from the Black Star Army, do you need any help?"

The previously ferocious pirates were immediately reduced to trembling little rabbits. In the Hyde Star System, there was an unspoken rule that must not be broken. They should never attack the officers of the six civilizations. If not, the army would not mind sweeping through the gray area.

The entire Colton Star Cluster knew that the Black Star Army and Godora were allies. These pirates had kicked a steel plate that they could not afford to provoke and were truly unlucky.

"Run!"

The pirates immediately scattered in all different directions.

The players seemed to be extremely used to such a scene and put their weapons away without bothering to chase after those small fries.

Upon seeing this scene, the Godoran officers did not take action. They nodded toward the players before turning around to take their leave. Their intention was very simple. They had just gone over to help because they saw members of the Black Star Army.

Both the camps were allies, and Black Star was the recipient of the Golden Gal Badge. All members of the Black Star Army would be able to gain extra help from the Godorans, and the Black Star Networking Group that the players joked about gradually became a reality.

...

After running for a long while, two space pirates only dared stop after making sure that no one was giving chase. They placed their hands on their knees and bent forward while panting heavily.

"Hu... I thought that we would be dead for sure. Thankfully, they didn't give chase," the shorter pirate said.

The taller pirate nodded in agreement with a face full of relief as though he had just escaped death.

In the few Star Systems around the Garton Star System, apart from Star System level civilizations, no organization was willing to provoke the Black Star Army.

"Thankfully, we are only a small gang without any bounties. If not, we would be in huge trouble," the shorter pirate said while panting heavily.

"We don't even have the right to be wanted criminals." The taller pirate laughed bitterly and did not know whether he should be happy or sad.

There was a saying among the pirates—they would rather meet the Dragon Emperor than meet Black Star!

One of the reasons for the swift uprising of the Black Star Army was because they took on the role of bounty hunters. All the galactic pirate groups around the Garton Star System had become the prey for the Black Star Army. These pirate groups had been wiped out, and all their battleships had been captured. The Black Star Army had at least four hundred battleships that had been snatched in this manner.

The pirates in the neighboring Star Systems had felt threatened, and a portion of them had joined hands to assassinate Black Star for their own survival. However, they had ended up falling into an ambush with over a million mercenaries being sent into battle. In the end, those allied pirates had ended up being completely wiped out.

While many infamous pirates had been captured, the majority of these pirates had been hidden by Black Star with only a small portion being exchanged for their bounties. These pirates that were taken out by Black Star had been tortured by Black Star to the point they did not even seem like humans.

After this piece of news was spread, many pirates trembled in fear and all felt that Black Star had some sick fetish toward pirates. Thus, Black Star immediately seemed a hundred times more ferocious in their eyes, causing the saying that they would rather meet the Dragon Emperor than Black Star to spread.

Dragon Emperor Ames was on neutral ground, but her field team had something against galactic pirates. Thus, they would rather land in Ames' hands than end up being in Black Star's hands.

As such, the pirates in the Star Systems surrounding the Garton Star System all escaped, and the security of these few Star Systems became extremely good. Currently, there were only a few small, puny galactic pirate groups left behind.

"Who would have thought that the members of the Black Star Army would appear here? Could it be that the Black Star Army think that it isn't enough to monopolize the jobs in the Garton Star System and want to expand into Hyde?"

"Who knows? However, that isn't impossible. In the few neighboring Star Systems, apart from the few Star System level civilizations, which other organization dares provoke the Black Star Army? They've already monopolized this region."

After catching their breath for a while, both of them continued running.

...

Frenzied Sword and Hao Tian were currently searching for clues in the transit station. After a few hours, they finally managed to piece together the clue for the last phase of the mission.

All of them came to a deserted maintenance workshop, and their target was a crippled maintenance worker. He had lost both his arms and replaced them with prosthetic limbs. He was currently repairing a badly damaged communicator and had an ordinary aura.

However, according to the information that the players received from the Detect skill, this maintenance worker called Ronaldo was 'Fatally Dangerous'.

Hao Tian and Frenzied Sword looked at each other and pushed Sleepy Winter into the workshop in unison. Sleepy Winter had the highest Charm stat among them and was the most suitable to talk to NPCs.

Sleepy Winter took out the mission item, handed it over, and respectfully said, "Hello, someone requested that we hand this over to you."

They had accepted a hidden mission that required them to hand this mission item over to Ronaldo. The mission item was a letter.

Upon hearing that, Ronaldo looked up and glanced at the crowd. He then placed the machine in his hands down before calmly asking, "Who are all of you?"

"We are from the Black Star Army."

"Black Star Army‽" Ronaldo's gaze flickered, and he said in a deep voice, "I've heard of you guys before. It's said that Black Star is an extremely powerful Mechanic. It's truly a pity. If it was a year ago and both my arms were still around, I would have wanted to exchange pointers with him."

Frenzied Sword and the others were shocked.

Han Xiao was a Grade A Super, and if the person before them dared say exchange pointers, he should be a Grade A Super as well. This hidden mission was truly unfathomable.

"Don't be in a rush to leave. Let me see what's written."

Ronaldo lowered his head and opened the letter that was filled with secret codes. He lived in seclusion due to some reason and could only use such a method to transmit information.

All the players waited for a moment, and Ronaldo sighed after reading the letter.

"These are truly turbulent times. A new storm is about to arrive. Sigh, please tell your employer that I am in seclusion and will not accept any hires. I only wish to stay here silently; the tremors of the Shattered Star Ring shall not affect me anymore."

The final mission objective on their interface changed to 'report back to their employer', and they would be able to accept the mission reward at any time. However, these players did not leave immediately as they were extremely sensitive to hidden storylines. Upon hearing Ronaldo's words, they knew that there was information to be dug up.

"I wonder, what do you mean by a storm?" Sleepy Winter asked.

Ronaldo looked at him and perhaps found Sleepy Winter to be more pleasant to the eyes. "Have you guys not noticed the hidden currents in the Shattered Star Ring over the past year or two? The seven Star Cluster level civilizations' actions have been weird; this is the signal of a storm. A whirlpool is gradually forming and is only in its infancy. When this whirlpool surfaces, the entire Shattered Star Ring will be dragged in, and not a single organization will be able to avoid the storm."

Everyone was completely puzzled. They had only visited the few Star Systems around the Garton Star System and did not understand much about the storm in the Shattered Star Ring. After all, their area of operation was not large enough.

There were some players who wanted to explore new maps and visit other Star Clusters. However, the effort that they put in and rewards they received usually did not match. They could only view the scenery most of the time and make a wasted trip.

The galaxy was extremely large, and just the Shattered Star Ring alone was already enormous. Trying to find a mission alone was akin to finding a needle in a haystack. On the contrary, the Black Star Army had numerous missions for them to choose from, and they would definitely have returns. Thus, their target was extremely obvious.

Sleepy Winter continued asking, and Ronaldo replied, "No one knows the target of these Star Cluster level civilizations, but the storm definitely isn't a coincidence. I think that there must be a powerful organization directing the changes in the Shattered Star Ring.

"Powerful organization? Is it the three Universal Civilizations that have only appeared in the background, or is it someone else?" Everyone guessed to themselves.

The players did not know about the Tyrant's gathering and naturally did not know what was going on behind the scenes. However, this did not stop Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, and the others from guessing that this was related to the storyline of the future version.

After all, this was not the first time. Black Star had also revealed Version 2.0's Mutation Disaster during Version 1.0.

Having clues of the future version ahead of time could provide them with a huge advantage.

Right at this moment, Ronaldo seemed to have thought of something and said, "Right, all of you are Black Star's subordinates. Give something to him for me."

Everyone was stunned for a moment before nodding. This was obviously a new mission.

Following which, Ronaldo took a pen and paper to write a long list of names before handing it over to the players.

Sleepy Winter received the piece of paper, and the interface notified him that he received a copy of [List of Names].

This time, Frenzied Sword could not help but ask, "What is this?"

"This is a list..." Ronaldo said with a deep voice. As though he thought about a terrible memory, he grabbed the position of his arm, and a trace of anger and fear flashed past his eyes. "A list of targets."

"Er, why do you want us to pass this to Black Star?"

"Because... he is on the list!"

Chapter 629: Mysterious Killer

Who had put Black Star as their hunting target?

A look of surprise appeared on Frenzied Sword's face.

The expression of everyone present turned weird. Black Star was the leader of their faction, and upon hearing that someone was going to deal with him, the group inexplicably felt some hatred toward the other party.

Hao Tian's eyes gleamed, and he communicated to them through the channel. "We might have picked up on a hidden storyline. Sleepy, continue asking. Try to trigger more of the storyline."

Sleepy Winter nodded. "Black Star is our leader; we will definitely pass this list on to him. However, we would like to know more about this. Could you tell us more about the list itself?"

"The people on this list are all well-known Supers around the Shattered Star Ring," Ronaldo said in a deep tone. "None of them are ordinary Grade A Supers, either having powerful influences or solo powers with a strong personal force. The goal of those who released this list is to kill or capture these strong Supers. As far as I know, there are already some people on the list who have gone missing."

"Who are the people in charge of pursuing those on the list?" Sleepy Winter took the chance to continue down this lead.

"It seems to be a mysterious organization. I don't know their origin and just refer to them as 'Hunters'. They have captured a few of the stronger Supers on the list. I've only met with them once. At that time, I chanced upon two of the hunters, and their strengths were perversely strong, probably having the level of Grade A+."

A sense of heaviness passed through Ronaldo's eyes as he added, "My hands were broken by one of them."

"So, you were their target as well?"

"Nope." Ronaldo shook his head.

Sleepy Winter paused, suspicion filling his face as he asked, "Then why..."

Ronaldo cut in as he leisurely explained, "I was an outsider that was implicated. Hence, I got off with only my arms being broken."

After pausing for a while, he said, "I have a friend who's also a Calamity Grade Super. He was the actual target they were looking for on the list. He runs an armed organization in the Skywalker Star System, which has a close relationship with the Hutt Civilization.

"A year ago, while I was paying a visit to his headquarters, two of the hunters suddenly appeared. They killed their way into the headquarters, without anyone being able to stop them. Thus, I went to meet the enemy with my friend, but those two had overwhelming power, and we ended up being wiped.

"I managed to steal some of their information through their communicators during the battle, which was this incomplete list. Their target was my friend, and they captured him in the end, throwing me aside after giving me some serious injuries.

"I'm technically a Grade A Super, and you would think that they would capture me too, but they didn't even look at me before swaggering out. They seemed indifferent to non-targeted people."

Ronaldo laughed bitterly. "They did not look at me at all, which is why I managed to escape."

Everyone present was stupefied.

The goal of the hunters was to capture the strong, but they did not even bother taking along a Calamity Grade Super that could not retaliate. Was it because they had specific targets, or were their goals too lofty?

No matter what the case was, this group of mysterious hunters seemed unfathomable.

"This hidden storyline must not be a simple one," Frenzied Sword said within the team channel.

"While the hunters themselves are mysterious," Ronaldo said, "the missing people on the list cannot be hidden. This means that the hunters are continuously on the move. Please be sure to transfer the name list to Black Star. While I might not know him, the Black Star Mercenary Group has helped me, so I don't mind repaying my debt by reminding your leader."

He had also calculated that behind Black Star stood the Dragon Emperor, and they could probably handle the hunters. If Black Star really succeeded, he would not need to remain in hiding forever.

The reason for him being low key was because he feared that his name would one day appear on the hunters' list. Although he had only exchanged blows with them once, he was thoroughly afraid of their strength.

At this time, the interface of the players showed a notification.

You have triggered the Hidden Mission: [Mysterious Hunting List]!

They all glanced at each other, nodding in return.

In a random Star System of the Shattered Star Ring, a spaceship with visible signs of damage was moving at full speed, like a streamer, across the dark universe.

"Warning! Warning! Fuel reserves have fallen to the critical line. Exiting hyperdrive in one minute." The Artificial Intelligence issued a reminder.

"Dammit! Those two fellows will catch up at this rate!"

Bang!

Within the cockpit, Kernid desperately smashed the control panel, an anxious expression on his face.

He belonged to a humanoid race with darker complexion, with natural wrinkles on his skin. He wore a special rune armor combat suit that combined mechanical and magical techniques. The armor was filled with countless mysterious runes on the inside and outside, with dozens of enchants as well. It was equipped with hundreds of different magical combat means and was the most commonly used type for interstellar magicians.

However, this high-end rune armor was currently torn and ragged, covered in Kernid's own blood.

Kernid was the first official Grade A Super of a random civilization in the Star System, as well as an honorary member of the Hidden Red Robe Abbey. He was adept in magic and was named the Dark Purple Warlock, giving him high prestige. However, he was currently fleeing like never before.

And everything was because of the two enemies that had unexpectedly appeared.

While he was enjoying a paid vacation, exploring the interstellar regions, he chanced upon these two mysterious men, who attacked him without a single word.

Afterward, Kernid actually found out that he was not a match for the two of them and received heavy injuries.

Fortunately, he had kept a trump card, and managed to shake them away before boarding his spaceship and escaping. However, the two mysterious assailants continued chasing after him nonstop, causing him to be unable to stop.

The hyperdrive consumed his remaining fuel quickly, and the aircraft speed finally slowed down, exiting from hyperdrive and returning to normal flying speed.

"Drat!" Kernid had a face full of sweat, as he gripped his head tight.

Just as his voice sounded, the hum of magic waves passed through the many layers of the bulkhead. Kernid keenly captured the waves of magic through his senses, causing his expression to change greatly.

A bright blue ring was lit up around the abdomen of the spaceship, and the ring quickly expanded into a portal. A duo walked out leisurely from within the portal.

The two wore similar white overcoats without any embellishments. The material of the clothes seemed strange, gleaming dully, and was covered with countless enchantment inscriptions.

Both of them wore specially alloy masks to cover their faces. The man's mask resembled a bird's head, whereas the women's resembled a cat.

More than a dozen thick, ancient-looking books were seen floating around the man, all of which were open. They were filled with magic texts and glowing with colorful spell rays. The golden yellow inscriptions morphed into several circles, surrounding the man's body.

"The positioning is confirmed."

The man's tone was passive, and as he flicked his fingers, one of the pages turned up. The portal behind him then narrowed down to a point and disappeared. This man was a master of magic!

Suddenly, the bulkhead in front of the duo burst apart as tens of purple light beams arced out from Kernid, who was in the cockpit. The gorgeous purple lights pierced through the walls, striking the two uninvited guests.

Knowing their capabilities, he chose to attack first.

Boom!

Between the flashing lights and fire, the masked man changed his stance, which caused all the books to begin flipping at once. A blue magic circle covered him and the woman beside him, isolating them from all attacks. The purple arcs were deflected into space instead, unable to even touch them.

Kernid flew out of the gap, and his rune armor lit up, casting lights all around. Countless magical forces gathered around him and, like a colorful streamer, crashed toward the blue magic circle.

He had already suffered once from their attacks, and because it was humiliating to compete with the opponent in long-range magic, he switched to melee.

Kernid had condensed all his power, and his control over it was exquisite, not allowing any of the energy to dissipate. If an ordinary Grade A Super was faced with this attack, they would basically choose to avoid the blow instead of going head on. However, faced with these two strong and mysterious enemies, he did not have much confidence in being able to damage them.

Boom!

The resulting sound was like ramming a huge bell. The blue magic circle failed to withstand the blow and burst apart, turning into numerous glass-like energy fragments.

"Success!" Kernid was jubilant, and his confidence returned at the same time.

However, he saw the resulting burst of light illuminating the masks of both his assailants. Their eyes remained calm and indifferent, as though they did not view Kernid's full powered blow as a threat at all.

The next moment, the magic shards suddenly integrated together before bursting in a beam of blue white light, which struck Kernid. The beam had superimposed the power that Kernid had used to attack them with previously, which was equivalent to him facing his own attack.

Kernid's remaining offensive was interrupted, and he was blown back. Suppressing his pain from the injury, he exclaimed in amazement.

"What sorcery is this‽"

It was just protective-type magic, but it was surprisingly able to withstand his advanced-level Calamity Grade strike and could even rebound the power. This sounded simple, but at their level, the rougher and simpler a type of magic was, the more terrifying it would be. Unlike those magic shields that were layered with many inscriptions resulting in a 'quantity change', this was a qualitative change.

"Self-created," the masked man replied simply, but this answer caused Kernid's eyes to open wide, an expression of disbelief on his face.

At this moment, the woman by the side also attacked. Raising her right hand, she punched out violently.

Ka ka ka!

With the shrieking of bent metal, the entire spaceship started to rip apart.

The spaceship suddenly crunched up, as though it was violently pinched and crushed by a large hand.

Boom!

A large amount of oxygen leaked out, and the fuel tank as well as the engines of the spaceship exploded.

Fire burst outward, and the 'sphere' spaceship exploded directly, disintegrating instantly. Various debris flew outward into empty space.

In just a few seconds, a spaceship had been turned into space junk floating around the universe.

A spherical magic shield protected the duo, allowing them to levitate in the universe. Not far from them, Kernid's rune armor also flashed with a flickering shield of light.

The spaceship exploding had worsened the already serious injuries of Kernid, and his rune armor was also on the verge of being destroyed.

Without the spaceship, there was no way to escape, and a hint of despair leaked out from Kernid's eyes.

Within the magic shield filled with oxygen, the woman waved her arm.

All the wreckage came together once again, this time directly clamping Kernid in the center. It slowly turned into a huge sphere, as though there was some invisible force crushing it inward. The metal sphere slowly shrank further, as the original irregular shape turned round.

While there was still resistance within the sphere initially, it slowly turned lighter and weaker. Finally, there was no longer any more movement.

"Capture is complete for the Dark Purple Warlock Kernid," the woman coldly said.

The man then took out a communicator and opened up a list, crossing off Kernid's name. He sighed. "Shana, who's our next target?"

Shana was the name of the woman. She glanced over and tapped on the list, saying, "I pick him, the commander of the Black Star Army."

"Oh, this guy entered the list a year ago. His forces are developing very quickly, and if not for that, we might not even have paid attention to him. Yes, this guy is a bit special—he has the nickname of immortal. Seems difficult to handle. We should lead him to a suitable place to isolate him before capturing. That requires enough preparation time, and we also have to take Kernid back. Let's change targets."

"There's no need. We'll move separately. You take the captive back; I'll go handle Black Star," Shana blandly said. "Based on the intel, he only entered the Calamity Grade two to three years ago. Furthermore, he's a Mechanic. I alone can resolve this."

The man paused before smiling. "I almost forgot, your ability can restrain the Mechanic profession. Very well, I'll go and complete our mission while you proceed on to capture him. It seems like our harvest this trip will be quite fulfilling."

As for the relationship between Black Star and the Dragon Emperor, they did not even mention it once as though it was irrelevant.

Chapter 630: Development Status and Bottleneck

In the headquarters of the Black Star Army on Planet Golden Gate, a battle was currently going on.

Bang!

A black, streamlined, mechanical soldier knocked five purplish blue mechanical warriors aside and charged in front of Reynold while withstanding the laser beams being shot out from ten artillery towers. The arm of the mechanical soldier changed form into eight gears that rotated at high speed and struck Reynold's shield.

Reynold had a solemn expression on his face and left an electromagnetic trap behind as he retreated. At the same time, he released a blinding bolt of Mechanical Force lightning. He then used a skill to boost the might of his artillery towers and sent out a barrage of never-ending fire.

Ka ka ka!

All of a sudden, the black mechanical soldier suddenly disintegrated into black nanoparticles and flew back to the side of a figure not too far away. The black nanoparticles then reconstructed themselves back into the form of a mechanical soldier and stood beside this figure silently.

"You are becoming more and more powerful. It is only a matter of time before you breakthrough into the Calamity Grade," Han Xiao said with praise while clapping his hands.

Compared to two years earlier, Han Xiao was still young and handsome with his height increasing a bit. His aura was even more unfathomable than before. Han Xiao was currently dressed in a low-profile black windbreaker and was not wearing a mechanical suit.

"This is all thanks to your tutelage," Reynold said solemnly.

Han Xiao waved his hand and said out of politeness, "It is because of your talent."

After two years of guidance, Reynold was growing closer and closer to the Energy Rank of Grade A. He frequently exchanged pointers with Han Xiao, and since both of them were comrades, there was no need to exhaust each other. Thus, they would limit their spar to a small area and only test the strength and control of their machines.

The black mechanical soldier beside Han Xiao was one of the new models that Han Xiao had researched over the past two years. It had the ability of nano transformation, and its individual capability was spectacular, exceeding that of the Protectors. It was an elite machine that belonged to Han Xiao's Calamity Grade arsenal called [Phantom].

Reynold would always be shocked whenever he exchanged pointers with Black Star. Black Star would always be able to take out a different but powerful machine and would make use of him to test out his new machines. Reynold could not imagine how many different blueprints Black Star actually had.

Even at his level, it was no easy task to learn a single blueprint, and researching a new machine would take even more effort. However, Reynold just was not able to grasp Black Star's realm, and he could not understand why Black Star's efficiency in researching new machines was so frightening.

Furthermore, Reynold could feel that Han Xiao could deal with him more and more easily whenever they exchanged pointers. Black Star was already a Calamity Grade Super, but he did not seem to have a bottleneck and could continuously grow stronger. This made Reynold extremely baffled and felt that Han Xiao was unfathomable.

Reynold had always felt that he was an extremely talented individual and had great confidence in his own abilities. However, Han Xiao truly dealt a huge blow to his confidence. Reynold felt a sense of inferiority before Han Xiao with his attitude becoming more and more humble.

There was truly too much for him to learn from Black Star, and Reynold hated the fact that he could not use every minute of his life to follow Han Xiao and record his every single action.

After putting his machine away, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and casually asked, "How are the logistic reserves for the army?"

When it came to work, Reynold's expression grew serious, and he replied unhurriedly, "We have ample stock for all the different resources, and our reserves are healthy. Only Bases 17, 21, and 24 have a shortage of resources, and they mainly lack ammunition, fuel, and materials for commonly used machines. Four days ago, I channeled resources from the five nearest bases, and the first wave of resources should reach in two days..."

Upon hearing the report, Han Xiao nodded and got Reynold to leave while he thought to himself in his room.

Over the past two years, the Black Star Army had experienced rapid growth, and just as industry insiders predicted, they gradually monopolized all the employment missions within the Garton Star System and set up dozens of bases across the Garton Star System. They had even built an office on the mother planet of Godora.

The one million or so players brought the Black Star Army endless benefits. Han Xiao borrowed the hen to lay eggs, and the reputation of the Black Star Army grew continuously. As the scale of the Black Star Army expanded, more and more freelance mercenaries were attracted to join the Black Star Army.

Currently, apart from the one million or so cannon... cough, players, the army had a hundred thousand official mercenaries. Furthermore, the number of students that they were training in the various training camps had three to four times this number. Even by relying on only NPC mercenaries, the Black Star Army was an undeniable super-sized mercenary group.

The target of the training camps was no longer limited to the freelance mercenaries that did not make the cut but also ordinary individuals without any foundation. In the various bases on all the different planets, there would definitely be young individuals who wanted to enter the universe or become Supers.

The entire army was restructured with a clear system being developed to ensure that it could be managed more efficiently. The officers all had their own roles with some of them becoming managers of a region to manage hundreds of mercenary teams, trump card mercenaries to tackle high difficulty missions, commanders of fleets, instructors of the training camps, prosperity figures, and the female secretaries of the Army Commander.

The position of vice Army Commander is still empty. The individual who sat in this position needed to be sufficiently powerful in order to convince everyone in the army. Han Xiao was the only Calamity Grade Super in the entire Army, and his vice commander would also have to be of the Calamity Grade. Among all his officers, only Reynold was the nearest to the Calamity Grade.

Over the past two years, Han Xiao had hired over a hundred Grade B Supers. There were some who took the initiative to join the army, and others were elites who he sought based on his memory. There were some low-grade protagonist level characters to fill up the middle ranks of the army.

After monopolizing the entire Garton Star System, Han Xiao continued his expansion with the Garton Star System as the core. He also began to target the surrounding few Star Systems and snatched a portion of the markets.

The larger the market that his army occupied, the greater the demand on the strength of his market.

As a young teen who grew up in a capitalistic society, Han Xiao invested all his resources into the construction of new bases and the expansion of his fleet. He tried his very best to create a never-ending cycle of benefits.

Currently, the Black Star Army had 26 fleets, which were in charge of various responsibilities such as battle, transport, reinforcements, and so on. The Black Star Army had a total of 1,600 battleships, and the truth showed that robbing galactic pirates... cough cough, getting rid of tyrants to help the weak was a very beneficial action.

The number of Black Star Army bases also increased to 34, and apart from Noriosse and Rossozzi, the Black Star Army had three new sponsors. Two of them were ordinary financial groups, and one of them was actually the Godoran government. They had also increased the strategic resources provided to the Black Star Army, and the relationship between the two had grown even closer.

The influence of their faction expanded even further, and the Black Star Army was now ranked among the famous private organizations within the Colton Star Cluster. This time, it was Floating Dragon Island that benefited from the fame of the Black Star Army. The strength of the Floating Dragon field team made it such that Ames was no longer the only deterrent force in Floating Dragon.

However, Han Xiao could feel that the development of his faction was reaching a bottleneck.

As a mercenary group, the Black Star Army had already reached the peak, and if they continued to expand their operations, their efficiency would only decrease. Distance was a very obvious restriction. The larger the scope of their operations, the greater the requirement of a faction's strength. Monopolizing the Garton Star System was already the limit, and they did not have the ability to monopolize a second Star System.

The other reason behind the bottleneck of a faction was the nature of a faction. A mercenary group was a more relaxed organization, and if they wanted to enter the next level, the organization would have to be transformed to let the employment missions be of secondary importance. The faction would have to become a semi-private armed organization like Bloodshed Land.

The difficulty of such a task was extremely high, and this was not the right time to make such a change. However, Han Xiao was one to plan far ahead and knew that this was something that they had to do eventually.

"The only thing I don't have to worry about is my strength..."

In the blink of an eye, Han Xiao was already at level 170. His level had only risen by over twenty levels, and he was currently stuck on the [Galaxy Mechanic] Class Advancement Mission.

This was because Han Xiao did not place his attention on leveling up but stored most of his experience points up. His stash of experience points was already sky high, and even at his current level, the amount of experience that he had stored up was enough for tens of levels.

However, Han Xiao did not do so. He had not met any strong opponents over the past two years and was not in a rush to increase his level. As such, he invested his experience points into his skills in exchange for Potential Points and gambled on a large number of blueprints.

More importantly, Han Xiao considered the problem of the next version update.

The time taken for the next version update would be a full ten years in the game. This meant that he would not be able to harvest anything for a full ten years. His experience stash was like his rations for the winter, and the more the merrier.

"We are already at the end of Version 2.0. The version update should be coming after the Pro League. Sigh, that's a full ten years..."

Han Xiao could not help but let out a long sigh of worry. He then opened his interface to take a look at his personal stats.

Level: 170

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Chaos Observer (Human Form)

Attributes: 254 STR, 634 DEX, 608 END, 1956 INT, 263 MYS, 105 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Point: 31

Health: 93,732

Stamina: 94,180

Energy: 17,580 [Lv.11]

Lv.11 Energy bonus stat: +111 STR, +158 DEX, +174 END, +204 INT, +129 MYS, +21,220 Stamina Limit, +142% Machinery Affinity

Energy Rank: 14,780

Grade: A

Grade A Ranked Bonus: +10 END Bonus, +8 All Resistances, +10% Highest Stat(s), +5% Other Stats, Additional 30 Free Attribute Points, Additional 5 Potential Points

You are an experienced Grade A Super, and your enemies will have a taste of their nightmares.

Compared to the development of the faction, his own strength did not face a bottleneck. If he met a perverse Class Advancement or Promotion mission, he still had the option of using a Mission Completion Card.

As long as his experience stash could keep up, his own strength would increase rapidly. This was something that Han Xiao did not need to worry too much about.

His level was not the only thing that contributed to his strength. In the past two years, Han Xiao had looked around for talents.

While Han Xiao still had no clue on how to obtain Reynold's talent, Han Xiao managed to grab a similar talent, [Elementary Grade Mechanical Sense], and finally had a Mechanic Class talent.

His [Intermediate Strengthened Life] talent also gave him a few notifications that it was strengthened. Han Xiao estimated that he should be able to level the talent up if he consumed a couple of Genetic Medicine of rare lifeforms.

It was a pity that Molding Abilities were extremely rare, and Han Xiao had only managed to obtain ordinary talents in the past two years.

Apart from the change of attributes on his interface, the change in his combat strength was even more obvious!

Han Xiao's Mechanical Army had been expanded a couple of times, and he had strengthened the battle tactics of the various styles. He had added many new Calamity Grade machines, and his combat capabilities were more well-rounded than before. He was a changed man from two years ago, and Han Xiao felt that he should be able to fight five to six of himself from two years ago at once.

Whoosh!

At this moment, the room door suddenly swung open, and Sylvia was standing outside.

"Teacher, I finally found you. There are a couple of mercenaries who wish to meet you. They say that they have some important intelligence."

Two years ago, Sylvia had still been a budding young lady, and now, she had matured greatly. She was a beautiful young lady with nice curves and the perfect height. She was glowing with radiance, her eyes like the starry night sky.

Her position was Han Xiao's secretary, and her potential was fully unleashed by Han Xiao.

The homework that Han Xiao gave to her could make the Sylvia from two years ago crack her head with frustration but was extremely easy to the current Sylvia. She grew up faster by the day. Although her potential had not been converted to strength because of the lack of time, she could unleash the strength of a C+ Super with the mechanical suit that Han Xiao had built for her. She was able to exchange a few blows with an ordinary Grade B Super and was slowly gaining the aura of the 'Mechanical Lady Knight' from Han Xiao's previous life.

Han Xiao glanced at Sylvia for a while before asking, "Who wants to meet me?"

"These few individuals." Sylvia handed some information over to Han Xiao, who was stunned for a moment when he saw it. The ones who wanted to see him were Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, and the gang.

Chapter 631: Prologue of the Crimson Tide, Request From a Star Cluster Civilization

When Han Xiao entered his office, Sylvia brought Frenzied Sword and the others in.

"Black Star."

Including Bun-Hit-Dog, Frenzied Sword and the rest called Han Xiao's name simultaneously with excitement.

As the faction developed, Bun-Hit-Dog could not follow Black Star around everywhere anymore. Upon hearing that Frenzied Sword and the others were visiting Hao Tian, he instantly had an idea. For the sake of material for his show, he did everything he could to convince the others to let him join them. He started videoing as soon as he entered through the door.

Han Xiao looked across them and stopped at Frenzied Sword. He then loaded the 'Faction Leader' emoticon bundle and nodded. "It's been a long time, my friends."

Hearing this familiar tone, the others smiled. They had all been members of that highly skilled group of players, and they felt that Black Star speaking to them in a different manner was a special privilege.

"What important information do you have for me?" Han Xiao was curious. The players would not do things if there were no profit involved, so they had definitely accepted a mission from someone.

"We heard this is a hunting list. You're on it..."

Frenzied Sword explained about what had happened, took out the list, and passed to Han Xiao.

Ronaldo? Never heard of this name before, and what are hunters? Han Xiao frowned. He scanned through the list, and his name was indeed on it.

Someone is targeting me? Who could it be? Han Xiao pondered. The only similarity the people on the list shared was that they were all well-known Calamity Grades in the various areas of the Shattered Star Ring. Some of their names were very famous. He had even heard of them before in his previous life.

The fact that they dared target these people, no matter what these hunters' goals were, proved that they had an unfathomable amount of strength.

Are they targeting me because of my fame and strength? Han Xiao contemplated.

The Black Star Army had risen very quickly in these two years. There were barely any opportunities for Han Xiao to do things himself. The fact that he was one of the targets meant that he was seen as one of the well-known people in the Shattered Star Ring.

"Did that Ronaldo say anything else?"

Frenzied Sword shook his head. "No."

"Looks like we lack information and can't prove the credibility of this list. I will let Phillip search for the whereabouts of the people on this list. If there really is a group of hunters like he suggested, because he gave too little information, I can't figure out who these people are either."

Han Xiao shook his head.

Things like this were not very rare. In other words, Calamity Grades were like rare resources in the universe. They were always targeted by organizations with ulterior motives.

Currently, storms were quietly brewing in the Shattered Star Ring. Version 3.0 'Crimson Tide' was slowly approaching, so all sorts of people might appear. In fact, not just in the Shattered Star Ring, but other Star Fields too. The effects brought by the Crimson Dynasty's expansion spread across the entire Galaxy.

The three Universal Civilizations had finally entered the 'exhausted stage' of peace. Just like the 'seven years itch' between partners, although it would not lead to a divorce, quarreling and fighting would become frequent. The couple might be able to sort things out after these small emotional fights, but the damage caused during the fights would not disappear.

In his previous life, the Crimson Tide had been a chaotic era. Many hidden organizations had shown up, made use of the chaotic situation, and blamed the Crimson Dynasty for it. Those were troubled and chaotic times that the players faced back then.

Although Han Xiao was very familiar with the storyline, there was more than one organization that targeted people like him during the Crimson Tide. Some had been exposed in his previous life; some had never been discovered. He could not yet confirm who these hunters were with the limited information that Frenzied Sword and the others had given him.

It might just be an ambitious private organization, such as DarkStar, which indeed did the same thing in his previous life, but it might also be a sign of the 'Calamity of the Supers' or the 'Silver Revolutionary Army'. It was all unclear at this point.

Regardless, this list at least reminded me to be wary of my safety...

Although Han Xiao did not know who the enemy was, he knew that someone had their eyes on him. Hence, he knew that he had to be alert.

According to the intelligence, these mysterious hunters were very strong, strong enough to easily beat usual Calamity Grades. They were very likely Grade A+, which gave Han Xiao a little pressure.

I should find time to deal with the Class Advancement mission. I'm now level 170, and the Promotion at level 180 will be the next Race Evolution. It will make me much stronger. By then, I won't have to worry about Grade A+ Supers.

Sadly, the information of the enemy was too little. He could only stay defensive and could not search for the enemy. This was like a time bomb.

I shall find the time to go back to Floating Dragon Island and have old man Aesop do some foresight...

This time, Frenzied Sword, who had the highest Favorability with Han Xiao among the rest in the room, spoke again.

"Black Star, do you know about the changes happening in the Shattered Star Ring recently?"

They had received some hidden information from Ronaldo and felt it was related to the storyline of the next version. Now that they had finally gotten the chance to meet their faction leader, they felt that since Han Xiao was the mission target, he might know some of the information.

Frenzied Sword wanted to know as much as he could about it.

"The changes recently? What are you referring to?" Han Xiao raised his eyebrows.

"Ronaldo told us that there has been a lot of unrest in the Shattered Star Ring recently. He said that there's an organization behind this..." Frenzied Sword broached the subject in a very subtle way.

"Ah, I know, the Crimson Dynasty."

The atmosphere suddenly became silent.

Frenzied Sword opened his mouth wide.

Hao Tian's face twitched.

Everyone looked like they were struggling with constipation.

He—He said it this easily...

Although they got the answer they wanted, all of them felt somewhat empty. They had that thought this was a huge secret that no one knew about, but this was only the second person they asked, and he just casually said it.

It seemed that the things happening behind the curtain of the Shattered Star Ring, which Ronaldo took so seriously and could not understand at all, were just normal business to Black Star.

The process was so simple that Frenzied Sword and the others could not help but doubt whether this information was even important at all.

Except for Bun-Hit-Dog, who was the most excited. His eyes were sparkling.

During Version 1.0, Black Star had hinted at Version 2.0's Mutation Disaster. Now, Black Star gave the hint about the next version once again.

They felt that Han Xiao was more and more mysterious as if he knew everything.

Frenzied Sword had known Han Xiao the longest. Even he could not help but feel he did not know Han Xiao at all.

Han Xiao then changed the topic and said, "The information you have given me is indeed valuable. I have a mission for you guys..."

As he was speaking, he quickly wrote a reward mission and gave it to the players. Its rewards were very rich, and there was even a reward where they could pick one piece of equipment for free. Overjoyed, Frenzied Sword and the others quickly accepted the mission.

Han Xiao gave them a few words of compliment and gave them five points of Favorability. His Favorability was like a product discount. Then, he told Sylvia to send away the satisfied Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, Bun-Hit-Dog, and the rest.

After they left, Han Xiao leaned back, crossed his legs, and started pondering.

He had always been paying attention to the players. All the players had left their own novice planets and entered the galaxy. Among the others, his Black Star Army was undoubtedly the best guiding faction. The players from Planet Aquamarine were all fed very well and healthy. The second Pro League was about to start. He had quite high hopes for the performance of the Chinese clubs this time as well.

Most players had reached the level limit of level ninety; they would be able to make use of more of their class specialty. Their strategies would vary, so this season would be more exciting than the previous one.

The better the results of the Chinese clubs, the more attractive his faction would become. When the players entered the stage of inter-Star-Field travel in the future, his faction would be able to attract players from other areas. No number of leeks would ever be too much for Han Xiao.

These Genetic Medicines will be very popular.

Han Xiao smiled. After sucking dry countless galactic pirates, he had a lot of these stocked up in the warehouse.

After looking at the forums for a while, just as Han Xiao was about to get up and play with the cuties in the machinery modification room, Sylvia suddenly entered the room.

"Teacher, there's an important invitation."

"Invitation?"

"Colton Star Cluster's ruling civilization, the Purple Crystal Civilization, wants to hire you specifically."

Star Cluster Civilization!

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The Black Star Army's business was limited to Star System Civilizations and had yet to get in touch with any Star Cluster Civilizations. Although Han Xiao had gotten the contact of a Purple Crystal Civilization official during Tyrant's party, the requests made by Star Cluster Civilizations were all given to selected groups—the Black Star Army was not in them.

Now, they had finally received a mission from a Star Cluster Civilization. The Purple Crystal Civilization was the ruler of Colton. As they had invited him by name, it seemed rather important.

Completing a mission from a Star Cluster Civilization would add a huge amount of value to the resume of the army.

A few years ago, Han Xiao had no contact with any Star Cluster Civilizations because he was in no position to, but now he could.

Furthermore, contacting a Star Cluster Civilization was something that he could not avoid on his path of personal growth.

In the past two years, Han Xiao had learned almost all the High-End Knowledges; he now had to look for the next stage of knowledge—Cutting-Edge Knowledges. Star Cluster Civilizations were a very important part of gaining Cutting-Edge Knowledges.

This is an opportunity!

Han Xiao told Phillip to transfer the communication and added protection to the channel at the same time.

The image flashed, and a familiar face appeared. It was the Purple Crystal Civilization representative whom Han Xiao had met during Tyrant's party, Ralph.

"Black Star, it's been some time," Ralph said in a friendly manner.

Han Xiao chatted with him a little before they started to get down to business.

"You people wanted to hire me specifically?"

"That's right. Your army has a very good name, so you're one of our top choices."

"And what are the mission's details?"

"It's an elimination operation. The target is a fleet. They have disguised themselves as travelers, but their background is much more complicated than that. We plan to eliminate this fleet as a warning to the people behind them."

Ralph described the situation very vaguely. Han Xiao could not help but guess what the organization that the Purple Crystal Civilization wanted to warn was.

After giving it a little bit of thinking, he had a rough idea.

Purple Crystal had decided to find mercenaries to deal with this instead of doing it themselves, which was clearly not because they were not able to, but the identity of the enemies was sensitive, which caused Purple Crystal to not want to do things the official way.

"Klentans?" Han Xiao spoke softly. Purple Crystal and Klent looked like they had a very good relationship, but they were targeting each other secretly. In his previous life, Purple Crystal and Klent had even fought.

Ralph smiled and did not answer this question. He changed the topic and said, "There has been a lot of unrest in the Shattered Star Ring recently. These organizations have been crossing the line more and more, so they have to be dealt with."

Han Xiao stroked his chin.

Two years had passed, and the effects of the Crimson Tide had been fermenting. Many organizations wanted to make use of it, so many organizations had been showing themselves, the disorder was spreading quickly. The waves created by the Crimson Dynasty made civilizations that stayed neutral such as the Purple Crystal Civilization very annoyed. Strange things kept happening in the Colton Star Cluster, and the security of their territories had become more and more threatened. Purple Crystal finally could not take it anymore and decided to make an example of these people.

"So, Black Star, do you want to accept our hire?"

"Let's talk about the reward first."

"Of course, what do you want?"

"Mechanic Cutting-Edge Knowledge," Han Xiao replied.

Ralph's face became troubled when he heard this.

"That might not be possible. Cutting-Edge Knowledges are very precious. The people above will not agree. I can only pay you with money..." Ralph paused momentarily. "However, you're Floating Dragon's officer, and we respect Ames a lot. Therefore, if we have the chance to work together again in the future, Cutting-Edge Knowledge might not be impossible."

Cutting-Edge Knowledge is indeed not easy to obtain... Han Xiao had expected this, so he was not disappointed.

What Ralph meant between the lines was, this hire was like an entry ticket for the Black Star Army. If he completed it, Purple Crystal would hire him for more missions in the future. Once he made a big enough contribution, Purple Crystal would be willing to give him Cutting-Edge Knowledges. It was basically the path of increasing Faction Favorability.

Cutting-Edge Knowledges were very precious; only at this stage could one study antimatter, psionic energy, and the like. Han Xiao did not think that there was a problem with the way Purple Crystal was doing it. Nothing was free in the world—he needed Cutting-Edge Knowledges, and Purple Crystal needed stronger unofficial military power to do things for them privately. It was all part of a deal.

Han Xiao pondered for a while before nodding. "Okay, I can try it."

"Great." Ralph smiled. "I will send you a gathering location later. There are other people on this mission. The mission details will be sent to you later."

"Okay." Han Xiao had no objection. This was not the first time that he had a group mission like this.

Chapter 632: Gundam Is a Man's Romance

The gathering location was in another Star System within the Colton Star Cluster, very far away from Garton. Han Xiao had Risda fly him to the planet used for the gathering.

This was an unpopulated planet with just a series number. When the Blacklight Stealth arrived at the coordinates, there were already quite many spaceships parked on the ground, and a crowd had already formed. They all looked up one after another at the newcomer.

The spaceship descended steadily. Han Xiao walked out of the hatch and looked around casually. There were only two people there whose vital signs reached the level of Grade A. It seemed like they were two leaders, but they were unfamiliar. They both led a group of people, meaning there were two organizations present.

"The Garton Star System's Black Star? I've heard of him."

"He came too."

"Did he not bring those undying mercenaries?"

The crowd looked at Han Xiao with surprise and chatted among themselves.

A member of the Purple Crystal Civilization got out of the spaceship and stood in front of Han Xiao. "Welcome, Black Star. I'm the one responsible for this operation, level 3 diplomat of Secret Service Department 4, Dodder."

"Hi." Han Xiao nodded. "Where's Ralph?"

"His Excellency Ralph's position is very high; I'm his subordinate's subordinate. This operation does not require him to be in charge personally."

Ralph's position was quite high in the Purple Crystal Civilization. What Han Xiao did not know was, of all the people who were invited to this operation, he was the only one that had been invited by Ralph personally. The others only had contact with Dodder.

This special treatment was because Han Xiao had attended the Tyrant's party before. To Ralph, Black Star was a member of the upper-class social circle, so he personally involved himself in this small operation that he did not need to be bothered about, showing that he took Han Xiao seriously.

"There are three organizations that are going to be working together for this operation. Let me introduce you to the other two."

Dodder took Han Xiao over and introduced him to the leaders of the other two organizations.

"This is Jayne, a strong Esper. The others call him 'Seaquake'. This is Gadeli. His nickname is 'Hundred Rounds Cannon'. He's a Cannon Master."

The two of them sized Han Xiao up and shook hands with him respectfully.

Jayne and Gadeli's equipment was very sophisticated, especially Gadeli's. His battle suit was made of super-nanotechnology. Han Xiao could see that this battle suit had very strong shapeshifting capabilities from a glance. This guy was a Cannon Master, so he might have turned his trump card firearms into parts of the battle suit and wore it on his body.

Han Xiao had never heard of the two of them before, so he told Phillip to do a search. He then realized that the two of them were not mercenaries but small private military organizations only formed a few years ago and had a rather small size.

Speaking of which, the Black Star Army had only been formed for a couple of years, yet it had risen extremely quickly at an unmatched speed.

In Galaxy, the number of such organizations was right below mercenary groups. There were various reasons that these organizations were formed, but it could be mostly categorized under two reasons. One was for private reasons; these organizations had their own goal and did not accept requests.

The other was similar to mercenaries but did not accept public hires like normal mercenaries. They only accepted private invitations or looked for long-term partners. Hence, they were not a part of the mercenary industry. They had much stricter regulations toward their members compared to mercenary groups. The Bloodshed Land belonged to this category.

Usually, as long as the organizer had enough money and strength, forming a private military was simple. The strength of the leader was the ceiling of the private military—those created by Calamity Grades were the comparatively stronger ones. Jayne and Gadeli had both formed such organizations. Their active areas were in Star Systems rather far away, so their name was unheard by Han Xiao. However, they had both heard Han Xiao's name before. It was clear which one of them was more famous.

This time, Jayne suddenly asked in a confused tone, "You came alone?"

"I alone am enough." Han Xiao smiled. As this was a sudden mission, he did not waste time to gather others.

Jayne and Gadeli looked at each other with hidden joy in their eyes.

They were new organizations, so this cooperative operation was a good opportunity to get in touch with the Purple Crystal Civilization. To the two of them, this was a competition for the opportunity to have a long-term partnership with the Purple Crystal Civilization. The other organizations were all competitors, so they had to perform well.

Initially, when they saw Black Star, they had been very worried. If Black Star had brought the undying army under his command, the two of them would be completely unable to compete.

However, now that they realized that Black Star had come alone, they felt relieved that they had the opportunity to put on a performance.

After the introduction, Dodder took out the star map and explained the details of the operation.

"We are currently in Star Zone 3 of the Thousand Lights Star System. The target is in Star Zone 7. According to the target's movements, we can intercept them in Star Zone 9...

"We have three Calamity Grade Supers and forty-four battleships. The target has sixty-five battleships, but some of them are civilian spaceships used as cover. Therefore, the actual combat capability of the enemies will be lower than that. The strength of their members is unknown. They entered the Colton Star Cluster from the desolate universe and did not go through any identity checks. They have also yet to stop and resupply along the way."

The others nodded. The intelligence network of the Purple Crystal Civilization covered the entire Star Cluster—all they had to do was rush in. They had three Calamity Grades, so the enemy's advantage of just more than twenty battleships was meaningless.

"Just a small fleet..." Han Xiao raised his brows. He had initially thought it would be a high difficulty mission, but as it turned out, it was just clearing out some shrimps. Yet, the Purple Crystal Civilization had invited a few Calamity Grades for it. He felt that their main goal was probably to select some new private military organizations for future partnerships.

Ding.

A notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the mission [Purple Crystal Civilization's Warning]!

Han Xiao scanned through quickly and skipped the experience reward. Even the reward of more than a million Enas was not a big deal to him now.

The only reward that he felt was actually valuable was the Faction Contribution Point of the Purple Crystal Civilization, which was 330 points.

The higher level the faction was, the more difficult it was to obtain its Favorability. However, due to Han Xiao's pile of Legendary Points and titles, his current relationship with the Purple Crystal Civilization was not the initial [Indifferent] but [Neutral], so he had a starting Favorability of 450.

In order to obtain Cutting-Edge Knowledge, farming Faction Favorability was the method with the highest odds of success.

This time, Dodder suddenly thought of something.

"By the way, one more thing. The Star System Civilization ruling the Thousand Lights Star System requested backup from the Purple Crystal Civilization. One of the strongest people in their territory has gone missing, so they requested that we help them find him. The missing person is called Kernid, nickname Dark Purple Warlock. This is what he looks like. If you happen to discover any clues, do remember to tell me."

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment. The name sounded very familiar.

Kernid seemed to be one of the names on the hunting list.

Han Xiao kept this in mind.

...

The target of the cooperative operation—the fleet that was disguised as galactic travelers—was slowly moving through Star Zone 9 of the Thousand Lights Star System.

In the command room of the main ship, the captain, Bret, was recording the various data.

"Voyage dairy K-003015: It has been 134 days since entering the Colton Star Cluster. Everything is normal at the moment. Currently carrying out the 6th data collection. The scouting area is the Thousand Lights Star System. The transfer of data for civilization development, civilian planet ecologies, security, and the others have been completed. The next station is the core area of the Colton Star Cluster, the White Ceiling Star System. We will gather intelligence on the Purple Crystal Civilization there."

After the voyage dairy was sent out, the system completely destroyed its data.

Bret rubbed his eyes and soothed his tiredness.

"Alert! Alert! An unknown fleet is approaching!"

At this time, the lights inside the room turned bright red. The alarm of the spaceship artificial intelligence rang and instantly alerted Bret. He rushed to the radar screen, where an unknown fleet was shown to be heading directly toward them and would soon enter their vision.

"Send a message to them and ask about their entity," Bret yelled. "Tell them we're just galactic travelers."

However, like throwing a pebble into the sea, the message got no reply at all.

Very soon, the fleet appeared and, without any hesitation, started firing at Bret's fleet. The battle erupted in an instant!

"They're not galactic pirates; we've been targeted!" Bret was experienced. He instantly knew that this would not end well for them.

Being very decisive, Bret ordered to counter-attack while recording a video and sending it back to his organizations, letting the headquarters know who these enemies were.

This fleet that suddenly attacked belonged to Han Xiao and the others. Jayne and Gadeli were commanding the fleet and fighting with the enemy. The Blacklight Stealth was watching from the side.

In the cockpit, Han Xiao looked at the battlefield and squinted.

"Although the enemies are not much of a threat, it is a good opportunity to test my new weapon."

As he thought, Han Xiao switched to autopilot and walked to the ejection area in the middle of the ship. Berserk Ape quickly covered his body as he directly jumped into space.

The difference between Han Xiao's size and the battleships' was like the difference between an ant and an elephant. However, the next moment, the light of Mechanical Force flashed. Countless mechanical parts expanded from within the Berserk Ape mechanical suit, and compressed orbs opened up one after another.

In the blink of an eye, a more than thirty-meter-tall Giant Soldier mechanical suit was assembled. Its size was not much different from small assault ships. The huge energy wave attracted the attention and surprised both sides of the battle.

Giant Soldier, Ship Destroyer, Gen 3 Improved Version!

In the past two years, after obtaining the various High-End Knowledges, Han Xiao had finally reverse engineered the blueprint of spaceships and learned to build battleships. With this technology, he had improved the Ship Destroyer blueprint that Carroll had lost to him. He had enhanced it two times and updated many parts of it. Compared to the first generation, the third generation Ship Destroyer looked much more aesthetically pleasing. From a tube-shaped body, it became human-shaped, possessing four limbs and a head.

Giant Soldier mechanical suits were made for galactic battles, so their performances were all very high. With Han Xiao's Mechanical Force bonuses, this Giant Soldier was terrifyingly strong. Other than Virtual Intrusion, Han Xiao now had a more direct method to battle in space.

Inside the cockpit of the Gen 3 Ship Destroyer, Han Xiao completed the nerve connection. The giant mechanical suit became as easy to control as his arms and legs, and the small burden it brought to Han Xiao's mind was nothing to someone as strong as him. Han Xiao could not help but feel a little nostalgic.

"It's been so long since I piloted a large mechanical suit. I wonder if I got rusty."

Bret's eyes opened extremely wide. His voice was breaking as he said, "It's a Giant Soldier mechanical suit! Focus fire on it and destroy it!"

Every qualified commander knew what a Giant Soldier could do in galactic battles. Compared to bulky battleships, the mobility of the Giant Soldier mechanical suits was a nightmare for the entire fleet. As soon as a Giant Soldier appeared in galactic battles, they would definitely become the primary target.

Countless missiles rocketed through space and expanded in Han Xiao's eyes, yet a sense of anticipation for battle appeared on Han Xiao's face.

With just a thought, the three-dimensional mechanical body of the Gen 3 Ship Destroyer activated. Like a bullet, it entered the rain of fire, barely dodging the attacks one after another while the high level energy shield blocked the stray attacks.

The Great Mechanic Han's piloting skills had been honed by countless battles. Only a Giant Soldier mechanical suit could allow him to express his real skills.

The huge mechanical suit moved like a shadow, quickly closing in on the enemy fleet.

This time, two enormous cannon barrels extended from behind Gen 3 Ship Destroyer and mounted on both of its shoulders. They fired thick, massive beams of hot energy cannons, shaking up the shields of many enemy ships with every shot.

Then, four enormous hovering guards appeared, circling around the Gen 3 Ship Destroyer as a means of protection as well as to counter-attack.

The moment Han Xiao took out the Giant Soldier mechanical suit, the focus of the entire battlefield had been on him!

After some time, the Gen 3 Ship Destroyer finally approached an enemy ship at the edge of their formation and was stopped by the spaceship's shield. This time, the space around the Gen 3 Ship Destroyer suddenly looked bent and twisted. Han Xiao had activated the anti-shield impact waves. The shield of the enemy ship in front of him suddenly became dim and started flickering. Its defense was tremendously reduced.

Han Xiao had not wasted his time over the prior two years. He had spent a huge amount of Experience and built countless pieces of new equipment. A lot of different technology had gone into the Gen 3 Ship Destroyer.

The next moment, a Thermal Chainsaw extended from the Gen 3 Ship Destroyer's hand, slashed down, and cut the enemy ship right in front of it in half like cutting through tofu, leaving a hot, red light at the fracture.

Time seemed to stop for an instant.

The next moment, the enemy ship that was split in half exploded into fireworks. If not for the vacuum environment, the sound of the explosion would have been deafening.

Looking at the blinding explosion, Jayne and Gadeli's faces uncontrollably twitched.

There was no way their performances could be better than Black Star's Giant Soldier mechanical suit.

Just as Black Star had said, it was indeed enough for him to come alone without bringing any troops.

"How much money did it cost to build this Giant Soldier?" Jayne murmured.

Gadeli clenched his teeth in envy. Jealousy had turned his expression twisted. "Damn, it must be good to be rich!"

Chapter 633: Formation of the Organization, an Assault Invitation

There was no suspense in that crushing battle. With Bret's troops being completely destroyed, the battlefield that was crisscrossed with artillery fire turned completely silent, with corpses and metal debris floating all around.

Han Xiao had cooperated with the forces of Jayne and Gadeli, driving the 3rd Generation Ship Destroyer straight into the enemy's fleet like a knife to vegetables. The enemy fleet had no way to retaliate. After all, he currently possessed two interstellar combat methods. Virtual Intrusion served as internal disturbance, whereas driving the Giant Soldier was just mindless violence.

For such a small fry, why was there a need to utilize Virtual Intrusion? Just cut through them like a hot knife through butter, that would be more enjoyable.

In the past, Han Xiao had seen battlefields where thousands of battleships bombarded each other and had even participated in such battles himself. Compared to the large-scale artillery warfare density, this small-scale operation did not give him any pressure. There was no difficulty in controlling his mechanical suit to avoid and hide.

The 3rd Generation Ship Destroyer was also a crucial factor. Han Xiao had spent a lot of effort to perfect the blueprint of this giant mechanical suit. He had lost count how much materials he had poured into it. This sort of ship destroyers would show the greatest effect in such small-scale interstellar warfare. A 3rd Generation Ship Destroyer cost at least 3.5 million Enas, which was more than some small high-end battleships. If it was the him two years ago, this sum of money would have hurt him.

But right now, it only made a sizeable dent.

The ability of the Black Star Army to rake in gold could even destroy Floating Dragon Island. Han Xiao faintly remembered that the last time he checked the account balance, there seemed to be more than 80 million Enas worth of liquid funds, and their fixed assets were several times that number. This was far less when compared to a financial group, but he could be considered a young and promising leek scholar [1. Loosely translated, it refers to an organization that profits off dumping of stocks and shares to force a drop in the market before capitalizing on it.]. Oh no, a better word would be a powerful leader.

Originally, Jayne and Gadeli's troops were supposed to be the main attackers, but the moment Han Xiao entered the battle, he immediately snatched away their position as he dominated the fight. They ended up only being able to contain the enemy and watch the whole process. Watching Han Xiao control the Giant Soldier, his style gave them a deep impression, which could be summed up as...

Stylish!

Luxurious!

Mischievous!

The Third Generation Ship Destroyer had also received some minor damage, along with losing a large amount of its fuel in just this short battle time. Han Xiao retreated in the 3rd Generation Ship Destroyer, returning to the Blacklight Stealth and regrouping with Jayne and Gadeli. The three of them left the crime scene as one whole, heading toward the nearest unmanned planet for a rest.

"You guys did a good job." Dodder contacted the trio, praising their success.

The reward was already transferred into each person's accounts, and Han Xiao received a notification to show that his mission had been completed. The Favorability of the Purple Crystal Civilization had also risen slightly as a result.

"Everyone should have some sort of speculation in their hearts. That's right—this was a simple test for us to select some reliable unofficial armies to cooperate with us. You have all demonstrated your strength, and we hope to have a happy cooperation in the future."

Jayne and Gadeli immediately exclaimed. They had thought that since their limelight had been stolen away by Black Star, they would no longer have an opportunity. Thus, they got excited.

"With the chaos present in the Shattered Star Ring during the past two years, we think that the future will be host to even more unpredictable and complex dangers," Dodder explained. "Thus, we have planned to secretly form an organization of various armies. We're looking for more people of your caliber to cooperate with us, to defend the Colton Star Cluster in secret. As for the specifics, I can't disclose them to you yet, but what I can reveal is that we're building a secret army, and all of you are potential candidates."

A secret organization comprised of various armies?

Han Xiao perked up. He recalled which storyline this was at last.

In Version 3.0 'Crimson Tide', due to the flurry of activity all around, joining a faction had become a sort of culture. It was not just the Purple Crystal Civilization, but many Star Cluster Civilizations also recruited various armed forces to aid them in times of need, creating a secret organization much akin to the Protectors.

For example, the Shattered Star Ring Mercenary Alliance in Version 3.0 was one of such products of combining various armed forces.

The allied organizations would form the basis of the factions that the players could join in on Version 3.0, and their choices were plenty.

Han Xiao recalled that the organization formed by the Purple Crystal Civilization was codenamed 'Section Zero'. It referred to the hidden organizations and departments of the Purple Crystal Civilization. The members within were strong and came from various galaxies, accepting a long-term employment from the Purple Crystal Civilization in exchange for resources.

In other words, both Jayne and Gadeli would likely be comrades in the future.

Han Xiao would never reject such a good deal, and furthermore, he would still have to approach the Purple Crystal Civilization in order to obtain the Cutting-Edge Knowledge he required. Just his title as a member of Section Zero would net him quite a few benefits. This was a connection to having a long-term cooperation with a Star Cluster Civilization.

In his previous life, when the players entered Version 3.0, the joint organizations had already been formed way ahead of time. What the players gazed on was merely the end product, but what was before Han Xiao right now was the early stage of the preparation for the joint organizations. This was obviously a bigger opportunity for him!

Even without his shameless self-recommendation, the Purple Crystal Civilization already had him in their sights. His position today would not have been possible without all his hard work to manage his faction as well as the blood, sweat, and tears of the players.

If he could become the main force behind Section Zero, this would be akin to raising his reputation in the Shattered Star Ring, which would boost his name to become one of the first-rate organizations within the Colton Star Cluster.

This was his own shortcut to a higher level of prestige!

"If I receive a reasonable pay for my efforts, I would be pleased to," Han Xiao replied.

Jayne and Gadeli also recovered from their ecstasy and hurriedly replied, expressing their willingness to join in this organization.

"You will not be disappointed with the remuneration. At present, the organization is still in selection. When it is formally established, there will be many huge missions," Dodder replied.

This move from the Purple Crystal Civilization was akin to military conscription on Earth. The Purple Crystal Civilization initially had a fixed number of organizations that were in cooperation with it, but in the past two years, Klent had been restless, which had led to the Purple Crystal Civilization having a premonition that there would be a conflict with them sooner or later. As the conflict intensified, there was a chance of a secret war happening.

The so-called secret war was merely both sides screaming at each other to 'come get a piece of me', yet refusing to declare war on each other. Instead, they would secretly use their affiliated organizations to attack the other party, cutting off their wings. This is a torturous method under the Peace Treaty, where the killing and killed was all borne by the allied organizations.

Of course, the Star Cluster Civilizations knew the theory that if you wished to have good race horses, you had to allow the horses to graze. They were immensely generous with their benefits and were able to support the resource needs for the allied organizations. It could be said that as long as an organization could survive this secret war and cooperate as the pawns of the civilization, they would face a qualitative change and rush toward the sky in one shot.

Han Xiao understood the idea of the Purple Crystal Civilization. If he wished to develop and aim higher, it would be impossible to do so without facing danger. While he had a good organization at the moment, expansion would not happen on its own. Han Xiao knew that he had to correct his position at any given time.

Unless Ames became a collaborator with the Purple Crystal Civilization, he would not have enough leverage nor say when against a Star Cluster Civilization. He had not reached a point where he could haggle with a civilization of that level. The Purple Crystal Civilization was not begging him to join, but rather, this was a chance for him to properly develop his forces, which was essentially a fair deal.

As long as the reward was enough, he did not mind fighting for them. Right now, he was no longer the past self where he was weak and needed to be careful with every step. With enough strength and capabilities, he could bravely charge in.

Unlike Jayne and Gadeli who had expressions of joy, Han Xiao had already begun to deduce the consequences of his every choice.

A secret war... Han Xiao stroked his chin.

This was one of the most important storylines for Version 3.0. If one ignored the complicated interests behind Crimson Tide, the theme of Version 3.0 could be summarized in one word: fighting!

The various allied organizations would be in conflict with each other, and Section Zero would also have to face off against the Klent Kingdom many times. They certainly would not be excluded from the battlefield.

As long as the Tyrant did not appear, everything could be settled. He was not afraid of any other muscle-heads at all, and he had never been afraid of people at the same level as him.

Swoo!

At this time, the sound of a spaceship passing by was suddenly heard above them. Han Xiao stopped his communication and quickly looked up, seeing a small and exquisitely designed single-person spaceship. It was not known when this spaceship had entered the planet.

"Coincidentally here to collect some resources?" Jayne asked.

"Unclear." Gadeli shook his head in return.

The single person spaceship's hatch opened, and a woman dressed in white robes floated out in midair, with a white colored cat mask on her face. She surveyed the surroundings with a cold expression.

"Who are you?" Gadeli shouted out. Toward this uninvited guest, he could not help being vigilant upon feeling the powerful fluctuations coming from her.

This was a Calamity Grade Super!

Shana ignored him, instead looking around before her gaze landed on Han Xiao. She blandly asked, "Black Star?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and did not answer. He faintly felt that this visitor had unkind intentions.

"It doesn't matter even if you do not answer. You can't escape today." Shana swept her eyes across before muttering to herself, "Three Calamity Grades, a little tough."

Ka ka ka!

The next instant, Shana moved. From the time she showed herself till she attacked, it did not even take ten seconds!

She reached out, and the dozens of spaceships parked on the surface immediately turned into metal fragments. The spaceships violently exploded, and the fragments were transformed into a metal storm grinder. In a split second, the subordinates of Jayne and Gadeli were sliced into minced meat.

Gadeli was furious, and the battle suit on his body resonated like a giant wave. Nanoparticles gathered in his hands, turning into a giant firearm. The muzzle of the firearm fired toward Shana, and the cannon rays were extremely strong, incorporating all of his Mechanical Force.

Dong! Dong!

A sudden fierce battle unfolded!

Shana pointed, and an invisible magnetic field shield appeared around her. The defense of the shield was quite strong, and even after the flames from the explosion covered the body, they were all isolated outside of the magnetic field, leaving her unharmed. Then, Shana gripped with her hand.

Bang!

The huge firearm in Gadeli's hands immediately disintegrated, turning back into nanoparticles like sand falling off from one's hands.

Magnetic Field Control and Metal Manipulation‽ Han Xiao's expression contorted. This uninvited guest had come here to deal with him and could completely restrain any Mechanics. It was unknown where she came from. As he thought, the only thing he could link it to was the hunting list.

It can't be. How is there so much of a coincidence? Han Xiao was surprised. He secretly wondered how the enemy was able to discover his location.

Only he was involved in the operation this time, and those who could leak the report, other than the Purple Crystal Civilization, would only be his comrades, Jayne and Gadeli...

No, there was another possibility!

Han Xiao thought of the fleet that he had annihilated previously. Before they got destroyed, they had sent the intelligence out. Could it be that this mysterious hunter was associated with Klent?

Whoosh!

The huge metal fragments shot toward his head with a whistling sound, distracting him from his thoughts. It was not the time to consider such factors. Han Xiao wanted to use the Berserk Ape, but upon recalling the abilities of the enemy, he frowned and could only remove the thought of using his Mechanical suit. He relied on his own body to dodge the fragments, escaping far away.

The metal fragments slammed into the ground, creating a large pit and scattering stones everywhere.

Shana had faced everyone alone, but with just a few finger movements, she had already destroyed the army of Gadeli and flung him away hand. Seeing this, Jayne's face lost all color. The battle capabilities of this uninvited guest had far outstripped her expectations!

Han Xiao had a headache. Facing such an opponent, the Mechanic profession was bound to have its arms tied behind its back. The many methods at his disposal would all be easily resolved by the other party, causing him to lose a lot of money.

This was by far the enemy that most countered his abilities!

Metal Manipulation is the kryptonite of the Mechanics. This woman probably also has a battle capability at Grade A+. If this carries on, the situation won't be good...

Chapter 634: The Calamity Battle

Every class had its nemesis.

Among them, the Esper class was the most unique—they could sometimes be the nemeses of the other four classes, but the other classes might also sometimes be their nemeses. This was all because of the randomness of Esper abilities.

In the five Super classes, Espers' pros were just as clear as their cons. Their combat capability was almost solely dependent on their different Esper abilities. Also, their class knowledge tree was very straightforward, such as enhancing Esper ability's strength, range, accuracy, and so on.

Espers could shine brightly in one aspect and lack in others; all their abilities had their limitations.

For example, teleportation lacked defense, high speed recovery lacked the ability to deal damage, and prophecy... well, no need to rub salt in the wound.

Of course, these were all rather extreme examples of Esper abilities, which explained the clear distinction of Espers' pros and cons. To the players, the gaming experience would, of course, be greatly enhanced if one could obtain a special type of Esper ability. There were tons of players who topped up real money into their accounts to buy Esper Gene Awakening Potions.

Other than the lucky ones, some unlucky but rich ones would keep creating new accounts and use Gene Awakening Potions till they got an Esper ability that they are satisfied with.

During the team battles in the Pro League, forming teams that could counter the opponents was also a strategic focus.

For an Esper with the ability to control metal and the magnetic field, of course, they would not be much of a problem at all to Pugilists and Mages. However, it just so happened that someone like that was the nemesis of Mechanics. It would be a lie to say Han Xiao was not troubled.

Although, as a Mechanic, his energy had magnetic attributes as well, his ability to control the magnetic field was far from that of the enemy, who had the Esper genes to do so.

The Mechanical Force was more focused on enhancing machines; controlling the magnetic field was just a bonus. The most he could do was disrupt the opponent's Esper ability. In order to completely nullify the opponent's magnetic field, more specific machines would be needed.

In an instant, Han Xiao looked at the battle information and knew that the opponent's name was Shana. Shockingly, her level was a question mark. Han Xiao was already level 170. Even if Shana was not Grade A+, she would not be far from it. The huge difference between their strength was very difficult to overcome.

"Risda, leave the battlefield!"

Han Xiao dodged the attacks from shattered metal and ordered Risda. If the Blacklight Stealth was torn apart, it would be a huge loss.

The Blacklight Stealth quickly ascended and was about to accelerate and leave the battlefield. Unbothered by this, Shana reached out her hand and aimed at the Blacklight Stealth as she was about to clench her fist, crushing Han Xiao's spaceship just like she did to the other spaceships.

Bang!

The next moment, a while colored shadow of a man clashed toward her like a meteor, dragging a lightning-like tail behind. It broke the sound barrier and bashed heavily right onto Shana's magnetic field shield.

The invisible magnetic field shield was dented, and it bounced the white shadow out like it was elastic. Shana was not hurt, but she was sent flying a short distance away by the clash. She quickly controlled the metal on her and stabilized herself midair. She looked down at the white shadow.

In her eyes, Han Xiao wore a bone white mechanical suit. It was the Void Dragon mechanical suit that he had not used for a long time.

This person's Esper ability counters me, so I can only use non-metallic weapons... Han Xiao thought.

The metal content of the Void Dragon mechanical suit was very low. Although its attributes could not match up to a battle between Calamity Grades, at least it was not as restricting as the Berserk Ape, so it was barely usable.

Most of his machinery was made with alloys—non-metallic machinery might only make up ten percent of them.

Many machines had very strict requirements on their materials; high density and non-metallic materials that could replace alloys were very difficult to fuse. Depending on different materials, the machinery's attributes would be different as well. Before meeting an enemy that could control metal, it was clear that alloys were the most suitable choice.

If alloys could not be used, carbon nanotubes would be a very good choice as well. However, Han Xiao's previous opponent was Ember.

Even if he had to build machines that could deal with this situation, he would have to do it after this battle ended. Hence, most of Han Xiao's main machines, as well as his Army Style, could not be used unless he ignored the loss that he would incur.

From the way he saw it, the current situation was far from that desperate.

Test her limits first. Han Xiao squinted.

Using the instant when Shana was distracted, Risda accelerated and successfully escaped the battlefield, avoiding the fate of being turned into scrap metal.

All the rest of the spaceships were crushed into pieces by Shana and formed into a metal storm, directly going toward Han Xiao.

Other than the three Calamity Grades including Han Xiao, everyone else died without any ability to fight back. These Grade C warriors in metal battle suits were crushed by their own battle suits.

Whoosh!

Han Xiao dashed through the metal storm, deftly dodging the attacks. The cannon in his palm kept firing at Shana, but the Void Jet Sprays could not penetrate Shana's magnetic field shield.

At this time, Jayne clenched his teeth and yelled, "Ha!"

His shirt shattered into pieces, revealing his muscular body. His body was vibrating at a high frequency. The air around him trembled, the vibration transferred into the ground below, and the cracks on the ground rapidly expanded.

Right after that, Jayne slammed his palm toward Shana, who was in midair.

Boom!

An invisible vibrating wave headed directly to Shana. Everywhere it passed, the air was bent, outlining an oval shape.

Shana frowned slightly as she moved sideways in midair, dodging the attack.

Jayne was the only one present who was not countered. Han Xiao looked over. Jayne's upper body was naked, and his long chest hair was flowing and vibrating with the air.

That's some macho heart-protecting chest hair!

This time, a sudden mission popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the hidden Grade A Chain Mission [Prey]!

Mission Introduction: You have become the prey of a terrifying organization. They will try to hunt you again and again till they succeed. Don't think about escaping; their background is beyond your imagination. You have no choice. Keep struggling. By becoming stronger through these battles, you may have a tiny chance.

First Round: Defeat Shana

Reward: 37,000,000 Experience. Draw one of Shana's ability or talent

Han Xiao saw the mission introduction and thought, A horrifying organization? Interesting.

He remembered the storyline in his previous life; however, Shana could not fit into any organization in his memory. It seemed like it was a hidden organization that the players in his previous life had no contact with. Their hunting targets were all renowned Grade As, so it would make sense if the players did not know about them at that time.

This thought flashed past during the battle. The three of them attacked Shana together.

Both Jayne and Gadeli were Calamity Grades. There was no need for words; they could easily cooperate with Han Xiao.

Since there were helpers, there was no reason for Han Xiao not to make use of them. He took on the job of direct battle, standing before the metal storm and attacking Shana's magnetic field shield. Jayne took on the job of the main attacker; his vibration attacks were quite threatening and forced Shana to keep dodging. As for Gadeli, he did not come closer after being blasted away. He went dozens of miles away and made use of his ranged attack strength as a Cannon Master by attacking from afar.

Tens of miles was nothing to Grade A Cannon Masters; his accuracy was still very high, and he could still shoot from even further away. His nickname 'Hundred Rounds Cannon' explained his attack frequency. The nonstop ranged attacks caused Shana quite a lot of trouble. She wanted to deal with Gadeli but was limited by Han Xiao.

Boom!

The three of them were embroiled in the fight. The power of Calamity Grade attacks was very high. The ground cracked, and explosions continuously occurred.

They were in a stalemate; Shana was quite irritated.

Bret, who had been crushed by Han Xiao and the others, was actually a member of an intelligence organization under the Bloodshed Land. He had received a mission from Klent to come to Colton and gather intelligence. It just so happened that the organization Shana belonged to had a special relationship with Klent, and she happened to be in this area after capturing Kernid. After Bret was attacked, the intelligence organization that he was in had informed Shana, who was nearby, to rescue them.

However, Shana had arrived too late, but she did discover Black Star. Hence, she changed the goal and targeted Black Star. The way she saw it, Black Star had presented himself to her, so she did not have to go all the way to the Garton Star System to find him anymore.

Shana had been confident in dealing with Black Star, so she had never expected to end up in such a tough battle.

Bret's intelligence did not include Jayne and Gadeli's information. As Han Xiao had quickly eliminated the fleet with the Ship Destroyer, the two of them did not act. Hence, they were unexpected backup for Han Xiao.

"The game has ended."

Shana did not want to waste any more time. She yelled coldly before suddenly placing her hands on the ground, fully activating her Esper ability.

Rumble!

The ground started trembling violently.

The next moment, something shocking happened!

Dozens of miles away, holes suddenly started to appear on the ground. Almost a hundred gigantic snakes made of metallic dust soared up from the ground. They were all more than ten meters wide and almost endlessly long.

The ground was suddenly filled with holes!

The next second, almost a hundred gigantic metal snakes flew up and rushed toward Han Xiao and the other two.

Controlling the magnetic field of a planet and using the metallic elements underground... Horrifying ability strength.

Han Xiao felt it was quite a difficult situation. Espers that could control metal definitely needed metal to make use of their ability. With only those spaceship pieces, Shana was not very threatening. However, her ability was strong enough to control the magnetic field of the planet. This meant that the entire planet was Shana's armory.

She was indeed a calamity!

Gadeli's eyes opened wide. He quickly wanted to back away but was caught by two gigantic metal snakes. One of the snakes swallowed Gadeli, then the two snakes fused into a hundred-meter-wide metal ball, falling right down onto the ground.

Ka ka ka!

The sphere kept squeezing its interiors and increasing its density, trapping Gadeli inside. This was an attack that Shana loved to use.

Seeing this situation, Jayne's fists slammed down onto the ground, clearly using some kind of ability. A ring of shockwave expanded on the ground.

Boom!

The vibration triggered chain reactions, and the ground started rapidly trembling at a much higher frequency. An earthquake appeared in this area, and countless gigantic metal snakes were shattered into metallic dust.

The movement caused by this attack was humongous. Further away, a huge fissure appeared in the ground as if the planet had opened its mouth.

Boom!

The shockwave hit the metallic sphere that trapped Gadeli. The next second, the sphere was shattered into pieces, and Gadeli quickly escaped.

Han Xiao was surprised. Jayne's destructive power gave him quite a shock. His nickname 'Seaquake' was indeed accurate. There were practically no Grade A Espers that were weak. After all, if one's Esper ability potential could not reach A, that person would never reach Grade A.

Bang bang bang!

Shana and Jayne did not hold back at all. The battlefield kept shifting, and everything with hundreds of miles was turned into ruins and shattered, like a disaster crawling through the planet surface.

However, although it caused a lot of destruction, Shana was hovering in the air. The earthquakes had almost no effect on her. She had the absolute upper ground.

Glancing at Han Xiao, who was dodging around far away, a shade of disdain flashed past Shana's eyes. She shook her head.

Although Black Star was the target on the list, he had almost no sense of presence, much worse than Jayne's. On the other hand, Jayne seemed more qualified to be a target.

Shana was somewhat disappointed. The rumors said that Black Star was very strong, but she now felt that it was exaggerated.

However, she then realized that her ability countered Black Star so heavily, so it was normal for Black Star to not be able to fight back.

If these two guys were not here, it wouldn't be this troublesome.

Shana frowned. As long as she could get rid of Jayne and Gadeli, Black Star would be a piece of cake.

However, she had a new plan. Jayne was quite strong and would sooner or later be on the list, so she decided she might as well capture both Black Star and Jayne.

As for that Cannon Master, she did not feel that capturing him would be of any use.

At this time, Jayne's defense showed a tiny flaw. Shana accurately captured the opportunity, and the gigantic metal snakes instantly surrounded Jayne and turned into a sphere. Jayne kept vibrating from within, wanting to break the cell. However, Shana used most of her attention on him; she controlled tens of metal snakes and made them part of the sphere one after another.

The huge sphere kept shrinking as its density kept increasing. Its ability to resist vibrations grew stronger and stronger, and the frequency of the vibration kept decreasing. Finally, Jayne could not move anymore.

Done! Shana's eyes sparkled. To her, controlling Jayne meant that this battle had ended. Black Star did not have any strong backup, so she could capture him easily.

Shana turned around, her vision penetrated the dust everywhere and stared at Han Xiao. "Your helper is no more. Now it's your turn."

Han Xiao suddenly stopped and stood opposite Shana.

Just as Shana thought that Han Xiao had given up resisting, Han Xiao suddenly laughed.

"You're right, it's my turn."

Hum!

The next second, continuous sounds of explosions came from above.

Shana quickly looked up.

Fifty 'stars' were falling down at an unbelievable speed above her head.

These 'stars' were all Eye of God's attacks. One beam from the energy cannon was almost eight meters wide!

Shana's pupils rapidly constricted.

All she had time to do was form a magnetic field shield. The next moment, fifty satellite cannons' attacks plummeted!

Boom!

The deafening sound of explosions spread everywhere!

The impact waves blew everything around them away. Gadeli was sent flying far away, and the metal sphere trapping Jayne was shot up and crashed into a mountain more than ten kilometers away.

A bright mushroom cloud rose from the ground. It was white everywhere and almost nothing was visible.

Countless stones turned to ash, and the gigantic metal snakes melted into liquids.

It was like the end of the world!

Even in outer space, a bright red mushroom could be seen rising on the planet's surface!

It looked like Han Xiao was not doing much, but he had actually been giving orders to Risda, who had left the battlefield to plant the fifty Eye of Gods from the warehouse. One round of fire from those cannons was more than enough to destroy an entire city!

The enemy had shown extraordinary abilities. It would be very difficult for him to defeat her even if he was very tanky. Only such strong firepower could decide the outcome of the battle.

Han Xiao placed his hands on his waist and chuckled.

"Did you really think I was out of my depths? Let me introduce the Tactical Support Style. I'm the representative of rascals."

Chapter 635: After I Plant a Ward on You, You Will Be My Teammate

The Tactical Support Style was known for its powerful firepower beyond the battlefield. Han Xiao had a liking for this kind of style. In the two years' time, he had built enough Eye of Gods and kept them in the Blacklight Stealth at all times. It was a necessity for family travels, killing, and robberies.

The hot mushroom cloud was still continuously expanding, and a huge crater was created on the ground.

Han Xiao did not waste any time. With the mechanical suit's thruster accelerating, he advanced into the explosion area, heading right toward the bottom of the crater.

The combat information notified him that Shana had kept fortifying her magnetic field shield and blocked a lot of the damage. With her equipment's defense and her own resistance, this attack was not enough to heavily injure her. Furthermore, when the fifty Eye of Gods fired together, the attack was not concentrated enough, and a lot of its power was wasted.

The most important effect of this attack was to temporarily turn the situation around, putting a stop to the opponent's control of the battle. Han Xiao was not planning to give Shana any time to take a break, so he quickly advanced. As he entered the area, he saw Shana and her shield crushed into the soil. A semi-sphere magnetic field shield was at the bottom of the crater, very conspicuous among the flames and dust.

Boom!

At this time, Shana hastily looked up. Her mask was already destroyed, showing her face with a twisted expression. Blood flowed down from her forehead; her face was completely filled with murderous intent. As if she had expected Han Xiao to approach at this time, she pressed her hands on the ground. Suddenly, a metal particle fountain shot out from below Han Xiao and grabbed onto him.

Grade A Supers all had rich combat experience. The instant Shana was attacked by Han Xiao, she had guessed what Han Xiao would do next. As she blocked the attack, she had also planted a trap and concentrated the metal particles under the ground around her. This was to capture Black Star, who was dodging her like a fly.

However, the next moment, Han Xiao suddenly disappeared.

Hu!

Suddenly, the sound of wind appeared less than one meter behind Shana. Her senses told her that there was now another person in her magnetic field shield.

Racial Talent—Advanced Void Travel!

How did he enter here through the magnetic field shield‽ Shana's expression drastically changed. Before she could turn around, the back of her head was grabbed by a big hand covered in a bone-white mechanical suit. An irresistible force exploded from within and pressed her face down into the soil.

The next second, the gray light of Void Energy spilled out from within the Void Dragon mechanical suit and focused on Han Xiao's arm.

Maximum output Void Jet Spray!

Boom!

Void Jet Spray could be used continuously without any cooldown; the price of that was the increasing energy cost. Han Xiao did not hold back at all and almost finished up all the energy of the Void Dragon mechanical suit.

During just the first spray, he had already activated the injection module inside the mechanical suit and injected a Genetic Medicine. In the last two years, he had captured countless galactic pirates. He had even changed the name of his private prison into "Galactic Pirates' Warm Little House". He had gathered a lot of Genetic Medicines that could cater to any situation. The temporary ability given by this medicine was that continuous attacks had a higher chance to cause the 'stun' effect.

The chain Void Jet Sprays triggered this effect easily, and Shana entered the 'Stunned' status. Her brain was a mess, and she could not fight back at all. All she could do was take in Han Xiao's storm of attacks as her body trembled.

As the last spray ended, Shana was still in the 'Stunned' status and could not use her abilities. Without hesitation, Han Xiao immediately equipped Berserk Ape and entered the Berserk Overload Form!

With his arms high above his head, blinding lightning energy formed on his fists.

The next instant, his fists slammed down heavily!

Bang!

Lightning exploded like a spider web, and the bottom of the crater was once again filled with cracks!

Han Xiao used everything he had on this attack. Berserk Ape's [Power Detonation], his own [Gene Liberation], and the occasional critical damage triggered due to Shana's 'Stunned' status. The damage multiplier was greater than ten!

Ka!

Even with the deafening sound of impact, Han Xiao could clearly hear Shana's bones breaking below him.

Han Xiao calmly grabbed onto Shana's neck without mercy. He then took one step forward and turned rapidly, throwing Shana out like throwing a baseball. The moment Shana left his hand, a ring of impact waves appeared in the air.

Berserk Throw!

Hu!

Shana was sent flying out like a cannon, flying out of the mushroom cloud in an instant, and kept getting further away, almost disappearing from Han Xiao's vision.

However, this combo had yet to end!

As Shana was about to recover from being stunned while flying, tens of light suddenly appeared in the sky again.

The second round of fire!

Boom!

The second mushroom cloud appeared.

The impact wave arrived as expected. The mechanical suit on Han Xiao's legs shapeshifted and grabbed tightly on the ground, preventing him from being blown away.

Han Xiao waved his hand, and a huge square-shaped firearm appeared beside his feet. It was two meters tall and looked like a huge box. The top of the box had more than twenty openings. This was an explosives ejector. Han Xiao carried it on his shoulder with one hand and fired at the center area of the second mushroom cloud far away.

Bang bang bang!

Countless specially-made grenades arced through the air and landed on the target area, causing nonstop explosions.

All these grenades were Mini Nuclear Grenades and Space Bending Bombs, and the clip was quickly emptied.

Far away, Gadeli finally saved Jayne from the metal sphere.

The two of them looked at this and simultaneously gulped.

How brutal, this is a complete ravage...

With the clip emptied, this combo dealt tons of damage. However, there was still no notification showing that the target had been killed. This meant Shana was still alive. As an almost Grade A+ Super, her ability to resist damage was also very strong. Han Xiao equipped Void Dragon once again, using his energy to recover some of the mechanical suit's energy.

Just as he was about to continue, Shana suddenly dashed out of the mushroom cloud from above, rapidly heading toward the sky. All the gigantic metal snakes followed behind and fused together, like a mountain rising from the ground.

She's escaping? Wait, no! She wants to destroy my satellite railguns.

Han Xiao activated his thrusters and chased after Shana.

The two of them headed toward the outer space.

Damn it... Shana glanced at Han Xiao below her and clenched her teeth.

She had suffered the most during the time she was stunned, and after the combo attack, she was quite heavily injured. Her left arm was soft and dangling. Its bones had shattered into some abstract artwork. Her left leg was also twisted unnaturally. The left side of her body had been heavily damaged by Han Xiao. Even she did not know how many of her ribs were still connected. Her chest and her back were in extreme pain. She was in a terrible state.

It has been a very, very long time since she had been this badly injured. She was both shocked and furious. Shocked by Black Star's suddenly explosive power and furious about how heavily injured she was.

If Eliot was here... Shana unavoidably thought of her Mage partner and regretted doing this alone. This time, she had been overconfident.

Although she was heavily injured, Shana had no intention of retreating. She planned to go to outer space and dismantle all of Black Star's firepower support. This way, the fight would still be possible to win.

In Han Xiao's vision, the planet surface rapidly shrank. The two of them rocketed into the sky. He controlled all the Eye of Gods and aimed at Shana, firing one after another, hoping to slow her down.

However, Shana was prepared. Her flight path had no pattern at all, and she never flew in a straight line. At the same time, she used the huge metal snakes as shields. The attacks from the railguns were either blocked or dodged by her.

It seems like I can't stop her... Han Xiao calmly analyzed. Without hesitation, he activated the return program of all the satellite railguns. The Eye of Gods flew back to the warehouse in the Blacklight Stealth one after another. He planned to let Risda take the weapons and escape the battlefield once again. With the Blacklight Stealth's mobility, there would be nothing Shana could do.

The two of them finally closed in on the edge of the atmosphere. Before them was pitch-black space. The Blacklight Stealth had already collected all the satellite railguns and was about to get away from this planet.

Shana clenched her teeth, barely raised her right arm, and was about to activate her Esper ability.

Han Xiao's Advanced Void Travel was still in cooldown. He was just about to give Shana another Void Jet Spray when curved cannon light arrived from the surface and accurately landed on Shana. This time, she was not prepared at all. She was blown away and rolled in midair.

On the ground, Gadeli was operating an enormous Sniper Railgun with both of his hands. This shot had come from him. As a Cannon Master, he brought along firearms that could cater to various situations. This enormous firearm was used for extreme long-distance sniping.

Gadeli was a Grade A Cannon Master. Although he had been beaten up by Shana due to her Esper ability, he was not completely powerless. To snipe a target in outer space from the planet surface, even data such as the spinning speed of the planet had to be considered. However, with his level, this was just a regular thing to do. As long as the firearm had enough power, his sniping distance was extremely long.

This shot prevented Shana from activating her ability. The Blacklight Stealth escaped Shana's ability range within an instant.

Shana barely stabilized her body in midair and glared at Han Xiao. She realized that the situation had become very difficult.

In her current state, there was a very thin chance that she could defeat and capture the three Calamity Grades including Black Star. Shana started thinking about retreating.

Shana did not want to risk her life for something that clearly had a very small chance of success. There was no need for that. Even if she failed this time, she could bring an ally and come back again. This failure would at most alert the target.

However, in her eyes, even if Black Star was alert, it would be meaningless. She did not expose any information, so Black Star had no idea who was targeting him.

All she had to do was bring a strong enough ally next time. In a battle where one side was overwhelmingly stronger, regardless of whether Black Star was prepared or not, he would still end up being defeated.

Realizing this, Shana's flames of fury dissipated, and she calmed down.

She did not want to stay there any longer. She raised her hand, and the gigantic metal snake pounced right onto Han Xiao. She then summoned her single person capacity spaceship and quickly entered the cockpit.

Han Xiao was held back by the gigantic metal snake and could not chase her, nor did he want to. The Void Dragon mechanical suit could not race with a spaceship, and Berserk Ape would be completely countered. It would indeed be very difficult for him to hold Shana back.

Most importantly, although Shana was a rare tough enemy, Han Xiao did not want to kill Shana straight away.

Shana's spaceship quickly left. Before she entered hyperdrive, Han Xiao threw an Observer's Mark on her.

Without Shana's control, the gigantic metal snakes shattered into pieces in an instant and fell to the ground like rain.

Han Xiao hovered in midair, looking at the tracks left behind by Shana's spaceship. He smirked.

Making me your prey won't be this easy...

The mysterious organization that Shana belonged to had targeted him. Even if he killed Shana, there would still be strong enemies that came to chase after him. It would not solve the root of the problem.

Currently, Han Xiao knew nothing of this mysterious organization. What he needed urgently was information.

The Observer's Mark was a perfect ability to steal intelligence. Letting Shana go was part of Han Xiao's plan to catch the bigger fish.

Finding out what this mysterious organization was, their size, and the location of their base—that was the key mission. After all, Han Xiao did not want to keep his guard up every single day, worrying about being attacked at any time.

This mysterious organization was a ticking time bomb. In order to get rid of it, this was the most efficient method.

Although this would mean he would have to face Shana, who countered him, in the future, Han Xiao decided to shift the focus of the machines that he would be building from now on. He planned to start building a lot of non-metallic machines, as well as special machines that were focused on controlling magnetic fields. This would minimize Shana's ability against him.

As long as a Mechanic was given enough time, they could counter anything.

Nonetheless, that woman was quite strong. Without these two helpers, I would've had a very tough fight.

Han Xiao took a deep breath. If it was a duel, with his blood mana cycle, the battle would have been a battle of stamina. There would be an extremely low chance that Shana would be able to defeat him. Nonetheless, he would have had a very difficult fight. Luckily, Jayne and Gadeli had helped him take on some of Shana's power, so he had not been at a disadvantage the entire time.

After defeating Shana, a notification popped up showing that the first round of the hidden Grade A Chain Mission [Prey] was complete, giving Han Xiao more than 30 million Experience. Han Xiao did not instantly draw Shana's ability—Feidin was not beside him, so he had no confidence.

I shall draw after returning to the base... Han Xiao shook his head.

He could not be together with the Goddess of Luck no matter how hard she tried, but Feidin could make the Goddess of Luck willingly spread her legs. The treatment was just so different—it made him despair.

Chapter 636: How Can One Draw a Prize Without Touching Feidin?

Han Xiao lowered his head and took a look at the battlefield from high above. The ground was cracked up like a biscuit that had been stepped on. There were still two gigantic craters and a dust cloud that had not subsided.

Han Xiao then flew back to ground and took the Void Dragon suit off.

Jayne and Gadeli immediately came forward to welcome him. Both of them were covered completely in dust with Jayne being covered with injuries all over.

"Black Star, did you get rid of that woman?" Jayne asked anxiously.

"No, she managed to escape." Han Xiao shook his head.

"You were her target. Do you know who that woman is?"

"I am not sure. This is the first time she's attacked me."

Han Xiao knew that she was called Shana, but there was no need to let both of them know.

Both of them were truly furious. They had met a calamity that did not have anything to do with them, and all of their subordinates and battleship fleet had been wiped out.

However, it was useless for them to blame Black Star. Black Star was equally clueless and never intended to set them up. Besides, Black Star's strength and status were things that they would not be able to compare to, so the two of them could only treat it as their own bad luck.

While Gadeli and Jayne were feeling extremely sh*tty, they were also extremely shocked at Shana's combat capability. Even three Calamity Grade Supers were not enough to keep her behind. If not for Black Star's timely burst of strength, both of them probably would not have been able to defeat the enemy.

After the three of them adjusted their conditions a bit, Dodder sent an emergency communication request and asked about the situation.

"How are all of you? What happened just now?"

"An unfamiliar A+ Esper suddenly attacked us. Her identity is unknown..."

Han Xiao briefly explained what had happened and also asked the Purple Crystal Civilization to help him investigate the matter.

"No problem. We will thoroughly investigate the other party's identity. We will inform you of our investigation results." Dodder agreed to the request solemnly. "We are still in the midst of preparations for the alliance of organizations. There should be news within the year, and we will gather everyone when the time comes. I hope that the three of you will make appropriate preparations."

After a short conversation, Dodder ended the transmission.

Han Xiao put his communicator away and looked at the two others. "What do the both of you intend to do after this?"

Both of them let out a bitter laughter.

"We are truly too unlucky." Gadeli sighed.

"Start my recruitment and purchase battleships again to make up for today's loss," Jayne replied helplessly.

Upon hearing that, an idea immediately sprung up in Han Xiao's mind. These two individuals were powerful Grade A Supers. With their organizations being crippled, he might have a chance to recruit them.

"Actually, both of you can come to my Black Star Army. With your strength, there won't be a problem with you being vice commanders. I sincerely invite both of you to join me."

Han Xiao smiled and extended his invitation.

The both of them were taken aback. After pondering for a moment, they gave their response.

"Thank you for your invitation, but I do not have any intention of joining another organization," Jayne said.

"I still prefer to build my own organization. I'm sorry." Gadeli shook his head.

"No worries. My invitation will always be open to both of you. We can talk about this again in detail whenever both of you are interested."

Han Xiao was not too disappointed by the result.

It was far more difficult to recruit a Calamity Grade Super than a Grade B Super. Every Grade A Super had the strength and right to dominate a region, and their ambition would usually be in line with their strength. Gadeli and Jayne wanted to build their own organizations and were not willing to submit to others.

After all, even a beyond Grade A powerhouse might get rejected when trying to recruit a Calamity Grade Super.

"Black Star, we would like to trouble you with something." Jayne was slightly embarrassed, and his chest hair shook.

"Feel free to speak." Han Xiao tried his best not to get distracted by Jayne's chest hair.

"Er... our spaceships were destroyed, so..."

Han Xiao chuckled and slapped Jayne on the shoulder. "Don't worry, we are comrades who fought alongside each other. Take my spaceship. I'll take both of you to the nearest port."

"Haha, we shall trouble you then."

Upon seeing that Black Star was such an easy going guy, Jayne stroked his chest hair happily. He belonged to a race that judged beauty based on their chest hair. Soft and silky chest hair was the benchmark of a suave man.

Han Xiao immediately forced a smile and said, "Please put on some clothes first... don't drop any hair on my spaceship."

Shana's spaceship was currently flying through the universe.

In the cockpit, Shana injected herself with some healing medicine and could barely walk properly. Only then did she send a transmission to her comrade.

Eliot appeared on the screen. He was Shana's mage comrade, and both of them usually worked together.

The moment the transmission was connected, Eliot asked, "Shana, have you caught Black Star... Eh? Your complexion looks extremely terrible. Did something happen?"

"I failed." Shana briefly described what had happened calmly.

"Hahaha. How miserable..."

Eliot did not display any anger but laughed out loud in schadenfreude instead.

Shana's expression was ugly, and she hatefully said, "I will kill you one day."

After laughing for a while, Eliot regained his cool and calmly said, "You acted rashly and failed your mission. You will cause us to face the risk of exposure. All of us will have to remain low profile for a period of time."

Shana grunted and did not say anything. She did not attempt to find an excuse for her failure but did not feel guilty about it either. So what if she failed? It was not a big deal to her.

"Black Star's strength has been underestimated," Eliot said slowly. "While you did not reveal any information about us, he will now be wary, and it will be more difficult to capture him in the future. We should place him by the side temporarily and deal with the other targets.

"In any case, go back to headquarters and meet up with me there. We will discuss our plans back in the headquarters. Remember to shake off anyone following you, and do not reveal our location."

"I don't need you to remind me," Shana replied coldly and hung up. She then activated the stealth function of her spaceship and traveled toward the headquarters.

However, she did not know that an eyeball was looking at her silently from the void.

After sending Gadeli and Jayne off, Han Xiao returned to the Garton Star System without stopping and stopped at the base on Planet Golden Gate.

The mercenaries in the surroundings saw the landing spaceship and recognized that this was Han Xiao's personal spaceship.

The Blacklight Stealth then flew straight into Han Xiao's personal hangar, and he walked to the core region of the base through a priority tunnel. Without saying a word, he immediately went to find Feidin.

Feidin would usually be meditating on the rooftop on normal days. The moment Han Xiao came to the rooftop, he saw Feidin meditating cross legged with Psychic energy being emanated from his body.

Feidin's eyes were shut at the moment as he sang melodiously. The path he took was identical to Chen Xing's, and they used their Psychic energy through singing. The heavenly music was like elves within the winds to calm all fatigue and pain. Han Xiao also calmed down as he heard Feidin's song.

Feidin's song could cover the entire base and could give the players a temporary buff. This was the specialty of Planet Golden Gate, and Feidin was like the background music of the base.

Feidin had inherited all of Chen Xing's knowledge and was an extremely talented individual himself. Thus, his strength improved at a rapid pace.

Two years ago, he could already suppress Chen Xing on his own but did not choose to leave. Instead, he chose to continue cultivating in the Black Star Army and occasionally follow the troops out on their missions.

Occasionally, he would travel alone to explore the galaxy but would always return to the Black Star Army to rest and reorganize. Han Xiao was extremely willing to be Feidin's backer as long as he could touch Feidin.

Full marks for touching, zero marks for not touching.

However, Feidin's mission had not been completed yet. Ever since Feidin fulfilled his promise to hand over all of Chen Xing's savings, his relationship with Chen Xing had entered a cold war period.

Han Xiao estimated that when two of them could open up their hearts to each other, a new world would be open to the both of them, and they would enter a phase of passionate love. That would also be the completion of his mission.

There was another person seated on the rooftop as well. Aroshia was seated by the side, enjoying Feidin's singing. Two years ago, Han Xiao had shared the mission to find Aroshia's memories with the players, and the effect over the two years was obvious. The mission progress had accumulated quickly and was about to be complete. Aroshia enjoyed listening to Feidin sing as it could allow her to recall more memories.

When she saw Han Xiao arriving, Aroshia transformed her arm into energy and wrapped it around Han Xiao's waist like a belt as a greeting.

Noticing Han Xiao's footsteps, Feidin stopped singing and turned around. With a smile, he said, "Black Star, are you looking for me for something?"

"Nothing much. You can continue singing. I am only here to find some luck."

Han Xiao then walked forward and touched Feidin all over before turning around to take his leave.

Feidin touched his nose and laughed bitterly.

He had always felt that Black Star had somehow misunderstood him. Was his luck very good? Why did he not hear about it?

After Han Xiao touched Feidin to his heart's content, he left the rooftop and opened the interface. Before his luck could dissipate, he hurriedly concluded the [Prey] mission to draw for Shana's ability.

First round complete.

You have received: the opportunity to draw one of Shana's abilities or talents.

Note: Shana is a unique Esper, and the abilities that you draw will be adjusted based on your class.

Randomizing... draw complete.

Please select one of the five rewards:

[Magnetic Field Vision] - talent: You will gain a keen insight into magnetic fields. +12% Machinery Affinity, +6% Mechanical Force bonus range

[Magnetic Vortex] - skill: Control skill. Release a burst of magnetic energy to create a magnetic field. Chance to inflict a target within the magnetic field with the [Chaos] status. Chance determined by INT and external environment. Energy Usage: 160, Cooldown: 46s

[Electromagnetic Shooting Stars] - skill: Long ranged skill. Overlay multiple objects with electromagnetic force. Accumulate a large amount of kinetic energy before shooting the objects out and causing a damage between 210 – 742. Damage determined by the size of object and accumulated electromagnetic time. Energy Usage: 75, Cooldown: 12s.

[Strong Magnetic Field Shield] - skill: Defensive skill. A magnetic shield will be formed within a 3m vicinity of the user. Shield durability is unlimited, and maintaining the shield will exhaust energy. If the damage taken by the shield within a second exceeds the critical point, the magnetic shield will be shattered. Cooldown 2.5s. The critical point is determined by the amount of energy exhausted per second with the maximum damage being 22,000. Every time the shield takes damage, additional energy will be exhausted.

[Super Electromagnetic Sense] - talent: Your 'magnetic' attribute will be enhanced. The bonus received from every energy level will change.

This was the result after the skills had been modified, and Han Xiao was not too surprised. All of Shana's skills were rooted in her Esper ability, and it was impossible for him to gain the other party's Esper ability. The abilities to strengthen the control of metal in a magnetic field would be useless to him.

Thankfully, control of metal within a magnetic field was extremely compatible with the Mechanic class. After a series of adjustments, most of the skills were useful to Mechanics as well.

There was not a single skill that stood out from the rest, but the skills were not too terrible either. Han Xiao felt that he had drawn the average skills this time.

If I didn't touch Feidin, I am afraid that I would have drawn some sh*tty skills. It seems like Feidin's luck cancelled out my bad luck.

Chapter 637: In the Chaotic Crimson Tide, Storms Are Forming (1)

Han Xiao was not interested in the first choice, [Magnetic Field Vision], at all. He now had almost a thousand percent Machinery Affinity; this bonus would not make a difference.

Among the three abilities, [Strong Magnetic Field Shield] was undoubtedly the strongest. If a player obtained this, it could almost be a god-tier ability. Its only flaw was that its energy cost was very high. Nonetheless, to Han Xiao, he could totally afford its cost.

Sadly, he really did not want another tanky ability. [Strong Magnetic Field Shield] clashed with his mana health cycle. Only the damage taken by his body would be absorbed and turned into energy. If it hit a shield, it would not activate.

Although this ability was quite good, he was not really in need of it.

The names of the other two abilities were kind of lame, but their effects were quite good. They could be used as a means of attack when he was not using machines. However, it was too rare for him to not use any machines, so he would not use these skills as much.

The last talent [Super Electromagnetic Sense] had a very simple introduction. Han Xiao had seen similar talents before in his previous life; they enhanced the basic attributes of one's energy, causing the bonus given by energy to increase tremendously. This kind of talent was rather rare. Not just the Mechanic class, the other four classes had talents that enhanced their energy as well. Shana's Esper attribute just so happened to be suitable for the Mechanic class.

The magnetic attribute was related to the Mechanical Force. If he chose this one, the increase in his Machinery Affinity would be many times greater than the first talent on the list. Furthermore, when he acquired a new level of energy bonuses in the future, this talent would still be effective. It was the same as increasing his potential.

This was a high-level Mechanic talent that was rather difficult to obtain. It had growth potential.

Tsk, I can only choose one...

Han Xiao scratched his hair. Other than the first option, he wanted all four.

After pondering for some time, he decided that long term potential was more important and made his choice.

You have received [Super Electromagnetic Sense]!

Your Magnetic Energy has been enhanced!

Your energy bonuses have changed!

When Han Xiao opened his attributes and looked at it, he smiled.

His Machinery Affinity was largely increased in every energy level. His Energy Level was currently [Lv11], which originally gave him 142% Machinery Affinity. With this talent, it became 262%

A 120% increase in Machinery Affinity!

Almost double!

Nice, that makes it worthwhile.

Han Xiao was quite satisfied. This 120% bonus affinity made his Machinery Affinity go beyond 1,000%. Furthermore, this talent had more long-term benefits and would become stronger as his level increased.

Although it could not be compared with Reynold's almost cheat code level [Perfect Mechanical Sense], it was still quite good. Including his [Elementary Grade Mechanical Sense], he finally had two Mechanic class talents.

Now, this is more Mechanic like.

Han Xiao chuckled.

Nonetheless, the other three abilities were good. He was quite upset that he could not choose all of them.

This is just the first round. Shana is still alive. If every round's reward includes drawing her ability...

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he could not help but fantasize. He wanted to meet Shana a few more times.

Shana was an ability treasure trove!

He looked at the second-round mission of [Prey], but it had yet to update.

The second round would probably only start when the enemy attacked again.

The enemies are hiding, and I'm in the open. Luckily, I planted a ward on her, or I really wouldn't be able to guard against their sudden attack. Just like the mission name, they're hunters waiting for opportunities to strike, and I'm the prey they have targeted. If I'm attacked during an important part of another mission, I will incur a huge loss. These hunters really are a bunch of sh*t stirrers.

Han Xiao was glad.

On the way back, Han Xiao had peeked at Shana and Eliot's conversation through the Observer's Mark, discovering that that woman was heading toward the headquarters.

If he could confirm the location of this mysterious organization, he might be able to drag Ames along and advance to the high ground.

One slam from Floating Dragon Island, and not just the enemy Nexus, the enemy fountain might not even exist...

Patience was the basic of peeking; there was no use in hurrying. The Observer's Mark would only gain useful information as time went on.

Han Xiao went to the training room and tested his new talent for a while, then gave a lesson to Sylvia and Reynold, followed by letting Sylvia report the matters of the army. After he was done with those things, he shut himself in the machinery modification room and went into solitude.

Shana's attack had put him under some pressure. If all her friends had about Grade A+ strength, they would be strong opponents that he had never faced before. Han Xiao planned to build a batch of non-metallic machines and magnetic field reversal devices to nullify Shana's Esper ability.

With plenty of Experience in his bag, Han Xiao was not worried about spending. He gambled a lot of blueprints and found quite a lot of useful ones.

Including the blueprints, he already had more than a thousand abilities. The effect of [Research Theory] now gave him more than three hundred bonus Intelligence.

Building non-metallic machines was one part of becoming stronger; Han Xiao also felt it was time to increase his level.

He was now level 170 and stuck at the Class Advancement mission of [Galaxy Mechanic]. If he completed the Class Advancement, his strength would be largely increased once again. He would also obtain the crucial Mechanic abilities of the next stage.

The Class Advancement requirement was very direct—learn one Cutting-Edge Knowledge.

However, it was not easy for Han Xiao.

In his previous life when the players were at this level, it was already the later versions. After playing for so long and experiencing so many main storylines, the players had built up relationships with several factions by that time, so they could exchange Cutting-Edge Knowledge directly.

However, Han Xiao was too ahead of the schedule. Limited by the version, he did not have the chance to farm the relationship with any Star Cluster Civilizations. Hence, this Class Advancement requirement that was quite easy in his previous life suddenly became an obstacle.

It was not difficult to do, but it took a lot of time and effort.

Han Xiao had used up the random rewards that he had stocked up. Being unlucky as always, he did not get any Mission Completion Cards.

Mission Completion Cards were actually really cheap and not rare at all. Most of the things he got in these random rewards had a higher value than Mission Completion Cards, such as the rare Esper Ability Potential Enhancing Fluid that he had shockingly obtained twice. Including one from long ago, he now had three of them.

He kept feeling that trying to obtain Mission Completion Cards after touching Feidin was having the opposite effect.

Cutting-Edge Knowledges were a must learn, so Han Xiao did not want to gamble on Mission Completion Cards. What he hoped now was that the Purple Crystal Civilization could quickly form its Section Zero. During the [Crimson Tide], faction missions were in the least shortage.

At the outer space track outside the Purple Crystal Civilization's Mother Planet, a garrison satellite code-named 'Curved Blade' was circling the mother planet. This was a newly built space station, an office for a new department. This department's members were all elites selected from the various departments within the Secret Service.

At this time, inside the Curved Blade garrison satellite station, a row of Foreign Affairs Captains were sitting in the office of the highest commander, staring at the top commander of this department, Ralph.

Ralph flipped through the report of these people and listened as the captains explained the situation.

"The candidate list for the partner organizations has been sorted. There's a total of 173 new organizations selected, all of which we have contacted and are willing to work with us. Please take a look."

"It's too few," Ralph said coldly. In front of his subordinates, he was very strict.

"From an entire Star Cluster's perspective, it is indeed not many. However, the 173 candidate organizations are the result of our careful selection. They all have Calamity Grades in their organization, a compulsory requirement. They are spread across the various Star Systems in Colton, and all are renowned among the locals."

"Such as?"

"Severide's Arc Light Organization, Skywalker's Hero Group, Rain's New Phylen Rebels... These are the largest and strongest organizations among the candidates."

"It's still not enough. The strength of these unofficial military organizations is far from the forces gathered by Klent." Ralph shook his head in dissatisfaction. "The development of private organizations in Colton is too chaotic. Klent has the Bloodshed Land. Just that alone is enough to stop all of our partnered organizations. Klent has been helping its ally, the Bloodshed Land, expand over the years, fusing about half of the private organizations in their territory. Klent wants to build an alliance organization using the Bloodshed Land as its core. In the face of such an enormous organization, these partner organizations we've found will have no chance of resisting. If they want to start a secret war, we will have absolutely no chance of winning."

"Indeed. The enemy has the Bloodshed Land. If we don't use our official army, no one can stop the Tyrant. However, Beyond Grade As won't act easily. We also have Beyond Grade A too; the Dragon Emperor is here."

"However, Dragon Emperor Ames remains neutral. She isn't our ally." Ralph frowned.

"The Black Star Army is on the list of partner organizations. Although he cannot be compared with these three strongest candidates I just mentioned, their strength can be ranked in the second tier within the list. Their background is the military force of Floating Dragon. Maybe we can use the Dragon Emperor's power through him."

"I know Black Star; he's a very smart guy. Don't try to use him to get close to Ames. Plus, Ames might not be as strong as Heber." Ralph shook his head.

After a pause, he continued to warn his subordinates. "Klent is still holding back currently, but they will become more and more rampant. The secret war will happen sooner or later. The people above have made the call; we cannot be forced by the enemy to use our official army, or an all-out war might really break out. Klent wants to snatch parts of Colton's territory. Even if the three Universal Civilizations come to stop the war, the Crimson Dynasty is behind Klent. We are at a disadvantage politically, so we might be forced to sign an unfair treaty. I'm not satisfied with the current list. The reason that this department was created is to deal with Klent's ambitious expansions. You must get more military forces."

"Understood!"

"Also, the people above have given this department an official code name. When the time comes, you will notify the candidates of the name of this organization formed by all the partnered forces."

"What's the code name?"

Ralph knocked on the table and solemnly said, "Secret Service, Section Zero!"

Chapter 638: In the Chaotic Crimson Tide, Storms Are Forming (2)

In the Seoul Star Cluster, Klent Kingdom territory, Bloodshed Land headquarters, Planet Heber...

Inside Heber's palace, the emissary from Klent met with Tyrant to deliver the message from his superiors.

"The Purple Crystal Civilization eliminated the scouting team that we sent to Colton. This is their warning. According to the information transmitted back, the people that attacked the scouting team were all private forces in the Colton Star Cluster. This means that Purple Crystal is creating an alliance. We need to make the corresponding reaction."

"You guys need my help."

"Yes. In these two years, Klent has been helping you assemble many private military forces in the Seoul Star Cluster. The size of the Bloodshed Land is many times bigger than two years ago. We plan to form an alliance force with you as its core and secretly invade the Colton Star Cluster, starting a secret war with the Purple Crystal Civilization."

"Okay." Heber gave a short and simple reply.

"Although the Dragon Emperor Ames is in Colton, she is basically neutral. However, the Black Star Army under her seems to be on Purple Crystal's side. If Ames interferes, we hope you can deal with her."

"When it's necessary, I will." Heber shook his head.

Back at the party, Dragon Emperor and Black Star did not directly reject the Crimson Dynasty's invitation. After that, they did not make any decision. However, even if the Floating Dragon decided to choose the Crimson Dynasty's side, they were still not his ally. The two of them had different goals and were in two opposing Star Cluster Civilizations. The Crimson Dynasty did not mind their chess pieces fighting each other. The more chaotic the situation, the better.

Klent was willing to step forward and execute the Crimson Dynasty's belief of being as high profile as possible. With such a strong backer, Klent had been more and more daring over the prior two years, especially toward neutral civilizations not under any of the three Universal Civilizations such as Purple Crystal.

The Seoul Star Cluster under Klent's rule was the second smallest Star Cluster in all of the Shattered Star Ring, as well as Colton's neighbor. Klent was very ambitious; their goal was not only just taking a bite on the profits of the Flickering World but also to get their hands on the Colton Star Cluster. Although they maintained a good relationship with Purple Crystal on the surface, they secretly wanted to snatch a few Star Systems from Purple Crystal.

Of course, this would not have worked out in the past. However, now that the Crimson Dynasty wanted to stir things up, the restriction of the peace treaty suddenly became much weaker. The strong had the right to make rules. The laws and balance in the galaxy seemed unbreakable in the eyes of normal people, but to the three Universal Civilizations, they were very fragile. The other civilizations were just players that had to obey the game rules they had set.

Even Heber felt that the Klents were very greedy.

However, this suited what he wanted. He needed an ambitious ally, not an ally content with what they had. The greedier they were, the more they would rely on him.

Heber stood up. His gigantic body cast a shadow over the Klent emissary.

"I understand what Klent wants. Go back and tell your boss that I will be in charge of this war. They don't have to worry about anything."

The Klent emissary nodded and smiled with the confidence of a certain victory.

The difference between the Bloodshed Land and the alliance force built by Purple Crystal was like an iron fist and a plate of sand. For this secret war, Klent had been preparing for two years. Purple Crystal's reaction only came much later. This meant that they were at a disadvantage before the war even started.

With the Tyrant, Heber, taking care of the situation, demolishing Purple Crystal's alliance force was just a matter of time.

Through continuous victories, the Bloodshed Land had never disappointed Klent before.

...

Shana returned to the headquarters that were shockingly in an area so remote it was the desolate area at the edge of the Shattered Star Ring. There was absolutely nobody around; it was a truly unpopulated area.

All the Star Fields had desolate areas that very few stepped into. Their characteristics as a whole were that there were very few planets, hardly any resources, and no signs of life. Some wanted or mysterious organizations would occasionally choose these desolate areas as the location for their headquarters.

When Shana entered the headquarters, all of her colleagues were waiting. Other than Eliot, there were four others. They all wore different masks and gave off a vibe of unfathomable strength. They were all looking at Shana.

With a husky voice like an old man at the end of his days, a short man among them slowly said, "You failed and exposed your face. For the next few years, you will replace Adrian to guard the headquarters. He will go out to carry out missions with Eliot.

"Humph." Shana was not happy about it but did not object. This was their internal rule. In order for them not to be targeted by anyone, once someone failed, the person working in the field had to be swapped.

This secret organization had very few members, but they were all elites.

Adrian was a muscular and tall male being with the characteristics of a Beastman. He took out a palm-sized metal disk and threw to Shana. "It's your turn to guard the headquarters. Enjoy the boring times."

This metal disk was one of the specially made keys of the jail inside the headquarters. There were four of those keys.

All the captured targets on the list would be locked up in the prison. Usually, four of them would be guarding the headquarters, and two of them would go out to capture the targets on the list. This was their usual way of doing things.

Eliot shrugged and said, "Looks like we can't be partners. Shame, I always thought we worked very well together."

Adrian pointed at himself and said, "I'm your old partner, too."

Eliot shrugged and replied, "Other than Mister Albert, all of you have been my partner before."

Albert was the short, old man, the leader of this team, and had always been guarding the headquarters.

Adrian had never failed, so he was the only one that had never been swapped out. All the other four had been his partner before.

"Now, let's talk about the problem regarding Black Star." Albert stared at Shana. "Due to your failure, we now have the risk of being exposed. Black Star is now alert and will actively look for our whereabouts. We have two choices; one is to ignore Black Star and wait for the dust to settle before we move again. The other is to capture him as soon as possible and eliminate the risk of being exposed. Then, we keep a low profile afterward..."

"I've done some research on him," Shana suddenly said. "Previously, the Garton Star System's DarkStar organization did not take him seriously at the start and was destroyed by him. This man is very dangerous. We can't leave him be."

Albert nodded and said, "Makes sense. He's dangerous. Eliot, Adrian, the only target of your next mission is Black Star. You must capture him. If you can't capture him alive no matter what, I allow you to eliminate him."

"Alright." Eliot nodded.

"Mister Albert, I have fought with Black Star before and could not make him show his 'Indestructible Body'. He must have hidden more strong abilities. Two people won't be enough. My ability counters his, so please let me join the mission," Shana said with a deep voice.

Albert contemplated and felt that it was reasonable. He told Shana to give him the key and said, "Okay, I'll make an exception this time. The three of you will work together. Don't be reckless. Only act after you're absolutely certain you'll succeed."

Shana nodded. Revenge was just part of the reason she insisted on joining the mission; more of it was just as she had said. Although she had lost, she remembered the fight, and her ability was indeed very suitable for dealing with Black Star.

"Klent seems to be starting to move. Apparently, they're going to start a fight with the Purple Crystal Civilization. Black Star should be involved in it, so we'll have plenty of chances."

Eliot smiled. He was a Grade A+ Super, and the other two were close to Grade A+, but the opponent was just Black Star alone.

He felt that success was certain.

...

At the same time, inside Base No.1 of the Black Star Army...

"Tsk tsk, three people just to deal with me, how scary."

Through the Observer's Mark, Han Xiao watched the conversation between Shana and the others like watching a movie.

After waiting for many days, Han Xiao had finally obtained valuable information from the Observer's Mark. He was quite shocked.

He suspected Shana to be Grade A+, so the other two would not be weaker than her. Sending all three of them to capture him... Did I dig up your ancestor's grave? Do you people really have to send such an elite team after me?

Nonetheless, Han Xiao did not panic. After all, the problem was massive, so there was no use in panicking.

With my strength, the chance of winning against these three is negligible. Even if I'm very tanky and might not be killed, I will most likely be captured. If these six people have about the same strength, they could capture just about anyone under Beyond Grade A.

Being targeted by these people. Han Xiao felt heavy pressure.

These people seemed to be obeying orders to capture people. Han Xiao had a feeling that the six people whom he had just seen were merely the tip of the iceberg of this mysterious organization.

However, not only was Han Xiao not panicking, he almost wanted to laugh.

Originally, the situation was that the enemies were hidden, and he was in the open. If Shana did not join the mission, he would not have been able to guard against the sudden attack of the enemies.

However, Shana insisted on joining the mission and became a moving ward that allowed Han Xiao to monitor their movements at all times.

Such a great teammate!

This ward was more than worth it.

Han Xiao could not help but feel glad about how careful these people were. If they headed there right away, he would indeed be in quite a tough situation.

Hmm, let me think, how I should welcome them...

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and pondered.

Chapter 639: This Talent Is Wonderful to the Point I Don't Want to Upgrade It

The situation was extremely clear. Three of them were coming after him, and three others were staying behind in the base to guard their camp.

However, he could only spy on a single party. The problem was how Han Xiao should maximize his benefits.

He was considering how he could nab all the enemies in one fell swoop and also complete a few more phases of the [Prey] mission. Such a mission that could give him the opportunity to draw the abilities of a Grade A Super was extremely rare. If he was lucky, his strength could undergo a massive increase.

There seems to be only six enemies. I needed to think of a way to get rid of them all without alerting them, Han Xiao pondered to himself. The situation is now reversed. The enemy is out in the open while I am in the dark. This is my biggest advantage, and I need to make use of it well.

Should I deal with Shana and her group or attack the main camp of the enemy first?

All the trump cards that I can mobilize include the Black Star Army, my connections in the mercenary world, Ames' support, and the organizations behind those on that hit list. If the powerhouses captured by the enemy are all in the main camp, I'll be able to easily convince the organizations behind them to work together and fight the enemy. Every single enemy is extremely powerful alone, and their advantage is their high mobility. It would be extremely troublesome if even a single person escapes.

Han Xiao shook his head and felt that he could not attack their main camp under such circumstances. No matter what, the three who were keeping guard seemed to have the strength of Grade A+ as well. Even if he invited the Dragon Emperor to take action, the enemy would still have time to contact their comrades. The moment he alerted the enemy, it was extremely likely for the three on the outside to split up and escape. At that time, he would only be able to capture Shana, not the other two.

After considering for a while, Han Xiao also eliminated the plan of splitting up his forces. It would be a far more complex operation with too many factors that could go wrong. If he chose to split his forces, choosing how to allocate his forces would be a huge problem. After all, the enemy were not weaklings, and they might have some strange escaping abilities.

I shall do it this way...

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

If he wanted to attack the enemy's main camp, he would want all the enemies to gather together first to capture them all in one fell swoop.

If he captured Shana's group of three, he would not be able to spy on the rest. If he only captured one of the three, the enemy might shift their main camp due to fear of being exposed. The moment they entered the depths of the unexplored region of the universe, it would be extremely difficult to give chase.

Han Xiao pondered for a moment and decided on a plan. He would only fight off Shana's group of three and cause them to fail again. The other party would then return to their base for sure, and the six of them would be gathered together. He would just have to gather his troops and gain the high ground. He would not allow a single enemy to escape and could even save all the captured Grade A Supers.

For the sake of secrecy, Han Xiao decided to wait for Shana's group of three to find him. Taking the initiative to attack them would only reveal the fact that he had locked onto their position.

He felt that the role of hunter and prey had been swapped. He was like a hunter patiently waiting for the prey to step into his trap.

However, I have to find some helpers first.

Han Xiao opened up his communicator, and an endless list of leaders from the various organizations appeared.

In the office of Section Zero, Ralph was staring at his communicator with his brows locked as though he was troubled over a huge problem. His secretary did not dare disturb him.

In truth, the communicator was currently showing a galactic entertainment program, and he was avoiding work.

It could not be helped. The mission of scouting for private organizations fell on the shoulder of the envoys. Even if the mission to organize an alliance was extremely urgent, he could only wait for the envoys to complete their mission first. The war had not begun yet, and there was no point in him being anxious.

Right at this moment, an incoming call sprung up from his communicator and disrupted his show.

Ralph picked up the incoming call without a change in expression. It was Han Xiao.

"Black Star, it is rare for you to take the initiative to contact me."

"I have already received your notice. How many people are there in Section Zero right now?"

Not too long ago, Purple Crystal had sent out the name of the alliance to all those involved in the alliance. Han Xiao had also received news of it.

This organization was only in its infancy, so the structure of the organization had not been formed. They did not know the names of the other participants of the organization, and no notification of a new faction popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

"The members of Section Zero are temporarily a secret. We will gather all the members when it is formed officially. You will know who the members are then."

In his past life, the players only saw the organization in Version 3.0, which was perfected during the time of the update. This time, Han Xiao was personally joining the organization from the very start.

Han Xiao chuckled and could briefly remember which organizations joined Section Zero in the end. However, he felt that he had an opportunity to change the storyline this time.

"I have an idea to allow Section Zero to recruit more experts."

Ralph's eyes lit up. "Let's hear your plan..."

The Light Rune Civilization was the ruler of the Thousand Lights Star System. Of the many Star System level civilizations of the Colton Star Cluster, the Light Rune Civilization had always been an open supporter of Purple Crystal. The level of the Light Rune Civilization exceeded an ordinary Star System level civilization, and they had a close relationship with Purple Crystal.

Recently, the person in charge of Light Rune Civilization's national defense, Kemas, had been extremely frustrated.

It was because the most powerful expert of the Light Rune Civilization, Kernid, had disappeared on his holiday. The higher ups were enraged and ordered him to locate Kernid.

Kemas was heavily pressured by his higher ups to find Kernid. However, the pressure from his higher ups was not the only reason. Kernid was his biological brother, and it would be impossible for him to keep his current position without Kernid. As such, Kemas was more anxious to find his brother than anyone else.

However, he did not have a single clue. Kemas had already applied for aid from the Purple Crystal Civilization but to no avail. He was truly frustrated to the point his body hair was about to drop.

Ring ring!

Right at this moment, his communicator rang—his secretary was calling.

"Your Excellency Kemas, someone is requesting to speak to you."

"Who is it?" Kemas suppressed the frustration in his heart. His secretary was the one in charge of managing his incoming calls, and for his secretary to personally contact him, it meant that the caller definitely had a significant status.

"He is the leader of the Black Star Army, Black Star of the Garton Star System."

"Oh, so it's him." Kemas had heard of such an individual before, and it seemed like he was creating a storm in Godora. Despite being doubtful of why Black Star was looking for him, it would not be good for him to treat the other party rudely. Thus, he got his secretary to divert the call over.

The holographic screen lit up, and Han Xiao's face appeared.

"Kemas? I haven't got the wrong person, right?"

"It's me, Black Star. Why have you called for me?"

Han Xiao stroked his chin and said, "I heard from Purple Crystal that you guys are looking for someone called Kernid."

"Yes." Kemas was not aware of what Han Xiao's intentions were and thus gave a short reply.

"What if I say that I may know his whereabouts? Will you guys be willing to work with me?"

The moment Han Xiao said those words, Kemas' expression changed, and his breathing became heavy as though he was stimulated.

The Star Beast Organization was a special armed organization that was located in another Star Cluster. It was in an alliance with the Star Cluster level civilization that ruled the Star Cluster.

This organization was extremely famous in the Shattered Star Ring and their specialty was the ability to control various dangerous galactic beasts. They did not like to expand and chose to maintain neutrality most of the time. They would never sell or rent their beasts but only provide them to the Star Cluster Civilization that they were in an alliance with.

Their specialty came from the Esper ability of their leader, Gobili. He had a monstrous level of affinity with beasts and was able to control various different types of beasts over long periods of time. If these beasts remained under the influence of his ability for long periods of time, they even had a chance of evolving and mutating.

However, the Star Beast Organization was in a complete mess at this moment because their leader had disappeared.

The vice commander had sent out numerous search parties, but he could not find a single clue.

If their leader was gone, their organization was finished.

Everyone in the Star Beast Organization was filled with grievances. Don't we only like to rear pets? We only rear pets in our homes and do not provoke anyone. Why do others still have to come and provoke us‽

Just when they were on the brink of collapse, the vice commander received a call from Han Xiao.

"I am Black Star from the Colton Star Cluster. You may or may not have heard of my name before. However, that isn't important. The important thing is that I may know the location of your leader. Are you interested in working with me?"

The same scene happened in various locations throughout the Shattered Star Ring. Han Xiao called all the organizations of the names listed on the hit list.

With his huge network, finding these numbers was a piece of cake. His chain of calls immediately mobilized a large number of organizations.

As for the ones who were on the list but had not been caught, he could only say wrong number.

Just as he was gathering aid in secret, Shana's group of three was also approaching the Garton Star System.

On the spaceship, the three of them were discussing their strategy.

"Black Star may be on high alert this time. I feel that we shouldn't take care of him immediately." Eliot shook his head. He had always been a calm individual. However, since Albert had given his orders, he could only follow the orders.

"Not necessarily. I did not reveal much information, and Black Star may think that I am only seeking revenge. This is a very common thing for a leader of his status."

Shana shook her head and felt that her loss was not that big a deal. The way she saw it, Black Star was definitely puzzled about her origin.

"We should still be careful no matter what." Eliot paused to think for a moment before continuing. "It is said that Black Star has an undying body with his subordinates being immortals. A long, drawn-out battle will be to his advantage, so we must come up with a plan to take him down quickly."

"Should we wait for him to be alone before attacking?"

"Not necessarily. After facing an ambush recently, Black Star will definitely be more careful when he is alone. We should strike him at the most unexpected moment."

"What should we do?"

"Hmm... I know. He doesn't recognize me and Adrian. I can use a spell to conceal our aura and appearance to mix with the mercenaries and attack him from up close. The two of us shall control him, and you will take action to capture him. The three of us will then retreat immediately. With the three of us working together, we should be able to take care of him very quickly."

"If that's the case, we can take action in his base."

"Yes, this way, he will be caught off guard. The other mercenaries in the base won't be able to stop us, and he won't have other Calamity Grade helpers this time."

Adrian then spoke in a muffled voice. "I understand. We want to deal a lightning fast strike and not give him the chance to react."

Eliot nodded.

Shana pondered for a moment and also felt that it was a good plan. She could not think of how Black Star would be able to escape from their grasp this time.

Meanwhile, Black Star was on his way to Floating Dragon Island.

"Oh, I see." Han Xiao now understood their plan.

Chapter 640: Ambush

Han Xiao had convened a large group of helpers, with the core person being 'Long Legs' Ames.

He had rarely returned to Floating Dragon Island in the past two years, only occasionally communicating with Ames. The high amount of trust Ames had in him meant that he could move around in his own activities outside and not be doubted.

When the spaceship landed at the dock, Han Xiao walked out of the hatch to see Wilsander waiting for him. Every time Han Xiao returned, he would be the one to fetch him with great enthusiasm.

Looking around, Han Xiao did not spot the figure of Jenny, which made him a little surprised.

"Why didn't Jenny come? I thought she would come and give me a few jabs."

"She's very busy, no time for you." Wilsander grinned.

"It seems like she is still very dedicated to her role."

Han Xiao laughed in return.

Wilsander rolled his eyes in response. Is her dedication not forced by your activities?

After a brief greeting, Han Xiao headed directly to the palace.

In the past two years, Ames had remained on Floating Dragon Island, attentively training Hila and Aurora. Upon hearing that Han Xiao had come to visit, the three of them were quite happy.

Rising from her throne, Ames floated up to Han Xiao as she smiled. "It's been a while. I've missed you. What's your reason for coming this time?"

"Can't I return to see you if I have no time?" Han Xiao smiled. "But I do need your help this time."

"Let's hear it."

Han Xiao briefly explained the situation. He did not intend to ask Ames to deal with Shana and company but rather utilize her pressure to suppress the enemy whilst he stormed the base, to ensure complete control on his part.

At the same time, this was an opportunity. He had gathered many influential people from around the Shattered Star Ring and stationed them to ambush from a secret location. The moment he pushed back Shana and company, they would join forces to destroy the mysterious force's camp and rescue all the Supers. With so many various influences, if Ames was present to hold the fort, she would be able to command all these influences with her title of a Beyond Grade A Super.

To call in so many organizations just to deal with six Grade A Supers was akin to using a butcher's knife to slaughter chickens. However, his greater goal was to turn this into sensational news, to further expand his own influence.

With so many organizations under the lead of Floating Dragon, this cooperation would be able to reverse the public impression of Floating Dragon. Floating Dragon would also rise from a powerless neutral faction into a powerful one. Even if this was a misunderstanding, it would prove useful.

The general consensus was that among the four Beyond Grade A Supers within the Shattered Star Ring, Ames power was the weakest. This time, their knowledge of Ames would be refreshed.

While one's true strength could not be improved quickly, influence and connections could serve as a shortcut. The stronger Floating Dragon was, the more it would be able to protect itself.

Moreover, after fighting side by side, if they managed to save all the Supers from the powerful organizations, they would owe Floating Dragon a debt of gratitude. This would form a good relationship between the latter with the rest of the powerful organizations. While the organizations definitely had some status, they would give some face toward the prestige of a Beyond Grade A Super, and Han Xiao, through Floating Dragon, would be able to convert the forces into his connections.

Han Xiao had always attached great importance to organizations. After all, the universe was so large, an individual was limited in scope. Even Beyond Grade A Supers needed aides. One's individual combat power and organization strength had to be grasped with both hands, and both hands had to firmly hold on to each area.

Sooner or later, there would yet be another version update. The players would disappear for about a decade once more. During this period, if he wished to prevent the faction from sinking, he needed to be pre-emptive and search for external support.

After hearing the explanation from Han Xiao, Ames did not hesitate and immediately agreed.

She fully supported Han Xiao, and besides, having been cooped up for so long, she wished to go out and stretch her muscles, at the same time allowing Aurora and Hila to get some experience.

Hila and Aurora had stood to the side without interrupting once. After two years, their temperament had shown changes once again.

Ames had taught them how to develop their abilities, and Hila's aura had become colder, whilst the exact opposite had happened for Aurora, who had become sunnier and warmer.

In the area of strength, Hila had made rapid progress. She initially already possessed a strength of Grade C. Coupled with her own talents, it did not take much guidance from Ames for her to breakthrough and enter the realm of Grade B.

As for Aurora, her battle role was to be a super nanny. While her rank was not as high, her abilities got strengthened a lot more.

Hila's appearance did not change much, but she had received a life sublimation, allowing her to become more beautiful and elegant. Aurora did not grow much in height, but her figure showed obvious signs of becoming a real 'milkmaid'[1]. The front of her Battle Suit was packed tightly.

Her ability gave her frightening vitality, and with three nutritious meals a day, her appearance did not pale in comparison to her sister's.

Glancing at Aurora's chest, Han Xiao sighed. "Your training is too tough. Just look, how could a girl like you be beaten so hard that you are so swollen?"

Aurora could hear the teasing in Han Xiao's voice and immediately blushed. She did not wish for herself to become this huge, but this was linked to her abilities. She had no choice, and she even had to bear the soreness in her shoulders every day. If only she was able to remove them and put them in her pockets instead, that would be so good!

Having not seen him for two years, while Hila's expression remained passive, she was a little excited in her heart. However, upon hearing those words from Han Xiao, her face immediately darkened. She stared daggers at Han Xiao as though wishing to rip off his face. However, the result was that she could not do anything to his face, and Han Xiao even ignored her.

Han Xiao also brought up the issue of Section Zero and expressed his intention to work for the Purple Crystal Civilization for a period of time. Ames had no objections, brushing off everything. Jenny could only grit her teeth and inwardly curse.

Han Xiao secretly gathered his helpers, and after making sufficient preparations, he looked for one of his bases that was not so important and camped there, waiting for the enemy to step into the trap.

This base was located on one of the colonial planets of Godora. Many players often chose to settle there, and choosing this place as the battlefield had been carefully considered by Han Xiao. This was to paint a positive image in the eyes of the players. This face engineering process was extremely important.

At this moment, the Black Star Army had already completed the function of guiding the faction into the universe. Han Xiao's next objective was to retain the players and focus on managing the Black Star Army.

Starting from the next version, there would be a multitude of factions available to choose from. Many of them were combined organizations, which could offer large benefits and large main storylines. The players would inevitably be tempted. Han Xiao had to maintain the attractiveness of his faction, so as the leader, he had to continue to improve the players' impression of him.

After waiting for a few days, Shana's group finally moved. In fact, they had arrived in the Garton Star System much earlier, always monitoring the movements of Han Xiao.

Han Xiao was doing the same thing to them. The Chain Mission [Prey] had already released the second mission earlier on.

The mission requirement was to repel the attack of the three people. In addition to the high experience provided, he would receive a random reward of an ability from the trio. Han Xiao predicted that this series of difficult missions would each provide an additional special reward of being able to draw an ability. As long as his luck was good, he would be able to profit handsomely off this.

Because this was a colonial planet that belonged to Godora, the attacking trio did not wish to make too much noise, opting to use stealth and assassination tactics instead. They wanted to get Black Star and quickly evacuate.

Eliot was responsible for the advanced concealment and camouflage. While the base had access restrictions, in front of the abilities of a Grade A Super, it was useless. Adrian and Eliot very easily sneaked into the base without alerting Phillip, whilst Shana remained outside.

The camouflage technique that Eliot used turned them into common mercenaries. Eliot was extremely confident of his techniques, thinking them unbreakable. The two of them swaggered into the area, as though it was their own backyard.

However, after walking a short distance, they noticed that something was off. All around them, it seemed that the Black Star Mercenaries all started to turn around and look at them with weird expressions, as though they were out of place.

"I feel that the situation is a little weird," Adrian whispered.

"Could it be that we've been discovered? That's not possible. How can my technique be seen through so easily?" Eliot refused to believe it.

His deception was indeed effective, and the players around them could not see any sort of information about them. Even their names appeared as '???'.

However, the question marks for both Eliot and Adrian were bright red!

Two red-named people representing enemies walking around scared the players stiff. No one knew what sort of situation this was.

While Brock was part of DarkStar, he was an undercover agent. Furthermore, DarkStar had already kicked the bucket. Before he joined Black Star, he had merely appeared as a yellow name, but since Eliot and Adrian were downright enemies to Black Star, they appeared red named in the eyes of the players, the most dazzling attraction in this place.

Boom boom boom!

A player suddenly opened fire at the two of them, and the surrounding players immediately followed suit. A barrage of bullets enveloped the two of them, and a violent explosion sounded.

While the players were unaware of what was going on, they decided that since they were red names, they might somehow trigger a mission and earn something.

Hum!

The magic shield was deployed, blocking all attacks.

"We've been exposed!" Eliot was shocked. He could not understand it. How did all those Grade C mercenaries crack his seamless camouflage‽

At this moment, Han Xiao, who had long prepared himself, appeared, floating in the sky as he overlooked the two. He put on a show, pretending that he was not aware of their origin.

"The last time I was attacked, I felt that something was amiss. Indeed, there are people targeting me. To think I actually managed to wait for you to arrive. Who are you guys?"

Eliot did not reply, merely shouting lowly. All sorts of magic was deployed, and Adrian's body began to increase in size.

When Shana realized that her teammates had been exposed, she immediately acted by tearing apart the walls of the base. She was prepared to join them in attacking Black Star. With three Grade A+ Supers present, they could just forcefully suppress Black Star and end the battle quickly.

However, Han Xiao leisurely dodged their attacks, saying, "Did you think I did not do any preparations beforehand?"

Just as his voice fell, strong auras exploded from the sides of the base. Nagakin as well as two other Godoran Grade A Supers shot out from the hiding spots.

Han Xiao had gathered the other organizations for the sake of attacking the enemies' base camp. Thus, his goal here was just to repel the three of them, and as such, he had chosen the Godoran Colonial planet, which would allow him to request assistance from Godora. Without overwhelming suppression on his side, it would allow things to flow more naturally and allow Shana's group to 'escape'.

The Black Star Army had close ties with Godora, so this small request was merely a phone call away from Han Xiao. Nagakin was extremely glad to help.

Eliot furrowed his brows. They were faced with four Grade A Supers, and while they were not afraid, they had no way of forcing a quick end to the battle. This was Godoran territory; the moment they got entangled, Godora's fleet would be able to give them no small amount of trouble.

The three of them exchanged glances, immediately coming to the same consensus.

Black Star was just too vigilant. Merely a single attack, and without knowing their histories, he decided to make a mountain out of a molehill. It seemed like he was a cautious yet decisive person.

The three of them did not once suspect that their whereabouts had been leaked. Han Xiao pretended that he was using his stupid idea to wait for a reward, and this did not raise their doubts. They were confident enough that their actions were secretive.

Furthermore, if Black Star knew that they had three people, then he would not have brought along just three other Calamity Grades.

Han Xiao continued with his performance, speaking in a deep tone. "You have no way of escaping. No matter who you are, I'll find out your origins today."

"You're overconfident in being able to stop us. You can try!" Eliot snorted.

Just four Calamity Grades would not be enough to enter his eyes. Maybe only Black Star would give them some difficulty.

The three of them did not panic, for they were confident in their own capabilities. Black Star could not stop them with so few people; they could leave as and when they wished to.

[1] The original phrase can be read as either 'nanny' or 'milk mother/maid', so I decided to go with the latter to convey what the author wanted to say Back

Chapter 641: Mid Lane High Ground, Come for a Team Fight.

The battle erupted in an instant. The impact caused by seven Calamity Grades was tremendous!

The shockwave destroyed about half of the entire base, and the streets nearby became a wreck. Many players were blown away. Their level limit was currently 90, so just the shockwave alone had already taken away a bar of their health. There was nothing they could do.

Boom!

It was a battle between seven Calamity Grade Supers. Even with Han Xiao, Nagakin, and the other two trying to control the damage, it still caused quite a lot of destruction. However, Han Xiao did not mind how badly the base was damaged. Only the surface buildings were damaged, and it was cheap to rebuild them. Furthermore, he was already at the level of "I'm not interested in money", so he did not mind paying such a small price to lure these three people.

This was the second time that he had fought Shana. Han Xiao had built a team of non-metallic mechanical soldiers, mainly elites. They were strong and powerful under his Mechanical Force bonuses. It was difficult for Shana to counter him, so she could only fight him directly.

Eliot was a very strong Mage; he used all sorts of high-level spells like it was nothing and clearly was not even using his full strength. Adrian was a typical muscular man, taking on the job of a meat shield, holding back three Pugilists including Nagakin alone.

The three of them cooperated with each other very well. Nagakin and the others were no match. Han Xiao was 'doing his best' controlling the mechanical soldiers to attack. It seemed like he was having an intense fight with Shana.

Nagakin and his two colleagues were all Pugilists. Their raw strength was grossly inferior to the three opponents. Just Adrian alone could stall the three of them. They were instantly at a disadvantage. However, Eliot and the other two had no intention of continuing fighting. They kept retreating, and the battlefield kept moving.

Black Star had set up an ambush, so the fight would not end quickly. This was a Godoran planet, so there were fleets stationed nearby. Eliot and the rest did not want to be surrounded by the garrison. They planned to retreat as soon as possible, and they were very confident in doing so.

This was because Eliot knew how to use the teleportation spell, which was outstanding for escaping. Black Star would be dreaming if he thought that he could capture them. Therefore, Eliot thought that it was really funny. He did not know where Black Star got his confidence.

Whoosh!

This time, the sound of spaceships came from the edge of the sky. A fleet stationed there quickly reacted, and about a hundred battleships were approaching as backup.

"There's no need to fight the Godoran fleet. Let's go."

Eliot told Adrian to hold back Nagakin and his colleagues, then cast a spell. He then performed a stroke in the air with his finger, and an energy vortex suddenly appeared behind him, which then expanded into a teleportation gate.

"Sh*t, he can teleport!" Nagakin gave an exaggerated shocked expression. Han Xiao glanced at him and could not help but gave a like to his acting skills. His expression was lively, and his eyes had very intense emotions in them. This acting skill of his was definitely Grade A.

Eliot then cast another spell. A huge magic barrier separated all the enemies from him and his two comrades.

The magic shield blocked all the attacks and kept vibrating. Adrian and Shana entered the teleportation gate and disappeared.

With his two colleagues retreating successfully, Eliot looked at Han Xiao and mocked, "Hehe, as I said, you're overconfident. This level of ambush is far from being enough to capture us. We want to leave now—are you able to stop us?"

Han Xiao heard that and made his expression gloomy. He then deliberately said nothing and continued to attack with greater force, pounding loudly on the magic barrier.

In Eliot's eyes, Black Star was turning his embarrassment into fury. He immediately felt better; even the unhappiness from the mission failing diminished quite a bit.

Eliot squinted and suddenly said, "Wait for it. We will come to find you again. There won't always be someone helping you."

Then, Eliot turned and walked into the teleportation gate. The gate disappeared, and the three of them retreated successfully like they could just come and go as they wished.

They're finally gone... Han Xiao finally relaxed his tight facial muscles and uninstalled the 'Angry.jpg' expression bundle.

Although the battle was short, the streets nearby were badly destroyed. The level of strength that the enemies had shown made Nagakin feel a lot of pressure.

"Black Star, who are these people? They're way too strong. They have targeted you, so you've got to be careful," Nagakin said seriously.

"Don't worry, they can't escape."

Now we will just have to wait till they get home... Han Xiao smiled but said no more.

Eliot exposed his teleportation spell, which was bonus information that Han Xiao did not expect to obtain. This was a god-tier escaping ability. Had they not made any preparations for it, the enemies might have escaped when they attacked their base. Now that he knew about this, he could think of ways to deal with it.

Thinking that Eliot and the rest thought that they had successfully escaped, Han Xiao almost burst into laughter.

Things were going even better than he had expected!

After contacting the construction team to repair the base and getting rid of a huge number of players trying to trigger missions, Han Xiao used the Observer's Mark and peeked at those three's whereabouts.

The range of the teleportation gate that Eliot had hurriedly created on the spot would not be too far. The teleportation gate was connected to their spaceship, which orbiting the colonial planet.

As soon as they returned to the ship, they activated its stealth mode and went far away from the planet, preventing the garrison from chasing after them.

The escape was successful. The three of them did not even suspect that Han Xiao had purposely let them go. They retreated with Eliot's ability. There was nothing suspicious about it. They just thought that Black Star had misjudged their strength and did not set up a strong enough ambush.

Making Black Star's ambush a failure was nothing to the three of them. They felt that it was normal.

"This mission has failed. Should we continue looking for opportunities?" Shana asked.

Eliot shook his head. "Black Star is very cautious. After just one attack, he made a trap purely out of suspicion. Now that he has been attacked a second time, he will be certain that we're his enemies. He will only be more alert from now on. We can't attack him again for a short period."

After what had just happened, the only thing they could do was leave Black Star be for the moment.

His threat before leaving was just a scare technique to make Black Star keep being cautious about them so that he would always be afraid, alert, and careful, only to realize in the end that it was all for nothing.

Annoyed, Shana frowned and said, "That's our only choice."

"Hmm, I will suggest this to Albert and put Black Star under the Processing List," Eliot said.

They actually had two hunting lists. One was for the confirmed targets; one was the Processing List. Those on the latter list were targets that they had failed to capture the first time, targets who they had alerted. They would not attack these people any time soon. They had to wait at least a few years until the target let their guard down, only then would they attack again.

Black Star was such a target. Eliot did not want to attack Black Star within five years, and he believed that Albert felt this way.

"You were right. We should have dealt with this by leaving him be." Shana did not expect Black Star to be so cautious.

Eliot smiled and said, "It's not too late. Although we exposed our hostility and let Black Star know that the three of us are targeting him, he knows nothing about our background. It will be useless no matter how much he searches for it. It will only make us keep a low profile for a while at most. He definitely will get no results and will never know who's targeting him.

"As for us, we're hidden and have the upper hand. He can't be this cautious forever.

"Let's return first. We might have to stop making moves for the next few years."

Many had witnessed Black Star being attacked, and the message got out very quickly.

However, there was all sorts of news in the Shattered Star Ring nowadays, and huge matters were occurring all the time. Although Black Star was quite well known in the Colton Star Cluster, he was not famous enough throughout the entire Shattered Star Ring. The news that he had been attacked was like a droplet of water in the sea of news and did not attract much attention.

More than ten days later, Han Xiao arrived at an unpopulated planet in a desolate area nearby after nonstop traveling. This planet that had been desolate for countless years was not remarkably boisterous.

All the forces that Han Xiao had contacted earlier had gathered there. Spaceships were parked everywhere on the planet's surface.

All these forces wanted to find a lost person. They had followed Han Xiao's request and come to this planet. They had all initially thought that they were the only ones, but now that they were there, they were shocked and did not expect Han Xiao to have called so many people.

Many organizations there were well known in the Shattered Star Ring and recognized each other. After a little bit of conversation, they all knew that everyone had assembled for the same reason. They were all stunned. Could all the people that were lost be connected in some ways? What clue had Han Xiao found?

The moment Han Xiao's spaceship got close, everyone noticed it. After Han Xiao landed, all the people surrounded him.

These were all high-level officers of their organizations and very important. Usually, it would be difficult just to meet one of them, but now they were all gathered there. If Heber was there, he might think that someone was imitating his Tyrant Party.

"Black Star, when will we make a move?"

"Where are the enemies? Stop hiding."

When Han Xiao contacted them, he did not say everything and only told them to gather there. Many were unhappy about that.

However, Ames was also there to stabilize the situation. Black Star was Dragon Emperor's officer. Even though the people there all had very strong backgrounds, they did not dare cause trouble.

"The time has come. We will attack the enemy's headquarters together. Your lost friends are imprisoned there..."

Han Xiao explained the situation. Through his Observer's Mark, he confirmed that Shana and the others had returned to their base. The opportunity to get all of them had finally arrived.

Things were different now. Although it had taken many years to take down the Germinal Organization and DarkStar, that was because he had not been strong enough back then.

Now, however, the Black Star Army was rising quickly, and he had become someone important in the Shattered Star Ring. He did not want to have such strong enemies for that long. As soon as there was an opportunity, he would eliminate them and not leave any hidden threats.

So many organizations had sent out their elite troops; their power together could shock any civilization or organization in the Shattered Star Ring. There were dozens of Calamity Grades from different organizations in various areas. It was complete overkill for just six enemies.

The Great Mechanic Han's networking ability was incomparable. The Black Star Networking Group was definitely not an exaggerated title!

The crowd was overjoyed upon hearing this. For the same goal, these organizations were all willing to follow Han Xiao's orders temporarily.

When Han Xiao was communicating with the others, the players that he had brought along were all observing curiously from the back.

He had used a mission to have some players follow along. He did not need them to battle on this trip; he only needed them to be 'reporters' and send the video to the forums. This was the opportunity that he planned to use to deepen his impression and to remind the players of his charisma, increasing his personal charm and the faction's attractiveness.

At the same time, Eliot and the rest returned to their hidden base in the desolate area of the universe.

Albert welcomed them and said, "I've heard about the situation. Leave Black Star be. We will keep a low profile for a while. Everyone stays in the base, don't go outside."

The others nodded. This could effectively avoid risks. They would only start their hunting mission again after hiding for some time.

They instantly threw Black Star to the back of their minds. To them, this matter was already dealt with.

What they did not know was... a disaster was secretly approaching.

Chapter 642: Counterattack

Kernid slowly opened his eyes. In front of him was a transparent light curtain, and outside was an area that looked like a prison. Translucent single person cells were spread evenly throughout the area, and almost every cell had a tenant.

He was one of them.

This was the prison that belonged to Shana and the others. It was to imprison the captured targets on the list.

All the prisoners had specially made mechanical rings on their wrists and ankles. These limited the power of these Grade As. These rings were embedded in their flesh. The rings on their wrists sent out nano-level needles into their blood vessels, hearts, brains, and other vital spots. The mechanical rings on their ankles were Super-Gene suppressors that weakened their recovery speed.

They had collars on their necks, too. These were enchanted with very powerful magic that disabled them from using spells and weakened them. The person that enchanted these spells was clearly much stronger than the prisoners. Hence, the effect was very long-lasting.

Other than this, many drugs were also injected into them, preventing the cells inside their bodies from generating energy.

So many imprisonment methods made these Grade As extremely weak.

On the first day that Kernid was imprisoned, he shockingly realized that the others imprisoned there were all as famous and important as him, if not more. However, they had all been captured and imprisoned there. He was justifiably petrified.

Kernid tried to escape but failed. So many others were unable to escape, and he was no exception. Furthermore, even if he did manage to escape the prison, there would still be enemies guarding and waiting outside, which made him despair.

After being imprisoned for so many days, he had given up and clearly knew that he would not be able to escape by himself. All he could do was pray that someone would come to save him. However, no one had come to save those other prisoners who all had such high positions. He could not help but feel that the chances of escaping were close to none. He was rather pessimistic.

However, speaking of being pessimistic, he was far inferior compared to his neighbor.

A male Spacehuman was imprisoned in the cell beside Kernid. That person had been maintaining a long face the whole time. He looked not just miserable but almost depressed. His name was Lagi[1], a lone Calamity Grade. From what he said, he had been imprisoned there for almost ten years. He was the most senior around.

The days of imprisonment were very boring. Their only entertainment was chatting with each other, trying to find at least a shred of joy in those hopeless days.

When those prisoners were having a good time chatting, as long as Lagi opened his mouth, he would unquestionably shatter the atmosphere.

Everyone there had once been important, and everyone was pessimistic about ending up like this. However, in terms of being pessimistic, Kernid felt that they were all trash compared to Lagi.

This time, the gate of the prison opened. Albert, Shana, and Eliot walked in. The prisoners started an uproar.

"Let me out of here. Do you know who I am‽"

"You've messed with someone you shouldn't mess with. You're going to pay for this!"

"What is your goal‽"

Many spoke with rage. Every time someone came to patrol, they would try to threaten them.

The three of them ignored the prisoners completely. They were not there to check on the prisoners as per schedule today. Due to the two failures that Black Star had caused them, out of caution, Albert had decided to keep things at a low profile and not do anything for a few years. Hence, they were now making a count on the prisoners and preparing to move them somewhere else.

They definitely did not capture these targets because they wanted to collect stamps from their areas; they had other goals. This place was not the final location that these prisoners would end up in.

The yelling and cursing did not stop, but the three of them did not care. They split up and did a count. Very soon, Shana came to Kernid's cell.

Kernid bashed the transparent wall heavily and furiously said, "I remember you. You're the one that caught me! The Light Rune Civilization will definitely get me out!"

Shana sneered. "You've still not given up? Do you really think someone will come to save you?"

This time, Lagi slowly said, "Don't worry, no one will come to save us. We're definitely going to die."

Kernid was instantly at a loss for words. He covered his face with one hand and said, "Whose side are you actually on?"

Even Shana was speechless. This guy had been imprisoned for almost ten years, so he had probably gone haywire.

After the count, the three of them prepared to leave. The prisoners were still yelling and cursing. Albert paused before turning around and saying to everyone, "I know, you all think you're someone important. In reality, your positions in the Shattered Star Ring are not even worth mentioning in my eyes. In a few days, I will freeze you and send you out of the Shattered Star Ring. You will be determined as lost forever. You will never see your organizations or your families again. Fate is waiting for you ahead."

All the prisoners quietened down, furious and frustrated. If what Albert said was true, it would really be the end of them.

Many were despairing, anxious, and afraid of what was going to happen in the future. No one knew what the goal of this organization was.

Lagi sighed and said, "Sigh, I'm guessing they're going to make us experimental subjects and study our bodies. When we lose our value to them, they will then anatomize us; tear apart our bones, muscles, and organs; and place them in containers as specimens. Our name and life experience might be written somewhere on these containers. We will then become a collection to be displayed to others. 'Look, this is the very developed brain of the Calamity Grade Kernid' and so on..."

The others felt a chill run down their spines.

Kernid's face was filled with question marks. Why didn't you use your own name‽

Albert stayed silent for a while, thought about it, and decided not to explain. He then said calmly, "Anyway, enjoy your last few days of clarity. The next time you wake up, you will be in another Star Field..."

The moment his words sounded...

Boom!

A loud bang!

The entire prison suddenly started shaking violently!

Albert staggered and almost bit his tongue. Shocked, he asked, "What's happening?"

"Something's happened above!" Eliot said with surprise.

The three of them hastily left the prison and closed the gate after them. The prisoners looked at each other.

"Could it be that someone is here to save us?"

They were instantly energized and saw hope again.

With his usual long face, Lagi slowly said, "Even if there's someone here to rescue us, they might not be a match for the enemies. They will be killed in an instant. All of them will be wiped out. Their fleets will shatter, and the people inside will all be crushed and burnt into pieces. Your comrades, subordinates, and families might be among them. You will then be forced to eat those shattered parts of them, demolishing your spirit before anatomizing your body..."

"Shut the hell up!"

...

The shaking continued. Albert and the others returned to the main hall and met with the other three colleagues.

"What's going on?"

"Enemies!"

Albert's face turned grave. He then took the others out of the headquarters. When they got out, they discovered that an enormous amount of power was digging their headquarters out of the ground.

Two people were floating in the sky. When they saw who those two people were, Albert and the others were stunned and stupefied!

Black Star!

Dragon Emperor!

Ames was using her Esper ability to tear the ground apart, pulling their base right out of the ground.

"How can he be here‽" Albert opened his eyes wide.

They had attacked Black Star not long ago, and now he was here. Their location was very well hidden, so how did Black Star find them‽

Eliot could not believe it. He had never thought that Black Star would appear.

A thought suddenly appeared in his mind. He had just returned, and now Black Star had found this place—could it be that he had exposed them somehow‽

The last time they attacked Black Star, he could only cautiously wait for the next attack. However, after his failure, Black Star was now able to come right for them. Even though he could not understand how Black Star had done it, he could only be the one to blame for it. There was no other explanation.

Could it be that letting him escape was part of Black Star's plan?

Eliot was befuddled, feeling ashamed. Thinking back to when he escaped from Black Star's ambush, he felt that he was an idiot for not realizing that something was wrong and that Black Star had bigger plans.

Shana was extremely upset. She felt that this was all because of her failure when she attacked Black Star the first time. If she did not act alone but worked together with her partner, they would have been able to capture him, and Black Star would have become their prisoner.

Albert forced himself to calm down. He knew that Black Star was dangerous, but he never expected Black Star's counterattack to come so fast, bringing them so much danger.

Dragon Emperor was clearly helping Black Star. He had no confidence facing a Beyond Grade A at all, but he did not despair.

"Don't panic. Although the opponent is Beyond Grade A, we still have a tiny bit of hope. Although we're no match for the Dragon Emperor, we can at least stall her for a few moments. Eliot, whether we can escape or not all depends on you. We will create an opportunity for you to cast your spell." Albert clenched his teeth.

At this point, he could not care about the prisoners anymore. They were in extreme danger, so they had no choice but to stand the pain of letting go what they had been working on for so many years.

Ensure their own safety first, explain to the people above later!

"Understood!" Eliot replied.

At this time, Han Xiao took a deep inhale and said with a deep voice, "Everyone, come here!"

Hum!

The next moment, countless streams of light slashed across the sky and hovered above Han Xiao.

The fleets covered the sky, and countless cannons aimed at the six of them. The Calamity Grades arrived and sealed all their escape routes, surrounding the six of them.

Albert and the others were petrified. They could not believe it.

How did Black Star... gather so many people ‽

"Do it!"

Without saying much, Han Xiao told everyone else to attack altogether.

Villains always died for talking too much. He had no intention of speaking with the enemies. After they captured all of them, there would be plenty of time to have conversations with them.

"Run!" Albert screamed.

Seeing so many enemies, his last bit of hope shattered, leaving him only despair.

Covered in sweat, Eliot hastily tried to cast his teleportation spell. However, when he had only created a space vortex, it suddenly became extremely unstable. The teleportation gate that had always worked perfectly suddenly disappeared before it could even form.

Not far away, the eyes of a Grade A mage wearing a red robe was shining in the blue light of magic, and the staff in his hand was illuminating.

Spell Counter!

This time, only one thought was in the minds of Eliot, Shana, Albert, and the other three.

It's over!

[1] The name 'Lagi' has the same pronunciation in Mandarin as the word 'trash' or 'rubbish'. Back

Chapter 643: Crushed

The battle erupted in an instant.

Albert and the others were surrounded but did not give up resisting; they did everything they could to escape.

Indeed, all of them were very strong. However, the superiority of their individual strength could not overcome the collective strength of dozens of Calamity Grades. They were barely holding on.

Only Beyond Grade As could deal with a situation like this. Despite them being stronger individually, they were still in the Grade A range.

Boom!

The battle was intense, and the battlefield stretched across hundreds of miles. The earth was split open, and the ground was trembling. All sorts of abilities were flying all over the place; even the terrain was tremendously changed.

Following Han Xiao's information, a few Mages kept their eyes on Eliot at all times. As soon as he showed any signs of trying to cast a teleportation spell, they would use all sorts of abilities to prevent him from doing so.

Eliot was completely restrained. He was furious and had nowhere to run.

He regretted using his teleportation spell to escape from Han Xiao's 'ambush' not long ago. Clearly, that was why the enemies were so prepared.

Among the six of them, Albert was the strongest. He was a Psychic; his powerful psychic waves covered an extremely large area. He took on many people alone, hoping to create an opportunity for Eliot to cast a spell. However, his effort was wasted.

Black Star had gathered more people than he could ever have expected. Albert was filled with despair. Just the tens of Calamity Grades would be more than enough to cause them a lot of trouble, yet there were still tens of thousands of battleships in the sky and the Beyond Grade A Dragon Emperor.

This force that he had gathered would be more than enough to challenge the official army of a Star Cluster Civilization!

He had known that Black Star was dangerous but not this terrifying!

On the spaceship, the players that Han Xiao had brought along were having an exciting time doing nothing.

They had never seen anything like this. The excitement and awe of this battle between dozens of Grade As could even match up to the video where Dragon Emperor crushed the mothership in the previous version. Furthermore, in terms of thrill, this was even more exhilarating.

The players were all looking down from above. They could see the entire battle on the surface clearly. They all recorded videos of it and felt that their recordings might become the most astonishing videos on the forums.

On the way there, the players had all come to discover that Han Xiao had staged this. They felt like they were watching a cut scene of the storyline.

Han Xiao watched at the side. With so many helpers, there was no need for him to join the battle—he would have to repair his machinery if any of them got damaged.

It was completely one-sided.

He had planned to only receive the reward for the second round of the mission after he touched Feidin, but he had thought that attacking the enemies' base might be the third round of the mission, so he had completed the second round long ago, hoping to receive the next round of the mission. However, the third round did not appear; attacking their base did not become a mission requirement.

Han Xiao was not surprised by this. He could not decide the mission requirements. Even though this was not a mission, he would still attack their base. The fact that the third round did not appear meant that there were more enemies—he had to find out the true identity of this organization.

Without touching Feidin for luck, the abilities that he had drawn from the second round were very ordinary. Han Xiao had selected one of Adrian's normal talents [Bones of Steel], which gave him thirty Strength and twenty Endurance. This was already the most practical choice among the rest; it increased his maximum health by around three thousand points.

Bang bang bang!

The battle was one-sided from start to end and only lasted a while. The six's resistance was meaningless; they had no chance of escaping. They were all captured and thrashed without any hiccups.

After capturing the six of them, the organizations all sent people into the prison to find the person that was missing from their organization.

Albert and the others were heavily injured and taken to Han Xiao. All their masks were taken off, showing their furious faces. There was still shock in their eyes; they still could not believe that they had been defeated by Black Star so easily.

Black Star's counterattack came so quick and strong, easily defeating all of them. This was too difficult for the six of them to accept.

Han Xiao scanned through them and nodded.

Finally, all these people had been captured, and no one had escaped. He had achieved his goal.

"Who are you?"

Albert kept silent and glared at Han Xiao.

"No reply? Then let me change a question." Han Xiao took out the hunting list and coldly demanded, "Who ordered you to capture these people in the Shattered Star Ring? Where did this list come from?"

Albert was shocked. "Why do you have this list‽"

"You really think I don't know about it? I've known about you people for a long time. Who's the mastermind behind you?"

Shana could not believe it. She had thought that her failure had alerted Black Star, but it turned out Black Star had known about them long ago. Where did he get that information?

Albert still kept silent. It seemed like he had decided not to sell out the people behind him no matter what.

Han Xiao crossed his arms and said, "Do you think you're able to stay silent after falling into my hands? I have plenty of ways to make you talk."

Behind Han Xiao stood the Calamity Grades of many organizations, staring at Albert and the others. They were definitely not going to let the people behind this go easily. If Albert and the others were not going to talk, they were clearly going to be painfully tortured. These organizations would think of every way to get information from them.

Albert looked at these people then spoke slowly. "The end is death anyway; there's no difference between talking or not talking. Unless you can let us live."

"You're not in a position to make requests," Han Xiao said. "I can only ensure that you will be tortured less."

"Okay... I will tell you." Albert seemed to have made up his mind. "The Klent Kingdom ordered us to do this."

Han Xiao frowned.

"I need proof."

"I can prove our relationship with Klent. Our intelligence came from an intelligence organization under the Bloodshed Land; there are records for it. The hunting list was given to us by the Klent upper echelons. They want the Shattered Star Ring to be more chaotic, so they hired us to get rid of enemies and capture stronger individuals," Albert slowly said.

No, it's not Klent. Han Xiao frowned even more. It sounded like things were all connected, but the mission introduction clearly suggested otherwise. The truth was definitely not this simple.

He felt that Klent was most likely not the mastermind behind this mysterious group—there were contradictions in both their method and motive. Albert might be deliberately putting the blame on Klent.

Albert was done for; he had no choice but to give out some information. He might be lying to cover the truth and protect the real mastermind behind this, letting Klent take the blame.

As for why he chose Klent, it might be because Klent really was connected to this mysterious organization in some way. It might also be because Klent was the best choice to push the blame onto in the Shattered Star Ring.

Han Xiao stared at Albert's eyes but could not see anything but sincerity. He squinted but did not continue to question Albert.

"I see." Han Xiao suddenly smiled. "So, Klent is the mastermind. I believe you."

"That's right. If you want any evidence, I can provide it. I hope that you can keep your promise and not torture me." Albert insisted that it was Klent.

The emissaries of the other organizations felt an immense sense of hostility toward Klent. They were furious.

"Is Klent out of their mind? How dare they do something like this? Do they think we're easy to mess with?"

After Klent joined the Crimson Dynasty, they had become more and more imperious. Many organizations knew that Klent was ambitious, so they believed most of the 'truth' that Albert revealed.

The Purple Crystal Civilization emissary's eyes sparkled, and he was secretly delighted. If Klent ended up taking the blame, they were willing to believe it regardless of whether it was the truth or not. This would make these organizations hostile toward Klent.

The enemy of my enemy is my friend.

Albert and the others clearly wanted to hide the real mastermind, but Han Xiao was not planning to expose them and went with the flow of letting Klent take the blame.

He could search for the truth privately. After all, these people were now in his hands. He could do anything he wanted. Letting Klent take the blame was most profitable for him at the moment. This way, he could indirectly get more allies to help with the pressure during the secret war.

After so many organizations found out about this 'truth', the news would definitely spread across the entire Shattered Star Ring. By then, Klent's reputation would be heavily damaged. Even if it was not the truth, it would become the truth for many people. There was no way Klent would be able to come clean from this.

Han Xiao initially only wanted these organizations to owe him a favor and build partnership relationships with them; letting Klent take the blame for this was a pleasant surprise. Furthermore, he would not be responsible for it.

This time, the team that had gone to find the prisoners brought all of them back. These unlucky people got rid of the constraints over their bodies and finally started to recover.

"Haha, people really have come to rescue us!"

"There are so many people here."

Kernid and the others looked around with joyful faces. Many of them saw their organizations and returned to chat with their friends. Very soon, they got to know that it was Black Star who had provided the information that saved them.

They approached Han Xiao one after another to show their appreciation excitedly.

"If not for you, we would be done for."

"Thanks, we owe you one. If there's anything you need our help for in the future, be sure to tell us."

"Black Star, from now on, you're my brother."

Han Xiao replied friendlily one by one. Notifications kept popping up on his interface; the relationship with these organizations rocketed and all jumped right to 'Friendly'. For people that were saved such as Kernid, their Favorability increased the most.

He expressed his intention to keep this partnership going. Of course, the others were not going to reject. Not mentioning this favor, the Black Star Army itself was an organization that they were willing to work together with. This incident had become the bridge of their partnership.

After saving those unlucky people, Han Xiao's network expanded tremendously.

The Purple Crystal Civilization emissary got what they wanted, too—some organizations were willing to join Section Zero and help Purple Crystal fight Klent, their shared enemy.

This was all thanks to Han Xiao. His Favorability with Purple Crystal increased by 2,000 points straight away. He was one step closer to exchanging Cutting-Edge Knowledge.

Han Xiao had another goal. Some of the people captured were lone Calamity Grades. After saving them and increasing their Favorability, there was a chance to recruit them.

After asking around, most of those lone Grade A Supers rejected him and expressed that they had no intention of joining another organization. Only one person was an exception, which made Han Xiao overjoyed.

Being able to recruit just one of them was already more than good enough. He was currently the only Grade A in the army; adding one more meant that the number of Grade As doubled.

This was also the first Grade A whom he had recruited.

The person that accepted the invitation looked very ragged and depressed—it was no other than Lagi.

Lagi did not hesitate when he was invited. After being imprisoned for ten years, he did not want to go anywhere. Han Xiao had saved him, so he was willing to follow Han Xiao. The way he looked at it, no matter where he went, he would be rotting and dying anyway. It did not make a difference.

Han Xiao shook his hand and passionately said, "Welcome to the Black Star Army. You will definitely be satisfied with our treatment. We will be friends from now on. What's your name?"

Lagi shook Han Xiao's hand, sighed, and said, "I'm 'trash'."

"Come on, dude, you're too humble..."

Chapter 644: The Ancient Ones

Lagi's expression darkened, and an extremely bitter look could be seen on his face.

Han Xiao immediately knew that he had said something wrong and quickly replied, "Oh, sorry for the misunderstanding. Your name is... pretty good."

"Very regretfully, my father seems to agree." Lagi let out a sigh.

Why is this fellow speaking so politely? Han Xiao's expression was painfully awkward.

No wonder this fellow is always so pessimistic. Whenever he introduces himself to others, he has to say, 'I'm Lagi[1]'. How can he still face the world with a smile? It's only natural for him to be depressed and unable to see the hope in the world!

"It's alright. I'm used to it already." Lagi waved his hands to show that he did not mind. "In any case, we will all decompose into nothingness at the very end and not leave anything behind. I will disappear into the winding history with my name, and no one will remember me anymore."

Han Xiao's face was full of black lines.

This fellow's negativity was truly overflowing!

Lagi was a Grade A Mage, and apart from researching magic, he did not have anything that he wanted to do. He was like a piece of ambitionless salted fish.

He had accepted Han Xiao's recruitment because, first, he owed Han Xiao a favor and had nowhere to go, and second, joining an organization meant that he would not have to worry about his research expenditure.

The Black Star Army finally had a new Grade A combatant. Despite Lagi being a rather eccentric character, Han Xiao was still pretty happy. Even though Han Xiao wanted to understand this new partner of his more, Lagi did not seem to like talking at all. Whenever he asked Lagi about his past, Lagi would always give him a perfunctory response, and even after a long conversation, Han Xiao was still completely clueless about Lagi's past.

Han Xiao could not help but ask, "Do you have any friends or relatives?"

Lagi let out a depressed sigh and slowly said, "Just treat it as I don't have any."

Han Xiao rolled his eyes in response.

If he gave Lagi a cigarette and stubble grew all over his chin, the picture would be complete.

To think that such a depressed and lifeless individual was actually able to reach Grade A. Just what kind of tragic event happened in his life to transform him into such a depressed individual, or could it be that he had always been like that since young? If it was the latter, Han Xiao truly could not imagine what kind of a talent Lagi had.

Could it be that I picked up a protagonist level character? Han Xiao was extremely tempted to give Lagi a slap to see his attributes.

Right at this moment, all the organizations that were present had found their returning officers and were prepared to leave. Before they left, they all bade farewell to Han Xiao.

After fighting together this time, Han Xiao had built a good relationship with all these organizations, and his personal influence extended beyond the Colton Star Cluster.

Forming alliances and searching for allies was also an important aspect of developing his organization. Han Xiao's goal was to have friends all around the Star Field, and he had taken the first step in that direction.

The Star Beast Organization was extremely grateful to Han Xiao saving their leader, Gobili. They had never made any deals with outsiders but had expressed their willingness to enter a business partnership with the Black Star Army.

The Star Beast Organization only started to hire outsiders during Version 3.0, and players could complete faction missions to earn favorability points. Players could purchase rare Genetic Medicine and could even purchase pets and mounts. Since players already had spaceships, the purpose of a mount was only to increase their swag.

Han Xiao wanted to purchase a few rare galactic beast materials to upgrade his [Intermediate Strengthened Life] talent.

The last time, he had consumed the core of the Void Lord and confirmed this idea of his. Han Xiao needed rare materials that could fulfil this condition, and the Star Beast Organization was undoubtedly the experts in this field. They agreed without any hesitation and promised to complete the request.

There were a few lone wolves among those who were saved. Despite rejecting Han Xiao's recruitment, they left behind their contact numbers and promised to aid Black Star if he needed their help in the future.

Han Xiao treated this as a hidden trump card to be played in the future. The words of a Grade A Super could definitely be trusted.

Albert's gang of six became Han Xiao's captives, and after dismantling their headquarters, Han Xiao left together with Ames.

...

A few days later, the huge incident that Han Xiao had directed exploded in the Shattered Star Ring and caused another huge wave!

Including the seven Star Cluster level civilization, countless organizations in the Shattered Star Ring were shocked by the chaos that Han Xiao had created.

Numerous organizations from all directions had responded to Black Star's summons and formed a force that even Star Cluster level civilizations would not dare to underestimate. Since when did Black Star have such a huge influence‽

Ames had also participated in the operation, which allowed many to draw their own conclusions.

All the while, the Dragon Emperor had appeared to be a weak, neutral party. While the appearance of the Black Star Army had gradually increased the prestige of Floating Dragon, it was not enough to change the impression that most people had of Floating Dragon.

But this time, many individuals had misunderstood Han Xiao's actions to be those of Floating Dragon. They all thought that Floating Dragon was trying to flex their might and could not help but be startled.

Floating Dragon had unknowingly formed such a large alliance, and the seven Star Cluster civilizations could not help but reevaluate Floating Dragon's position.

As a beyond Grade A Super, Ames had always seemed disinterested in vying for power and influence. However, she seemed to have been getting more and more active since Black Star joined Floating Dragon. Black Star seemed to be the catalyst that allowed Floating Dragon to have a drastic transformation and rise rapidly.

After this incident, the strength that Floating Dragon had displayed planted some ideas in the minds of some private organizations.

With a beyond Grade A Super at the helm, as long as Floating Dragon wished, they would definitely be able to draw many to their side. If Han Xiao could draw more supporters for Floating Dragon, he would also receive benefits from it.

The other outcome of this operation was the 'truth' that Albert had revealed. Klent ended up becoming the scapegoat and was criticized by every organization within the Shattered Star Ring.

In truth, many civilizations had performed such an act before and had a tacit understanding with each other. However, the moment such an act was exposed, they would undoubtedly become the target for all criticism.

The Klent Kingdom was truly miserable. They were shot even while lying down, with a calamity falling on their heads even though they did not do anything.

Klent naturally released an official statement to deny their involvement, but it was not of any use.

Many organizations began to become wary of Klent after this incident. While living in turbulent times, every organization had no choice but to be on high alert.

In truth, Albert did indeed work together with Klent. However, Klent did no more than provide them with intelligence. Albert and the others came from another Star Field, and Klent was not their true master. Klent had indeed decided to provide intelligence to this group of six with the intention to kill with a borrowed sword and muddy the waters within the Shattered Star Ring. Thus, Klent truly was not maligned at all.

For such an incident to explode when they were in conflict with Purple Crystal, this was akin to providing Purple Crystal with more allies without doing anything. The Klents truly suffered a loss and were extremely frustrated by the incident.

Black Star's actions had disrupted Klent's original plans.

The Bloodshed Land had no choice but to adjust their plan and delay the time for war.

...

The Blacklight Stealth was currently on its way to the Garton Star System. In the spaceship, Han Xiao was currently extracting the Super-Genes of the six Supers. He had extracted a few dozen tubes of Super-Genes, and the six of them were extremely weak.

The [Prey] mission was not over yet, and the third phase had not been refreshed. The mastermind behind this incident would be his enemy for sure. In order to command six Grade A Supers who were all extremely close to having the strength of A+, the mastermind was definitely no simple character.

"I have said before. Klent is the one giving us orders," Albert said weakly.

Han Xiao shook his head and replied, "I didn't stop all of you from framing Klent because this is in line with my objectives. However, this doesn't mean that I truly believe you. I know that torture may not be useful to all of you. Thankfully, I brought a specialist for this."

Aesop then walked into the room. Aesop had also joined in the fun together with Ames and had always been on the spaceship. Aesop's Esper ability was extremely suitable for finding clues, and it would not matter if Albert and the others did not want to speak. Aesop naturally did not mind doing Han Xiao a small favor.

"Old man, I shall hand them over to you." Han Xiao moved out of the way.

Aesop touched the six of them and shut his eyes to use his Esper ability. After a long while, he opened his eyes with a strange look on his face.

"Old man, any luck?"

"I can't believe that it's them," Aesop muttered to himself with a grave voice. "Black Star, you have truly provoked some extraordinary characters."

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and he replied, "I didn't provoke them; they set their eyes on me."

"You are right. The winds howl around the highest peaks, and you can only blame yourself for being unlucky." Aesop sighed. "I thought that I would never have any more dealings with this group of individuals. Anything related to them will become extremely troublesome."

"Stop beating about the bush. Who exactly are they?"

"Have you heard of The Ancient Ones?"

Han Xiao's expression changed, and a solemn look could be seen on his face.

He naturally knew about this famous organization. Even in his previous life, The Ancient Ones was a famous organization among the players. Furthermore, Risda had also mentioned that Manison from the Mechanic Empire was also a member of The Ancient Ones.

This organization was extremely special. They did not have many members, and their members were in different Star Fields. They were all top figures in the galaxy and had lived for an extremely long time. The organization was one without much restriction, and it could be understood as a top social circle in the galaxy. Even the three great civilizations had to treat them with respect.

In the [Calamity of the Supers] storyline, many of The Ancient Ones beyond Grade A Supers formed their own faction, and Manison was one of them.

Aesop had once been a member but had withdrawn after that.

"You are saying that The Ancient Ones are the mastermind?"

The Ancient Ones was indeed an organization that he could not afford to provoke yet.

"I'm not sure. I did not manage to see any details; I was only able to see that this matter is related to The Ancient Ones," Aesop explained.

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao looked at Albert. Albert had a tranquil expression on his face and did not show any change in expression as though it had nothing to do with them. Who knew if he was putting on an act?

After thinking for a while, Han Xiao bent down and looked at Albert in the eyes, "Are The Ancient Ones your true master?"

"No." Albert frowned. "I've said more than once that it's Klent. It is up to you if you want to believe me."

Han Xiao frowned and raised his brows. "If this matter isn't related to The Ancient Ones, you would have been extremely glad for me to provoke them."

Albert fell silent and no longer said a word.

Han Xiao could not be sure that The Ancient Ones were his final enemy. Furthermore, The Ancient Ones were a loose organization, and it could be the plan of just a single member.

What a coincidence. This is the second matter related to The Ancient Ones. First, it was Aroshia, and now them... Han Xiao pondered to himself. It was truly too much of a coincidence.

Regardless of whether the mastermind is The Ancient Ones, I can't deal with them for now. Before reaching beyond Grade A, it will be difficult for me to even protect myself.

Han Xiao's mood was heavy. The enemy had already set their eyes on him, and with Albert and the others caught, new enemies would definitely appear. However, he did not even know the identity of his enemy.

This threat made him feel an immense sense of pressure.

However, worrying would not be able to change anything. There was currently a problem before him. Just how should he deal with his six captives?

It would not be a good choice for him to lock them up and squeeze them like orange juice. They were not rookie galactic pirates, and if they managed to escape, Han Xiao would not be able to suppress them. Furthermore, Han Xiao probably would not be able to find out anything else from them, so keeping them would only be a risk.

Eliot could feel Han Xiao's killing intent, and his body shuddered.

[1] Lagi is pronounced the same as trash in Mandarin. Back

Chapter 645: Galaxy Pro League Season Two

Han Xiao first returned to Floating Dragon to drop Ames and Aesop back. He then killed Albert and the others without hesitation. On the way to Floating Dragon, he had made a lot of Genetic Medicine from the six of them.

He was not planning to lock the six of them in the Galactic Pirates' Warm Little House because he did not want to take that risk. He was never soft-hearted toward enemies.

After killing the six of them, Han Xiao received a lot of Experience and a few Character Summon Cards.

Albert and the others were very calm toward death; only Eliot was panicking and furious. Nonetheless, none of them revealed the true identity of the mastermind till the end. This did not affect Han Xiao in his decision to kill them, but he was surprised by their loyalty.

Someone that could make a Grade A+ this sincere was definitely terrifying. That someone being a Beyond Grade A was the only possibility. No matter which member of The Ancient Ones the mastermind was, it was not someone he could deal with.

He would definitely become that person's enemy now that he had killed that person's subordinates. Han Xiao had no other choice. The enemy had targeted him, and he could not have not resisted. Thus, it was unavoidable.

The third round of [Prey] had yet to appear. He had no idea how strong the next attack would be. The only good news was that at least Beyond Grade As would not casually go to another Star Field, which meant that he would not have to fight a Beyond Grade A. Nonetheless, he still felt immense pressure.

For that, Aesop personally did a one-time 'fortune-telling' on him. He roughly foresaw that this issue regarding the hunters had come to an end for the moment, and that nothing would happen any time soon. This made Han Xiao feel relieved.

Star Fields were separated by very wide desolate regions. Whether it was traveling across Star Fields or getting information across, they were not easy things to do. Now that Albert and the others had died, the enemy would not be able to get to him shortly.

Han Xiao's position in Floating Dragon had been rising. He was Ames' best assistant, and Aesop had high hopes for him. On the way to Floating Dragon, he told him quite a lot of secrets about The Ancient Ones and helped Han Xiao guess who the mastermind was.

The Ancient Ones were not united; every member had their ambitions. The reason they had formed an organization was to fuse the members' influence into one and obtain a superior position in the universe, benefiting all the members. They rarely did anything using The Ancient Ones' name.

Aesop felt that the master of Albert and the others was just one member of The Ancient Ones. At least that was much better than the entire The Ancient Ones.

After killing Albert and the others, the matter had come to an end. Han Xiao took Lagi back to the Base No.1 in the Garton Star System.

Lagi was the only Grade A officer in the Black Star Army. Han Xiao introduced him to the other officers and let everyone know that there was a newcomer. Lagi had just escaped from imprisonment and was still rather isolated. He did not communicate with the others and went to familiarize himself with the environment. Han Xiao did not give Lagi any jobs yet.

With his Grade A strength, he was more than qualified to be the deputy captain. However, Lagi had just joined, and Han Xiao felt that he needed to know more about him more before giving him any important positions.

The secret war between Klent and Purple Crystal would not start any time soon, so Han Xiao could not increase his relationship with Purple Crystal even if he wanted to. There was nothing urgent to do, so he was quite free.

During the time he went out to look for trouble, there happened to be one huge matter that had attracted the attention of the players.

Pro League Season Two was about to start!

Some players uploaded the video of a scrimmage between tens of Calamity Grades, showcasing the Black Star Networking Group's ability. Bun-Hit-Dog's new video also mentioned information about the next version, which was related to the Crimson Dynasty as Han Xiao had said. These posts all got Han Xiao some attention. However, compared to the popularity of the Pro League, everything else was pushed side. Even he could not compete with the Pro League for popularity.

It was already the late stage of Version 2.0. Galaxy's players had been steadily increasing through the version. Although it had not reached the explosive increase stage, there were already many players.

The first season was quite successful. There were now many people paying attention to the second season. Galaxy Times had been talking about the Pro League for a few consecutive episodes, heating things up.

Han Xiao returned to his room, took out a bottle of 'Handsome and Happy' water and gulped it down. He then opened the latest Galaxy Times episode. This was the last episode before the start of the Pro League. It was their last effort to add more wood to the flames of this huge event.

The two hosts showed off their ability to make cold jokes before talking about the main focus of the episode, emphasizing on the rules of the second season of the Pro League.

Version 2.0 added a few novice planets. However, most players had already left their novice planets and entered space. Hence, the divisions were adjusted and were no longer based on novice planets. The divisions were now based on Star Fields that had novice planets in them. As some novice planets were in the same Star Field, they were combined into the same division.

There had been thirteen divisions in the previous season, but now there were nine. This meant that the teams of some countries would meet before the main event. Strong teams would face off against each other to qualify for the next stage. Even though more teams were allowed to advance this season, the competition would still be more intense.

The locations for the divisions were no longer on novice planets but a few nearby unpopulated planets in every division. The entire planet would be the venue. As the players had already entered the galaxy, they would definitely be able to come to the venue.

The format did not change much; it was still Singles and Groups.

There had only been three types of battles in the previous season—Duel, Groups, and Singles. One more was added this season—Survival. As the name suggested, it was about surviving. This would appear both in the point-based Division Regulars and the International Regulars. There would also be two types of Survival matches, one for teams and one for single players.

According to the Galaxy Times's introduction, the Team Survival was a battle between four teams. The only winner would be awarded a lot of points, the second and third would be awarded a certain number of points, and the last would not get any points. The Singles Survival would be a brawl between sixteen Singles players.

As for the schedule, the first stage was still the Division Qualifiers and Division Secondary League. All players would be able to register for the Division Qualifiers. The Division Secondary League was a jumping board for the second-tier teams of some clubs. The top forty teams and sixty-four Singles players would enter the Pre Season to warm up, followed by the Divisions Regulars.

The Divisions Regulars was point-based. The top eight teams and sixteen players would enter the Division Finals. After the Divisions Regulars, the ones at the top of the scoreboard would take part in the entertainment-oriented International All-Stars.

The Divisions Finals used the best of five format to determine first place and the runner up. As there were fewer divisions this season, the top four teams and eight Singles players would all be able to enter the International Regulars.

This time, the gap between the Internationals and the Divisions was hugely reduced; the schedule would be much tighter than the previous season.

The Internationals was also point-based. The most elite players from the various divisions would fight to determine the top eight teams and sixteen Singles players who would enter the International Finals, where the world champions would be determined.

Han Xiao looked at the forums' videos and nodded in approval.

The format was the same as in his previous life; the difference was the people taking part in it.

The show then heavily focused on introducing players with potential in China. When the time for the interviews came, the captains of the four biggest clubs in China were invited. Frenzied Sword, who had finished among the top in the International Singles in the previous season, was also invited.

The two hosts asked them a few questions and chatted. The atmosphere was light and relaxed.

For the last question, the two hosts asked every team about their goal this season and what they expected. The answers these people gave made the Chinese viewers feel excited.

Dynasty's King Admiral smiled lazily and said, "Dynasty only has one target this season, to win every single battle. We're going to be the Division champion and the world champion!"

Temple of God's Li Ge sounded very formal. "We will do our best to win every match and make use of all our strength. We hope to achieve enough in the Internationals to not disappoint the supporters of Temple of God."

Fried Eggplants with Fish's Sun Eggplant said with an expressionless face, "In the last season, we regrettably could not qualify for the Internationals. This season, we're going to fight to become the last winner."

Long Sky's Hao Tian sat up straight and said with a very serious tone, "Our only target is the world champion!"

The four biggest clubs all confidently announced that they were going for the championship; this made the Chinese players all very excited.

In the last season, Dynasty had been the first runner up. Although it was not bad, the Chinese players were still quite sad that they did not win.

They were close to the top, so they were more determined to reach it. The words of these four clubs were very morale-boosting.

"Four teams will be able to qualify in the Internationals. If all four of our clubs enter the top four and the Internationals, that would be really fun."

"Hehehe, that might not be certain. Although they are all very strong, the other tier-one teams are not bad either. Rainy Kim's Thunder Storm and Yan Ran's Berserkers are not easy to deal with. Nine Gates, Sky Palace, and Dragons and Tigers are all very competitive, too."

"I have high hopes for Rivervale. Frenzied Sword was top sixteen in the International Singles last season. Rivervale have rebuilt their team with him as the core. They might be a dark horse."

Many viewers discussed their thoughts in the comments.

Frenzied Sword was not as confident as the other captains on the show. He said that this was his first time leading a team and that he would do his best to enter the Internationals. He did not dare announce that they would be champions.

The clubs of other countries were all quite pressured. Planet Aquamarine was the base of the Chinese players, and they had entered space more than a year earlier than the others. This had resulted in the average strength of the Chinese teams being very high. All of them were strong teams that were not easy to deal with. Even the champions of the previous season, the French team, did not underestimate them and said that they would do their best to become back to back champions.

Han Xiao was looking forward to seeing what place China would be able to achieve under his influence.

In the Pro League's second season in his previous life, Dynasty had gotten third place in the Internationals and Temple of God had finished in the top eight. This time, China's overall strength was clearly superior. It was not just their equipment, abilities, and experience, but also the fact that the pro players had taken part in galactic-level battles long ago. Their skills were honed as well.

The second season of the Pro League is an important stage. The first season was just a test. A lot more effort has been put into promoting the second season; it's many times more influential than the first season. It will directly cause a huge number of new players to enter during Version 3.0. The better the results the Chinese teams achieve, the more exposure they will get, which will also be beneficial to my faction.

Currently, the roughly one million players in the Black Star Army had all been players from the earliest releases. There would be more newcomers joining in in the future.

The tons of new players in Version 3.0 were a second opportunity to expand the size of the army. Without the advantage of being the guiding faction, he had to compete with the many factions in Version 3.0. The Pro League would be a way for him to increase his faction's attractiveness.

Other than these long-term benefits, every Pro League was a business opportunity.

The players earned money to turn it into their strength. During the Pro League, the players' demand for equipment would explosively increase. The Genetic Medicines in his warehouse would sell very well. He was only worried about not having enough stock.

Pro League stimulated the players' need to spend. The players were happy to empty their wallets. This was a chance to make a huge fortune.

A few unpopulated planets in the Garton Star System made up the competition venue. Han Xiao planned to gather a fleet to sell equipment at the venue. Whether it was to repair equipment, buy items, or learn abilities, the players would be able to spend on the spot. It would be amazing for them.

Anyway, whether it was amazing for the players or not, it was amazing for Han Xiao.

The Pro League is going to start in ten days. Time to go.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Chapter 646: Training Soldiers

With the day of the Pro League drawing ever closer, practically all the players began to gather on the host planet. Even if they were not competing, they could still participate in the arena as spectators. This would be a large-scale event involving the entire playerbase, and for players who loved lively events, this was something that they could not miss.

The uninhabited planet that served as the competition grounds started to be filled with life. Spaceships flew in and out, and the entire planet served as the battlefield, a vast area. The players officiating and volunteers had constructed many platforms and viewing stands. Continuing the style of the previous season, they had allowed the players to participate in the construction of the venue, to enhance their sense of being part of the event. Since there were also many players that were idling away, they were happy to help out.

The casual players prepared the venue in full swing on the planet, while the participating players took advantage of the time to do their final preparations, strengthen their equipment, and upgrade their skills.

Han Xiao had brought a fleet, with a flagship serving as the core. They carried various stocks from the warehouse as they came toward the game planet. When the Black Star fleet appeared, the players on the planet were surprised as they did not know why the Army's fleet had appeared.

After the fleet arrived, it remained floating in outer space. The players were curious; thus, they entered the flagship, only to find Han Xiao inside.

When the players asked, Han Xiao's reply was concise.

"My intelligence showed that a large portion of our mercenaries had gathered on this uninhabited planet. This puzzled me, and I thought that you guys would be in trouble, so I came over to take a look."

This reason was both acceptable yet unexpected to the players. Many of them found it interesting.

The players had long gotten used to actual feedback from the NPCs. Their every action would determine the judgment of the NPC as well as the change in Galaxy itself. This sort of strong interactive feedback mechanism often left the players in full immersion.

As a member of the Black Star Army, to have tens of thousands of their people gathered in one place such that the leader of the faction actually got alarmed and came to inspect was a refreshing experience to the visitors.

In terms of character interaction, some players enjoyed role-playing, conversing with the NPCs in accordance with the game to make it as realistic as possible, while others liked to directly admit to Han Xiao that they were having a tournament.

"If that's the case, I would like to assess my mercenaries' growth. Just nice, I don't have anything on at the moment," Han Xiao replied in a natural tone, pretending to ignore the words such as 'Pro League' and other game related terms. He instead implied that they were doing this as a large-scale friendly spar.

The majority of players did not doubt him. They did not expect an NPC to appear to observe their Pro League, but this only made it more interesting.

In addition, upon finding out that the ship was stocked with various services for supply and maintenance as well as equipment and potions, the players were even more pleased. This meant that there was now a convenience store right beside them.

The happiest group was actually the club players. Because they were filthy rich, the services that Black Star provided could allow them to flexibly adjust their tactics without the need to run to other planets to prepare their supplies. This saved them a lot of time.

Having Han Xiao spectate the event would naturally not be suspicious to the players. As long as he did not move toward that topic, nobody would think about the strangeness of this whole affair.

No matter how low the possibility of a player suspecting him as an NPC, even if someone really found out, it was useless. For him to have gone through so much from the start, if there were problems, they would have popped up long ago. As long as he did not interfere in the Pro League, maintaining his distance, there was no need to panic.

Three days later, the highly anticipated Second Pro League officially began!

The first stage was naturally the qualifiers. This could be considered a side dish before the main course. Directed by the league staff, the numerous contestants formed teams to undergo an elimination process and obtain the qualifications to enter the formal round.

Because the venue was much larger compared to the First Pro League, the time taken for the qualifiers had been greatly shortened.

On the forums, the officials released the highlights of the qualifiers for each division. Any Second Pro League content was thoroughly analyzed, and anything not related to the Pro League was lost in the sea of posts.

The players of every country were discussing the giants, seeded players as well as potential dark horses.

On the Chinese board, the main teams of the four giants had direct team entry for the regular season and did not need to participate in the qualifiers. The teams that received the most attention were the front-line teams such as Thunder Storm, Fanatics, and so on.

Frenzied Sword's Rivervale also caught the eyes of many. Eliminating team after team, they blazed through the qualifiers.

In the Singles, King Admiral, Frenzied Sword, and the others who had fought and entered the International competition also had the right to skip the qualifiers, sparing themselves from the intense competition.

Unlike the team qualifiers, because the Singles was open to all, the majority of players wanted to have a go at it. Thus, the number of players in that event was the highest, practically the entire gaming community.

Compared to Version 1.0, the strength of the players was now much stronger, giving rise to various genres and fighting styles, as well as tricks. The scenes were more intense, full of lights and stars as different abilities were used, making everyone who looked at it dizzy.

Since entering the galaxy, the players had also begun to come into contact with the Mage and Psychic classes. A number of newcomers, as well as old players who were playing on new accounts, had chosen those two classes. All the competition divisions had the same five professions for Supers, but the ratio was different. For the Professions that had only popped out in Version 2.0, the proportion of players were naturally the least.

However, compared to his previous lifetime, the situation had changed. Originally, the proportion of players in the Mechanic class had been the second lowest, ranked even behind the Mage class. However, the number of players with the Mechanic profession was the second highest, only losing out to the Pugilist class.

This was because Han Xiao had swayed a lot of players to the class advancement of a Mechanic back in Version 1.0.

The other point that Han Xiao noted was that the players in China had a stronger average strength, surpassing that of his past life. Because he had allowed Planet Aquamarine to enter the galaxy a couple of years earlier than the rest, be it experience, money, or combat capability, the region of Shattered Star Ring had more advantages compared to his past life. Rich resources had allowed for better support for various combat capability and tactics, and any half-decent battle teams had standards that were well above the norm.

The Second Pro League event was unprecedented, as the entire planet was used as a battlefield. The qualifiers and divisional battles proceeded quickly, and with the schedule being shorter than the first Pro League, the feeling was more intense.

In ten days, the qualifiers finally came to an end, and the season roster of each division was released.

The lists released in the other regions were not much different compared to the previous season, but in the Shattered Star Ring, the season roster had undergone a significant change. While the strong teams were still in the running as with the previous season, there were large changes seen in the lower rungs, with many new teams and players surfacing.

One of them that made Han Xiao feel a little surprised was Maple Moon, who was only supposed to take part from the Third Pro League onward. Not only did she participate in this season, she had even entered the roster of Top 64 places in the Singles tournament, making her one of the dark horses.

Han Xiao had watched the video channel of Maple Moon. She was usually grouped together with Frenzied Sword and Hao Tian, and their standards rose extremely quickly as a result. Whatever Enas they earned would be spent immediately. She had possessed the potential to go Pro from the beginning, or else she could not have become so famous in his past life.

However, compared to his previous life, Maple Moon's standard was still a distance from her peak. The main reason she had managed to enter the Singles ranking was because she had bought the blueprint of the Void Dragon Mechanical suit from Han Xiao and created her own poorer version of it. Only in the Third Pro League would the Mechanic profession begin to display its version advantages and rise to power. Right now, the Mechanic class was neither strong nor weak, and equipped with a mechanical suit that was considered god-like in this Version, while she could not crush everyone, Maple Moon could afford to make more mistakes.

As the saying went, every version would have a generation of gods. The Mechanic profession in Version 2.0 was not strong enough, but with the great tutor Han Xiao, the players who chose the Mechanic profession had cut off a lot of dead ends. At least within the Shattered Star Ring, the disadvantages of a Mechanic were not so obvious.

Within the Singles list, there were at least ten more players in the Mechanic class than in his past life. In the area of team battles, the Mechanic class was also an important team member required for every team.

Han Xiao had made quite the killing in the qualifiers. The machinery went without saying, as most of the players were using Black Star's equipment. The sales for the Genetic Medicine also increased, with the clubs buying them in large quantities since they could provide a sudden edge in battle. If not for the abundance of stock, it was likely that the clubs would have bought all the Genetic Medicine that Han Xiao had in stock.

Taking advantage of the Pro League to earn a quick buck, the sum of Han Xiao's bank deposit broke through his short-term goal.

With the qualifiers over, the main course was about to arrive.

The impact of Han Xiao's recent large-scale operation still lingered, with the various organizations observing the every move of the Black Star Army.

The scene of large numbers of 'Black Star Mercenaries' gathering on a random planet for a competition gathered the attention of many of the organizations, which made them start to guess the intentions of Han Xiao.

When a few of the Mercenary Groups learned of this news, envy filled their expressions. This incident indirectly demonstrated the control that Black Star had over his Mercenary Group. Most mercenaries had no loyalty or bonds to speak of, but Black Star had thousands of these 'comrades'. Not only were they cohesive, they were also willing to follow Black Star's orders to act in unison without him having to spend a single cent. This was more reliable than those freelance mercenaries that most groups hired.

Many of the organizations believed that Black Star had what it took to transform from a mercenary group into a proper armed organization in the future.

Because the incident had added a lot of helpers to Section Zero, the Black Star Army's name had entered the sight of the upper echelons in the Purple Crystal Civilization, and they looked favorably upon the Black Star Army.

Currently, Han Xiao only required a few hundred more faction favorability points to reach the Respect tier.

This time's situation also attracted the attention of the Purple Crystal Civilization.

"Black Star has gathered more than eighty percent of his mercenaries on the planet to battle with each other. What is he doing?"

In the office of Section Zero, many of the foreign affairs officers were discussing this matter.

Ralph rapped on the table as he confidently smiled.

"There's only one explanation. Training. Black Star's training his soldiers!"

The eyes of everyone present lit up as they began to nod and praise him.

Ralph was full of smiles. In his mind, the Black Star Army was undergoing mock battles to simulate an actual battlefield.

"What a reliable ally." Ralph could not help but sigh.

Chapter 647: Advanced Strengthened Life

The Regulars were exciting as expected, and the competition was intense.

Han Xiao's fleet remained on the host planet. In his free time, he watched the broadcast on the forums. Other than that, he sold all sorts of potions and built some machines.

Among the nine divisions, the Shattered Star Ring Division was the most exciting. The Black Star Army's diverse range of machines provided the Chinese teams with many creative strategies such as group self-detonation with the nuclear flying backpacks. Those who used this strategy were clearly aware that they would not be able to qualify for the next round, so they decided to have some fun.

Compared to the competitions in the other divisions, the fights between the Chinese teams were more suspenseful. The Genetic Medicine that Han Xiao was selling added more uncertainties to these fights. Comebacks had already happened many times.

Near the end of the Regulars, the qualified teams for the finals in the various divisions were basically decided. To Han Xiao's surprise, Frenzied Sword's Rivervale team climbed as high as second on the point-based scoreboard, right below Dynasty, which almost won every single fight.

For Frenzied Sword, who was leading a team for the first time, this was outstanding. In fact, Rivervale was not very strong in direct battles, but it was like God was helping them in the new mode, Survival. They were able to be the last team standing many times. This gave them a lot of points. Hence, they rocketed to second place in the later stages.

The eight teams that qualified for the Shattered Star Ring Division Finals arranged in descending order were Dynasty, Rivervale, Long Sky, Thunder Storm, Thunder Storm, Fried Eggplants With Fish, Fanatics, and Nine Gates.

As for the Singles, King Admiral, Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, Li Ge, and the other strong players all got into the top 16. Maple Moon was 38th place.

Despite not being able to qualify, her performance was quite good and attracted some fans. Although she did not achieve the results that she obtained in the third season in Han Xiao's previous life, she gained some fame in advance. Quite a number of teams wanted to sign her into their training program.

The Division Regulars ended. The Division Finals would start after some resting time. As the schedule was tighter than the previous season, it would not be a long rest.

During that, the top teams from the nine divisions and the champions in the Singles took part in the International All-Stars and put on a show for the audience.

On the forums, the Chinese players commented that they could not wait to see Dynasty's battle with strong teams with other countries. The champion of the previous season, Tulips, was the champion in their division. As the first runner up in the previous season, Dynasty had the opportunity to fight with the previous champion. Although it was just a performance, countless Chinese players still hoped that Dynasty could win.

Before the International All-Stars started, Han Xiao received some good news.

During this time of the Pro League for the players, the Star Beast Organization finally gathered all the rare materials Han Xiao had requested and sent them to Han Xiao from far away.

In the flagship's hall, the Star Beast Organization member delivered an alloy box and said in a respectful tone, "Your Excellency Black Star, the goods you wanted have been delivered. Leader Gobili sends his regards."

"Okay, thank him for me. We will have many opportunities to work together in the future."

Han Xiao nodded and sent him away. He then took the box to his training room.

After closing the door, Han Xiao opened the box. Cold air flew out and obstructed his view. After it slightly dissipated, Han Xiao saw ten tubes of liquids inside with various colors. Some had multiple colors, some were transparent, and some were deep blue. These were all potions extracted from the essence of rare galactical creatures related to the Void Race in some way.

Injecting biological medicines had the risks of causing mutation. The most direct effect of it would be a decrease in attributes. The lower the compatibility, the higher the chances for a mutation to occur. To lower the risks, the creatures Han Xiao listed all had the Void bloodline. Han Xiao was one of the Void Race himself, so the high compatibility would hardly lead to any mutation.

Void creatures were difficult to find. It had taken the Star Beast Organization quite a lot of effort to obtain all of that.

Han Xiao took out the Injector and injected them into his body one after another. He always rested a while in between each tube to ensure that everything was fine before injecting the next tube.

The first few tubes gave him a few more points in attributes, but the effect was getting weaker. When he was at the sixth tube, it did not give him any attributes anymore. The last time his talent leveled up also happened when he continued injecting after he stopped getting bonus attributes.

As Han Xiao injected the last tube, a notification finally popped up on the interface.

Your talent [Intermediate Strengthened Life] has upgraded.

Upgrade complete, original talent changed to [Advanced Strengthened Life].

Advanced Strengthened Life: Provides extra health based on END on a scale of 1:60, +25 Resistance, +10% all attributes temporarily for every 40% health lost.

"Finally, this talent is upgraded."

Han Xiao had a joyful expression on his face.

Before the upgrade, the ratio of Endurance to health was 1:30, but it was now 1:60. There was also the effect of getting a ten percent bonus in all attributes temporarily for every forty percent health lost.

"I have two talents that can exchange between mana and health, which makes my health recovery extremely fast. If every forty percent of my health lost triggers a new effect, this means that the longer the battle is, the stronger I will become."

Harmon had a similar ability, and he had seen its power with his own eyes.

"The only problem is... I'm too tanky. It will take too long to reduce my health by forty percent."

Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at his health.

[Health: 117,910]

"Hehe, finally, my health is more than a hundred thousand. Even if the Vanguard Officials of the Bloodshed Land fight me all at once, I will be able to tire them out easily. When the secret war starts, I've got to find them to have some fun."

Han Xiao chuckled.

He was so tanky that instead of being called a Mechanic, he might as well be called a Musclechanic.

...

At the center of the known universe was the base Star Fields of the three Universal Civilizations, which formed a triangle. These were the most advanced and bustling Star Fields in the entire galaxy. This place was called the Central Galaxy. It was the universe center of the strong, the powerful, and the rich.

The Abyss of Stars was one of the three Star Fields in the Central Galaxy, the core territory of the Federation of Light.

In this Star Field, there were some known forbidden areas.

The Shadow Realm was one of them.

This was a manually modified planet, and beside it was an eerie black satellite. There was no land, no seas—it was as if this was a gaseous planet formed by some sort of black gas.

The Shadow Realm was a forbidden place in the Abyss of Stars because this was the territory of a Beyond Grade A—[Thousand Shadows].

Just like the Shattered Star Ring, there were also Beyond Grade As in the Abyss Of Stars. In fact, there were more than four of them. Between the Beyond Grade As in the Abyss of Stars, Thousand Shadows was known to be an outcast.

No one knew his name; no one had seen his real face. Every traveler who stepped into the Shadow Realm had disappeared without a trace. This gave Thousand Shadows an aura of mystery and danger. People could only know about him through parts of legends.

These legends could be traced back to as early as the end of the exploration era, meaning there were records of Thousand Shadows dating back to thousands of years ago.

There was a city in the Shadow Realm, comprising many buildings and a lot of bases. Countless spaceships were docked there. However, strangely, there was almost no one there. It was deadly silent.

A man sprinted down the completely empty street. His footsteps and the sound of wind were among the only sounds in this city.

There was a tall tower-shaped palace in the middle of the city. This man ran into the open door of the palace, through the deadly silent corridor, past the spiral staircase, and arrived at the top of the palace.

This was a room, a very wide and spacious room. At the end of the room was a wall embedded with a circular black mirror. The man came before the mirror, and the pitch black and smooth mirror reflected the man's face. He had an ordinary look, except his eyes were pure white like two white crystals.

The man stared at the mirror and softly spoke.

"Your Excellency Thousand Shadows, I did not intend to disturb your rest. Some things have happened; Albert has failed. The team in the Shattered Star Ring was wiped out. Their prey was rescued. We need your guidance."

Then, the man patiently waited for a reply. After a while, the mirror suddenly started rippling. An indescribably eerie voice appeared. It was ethereal and husky, like the murmur of a higher dimensional being.

"The others?"

"The teams capturing prey in other Star Fields have not met any trouble. Everything is normal."

"The new shadows... will convey my message..."

The next second, the black satellite in outer space suddenly launched a thin, long beam, heading right to the Shadow Realm and accurately landing at the top of the palace. It was like a bridge that connected them.

Swoosh!

A rippling sound came from the black mirror. The next moment, ten black shadows walked out of the mirror one after another like walking into reality from the world inside the mirror. These shadows were all completely pitch black. Tiny black dust made from an unknown material was dissipating from them and vaporizing in the air. The shapes of these shadows were gradually changing. New limbs kept growing out and disappearing.

Within a few seconds, the ten shadows finally stopped changing shapes. The black color on their bodies rapidly disappeared, and they turned into ten beings of different races. There were some that looked like humans and some that did not. Their faces and body shapes were all different, too. It was like they were all individual beings.

The leader was a beautiful, naked woman. Her eyes were closed. She took a deep breath. As if the air she inhaled had awoken her bodily functions, only then did she slowly open her eyes. Her blank, lifeless eyes started to look lively and intelligent. She did a stretch and moaned.

"How long was I asleep? I seem to have forgotten many things..." The woman raised her eyebrows and seemed to be trying to recall something. "My name is... Stephanie?"

The man at the side was used to this. He bowed and said, "Hello Stephanie, what orders does His Excellency Thousand Shadows have?"

Thousand Shadows? Stephanie felt a sense of belonging to this name, and a lot of memories started appearing in her head. Without hesitation, she said, "He told us to continue Albert's mission and capture the targets on the list, bringing the escaped prey back."

The man nodded and said, "Okay, the ten of you will be the new team in the Shattered Star Ring. Follow me to get your equipment. Rest for a while and get going. Remember what happened to Albert. You have to be stealthier when carrying out the mission."

"I'll do my best," Stephanie replied.

Chapter 648: Divisions

The schedule for the International All-Stars was released. The first match was already very exciting—the fight between the champion and the first runner-up of the previous season—Tulips vs. Dynasty.

The event organizers clearly knew that this would bring more attention to the All-Stars event, so they heavily promoted this match. In all the pro competitions, inviting the champion and the first runner-up of the previous season as the opening match of the All-Stars was a kind of tradition.

This was highly effective. This opening match was extremely popular, especially among the Chinese viewers. Being first runners-up was an achievement, but it was also regretful. They hoped to see Dynasty's victory over Tulips and start off this season with a blast.

Not just the spectators, but all the teams that intended to enter the Internationals were paying attention to this opening match, wanting to learn more about Dynasty and Tulips. When the time came for them to face one of these strong teams, they could at least be somewhat prepared.

Han Xiao was paying attention to this match as well. After all, Dynasty's guild had bulk purchased hundreds of Ability Potions from him. He had to observe the effects they would bring and think about after-sales services.

Like the previous season, the store would sell a specific Gathering Crystal to bring the attending players into the same virtual environment for the match. It would be broadcast officially as well as by the Galaxy Times.

A few days before the match, the Galaxy Times interviewed both the Tulips team and the Dynasty team, asking about what they thought of this match.

Tulips' captain, Lost Angel, was extremely confident and said that they would definitely win this match, protect their honor as the champions of the previous season, and so on. As they were the previous season champions, most of the spectators naturally had higher hopes for Tulips.

As for Dynasty, King Admiral did not know the meaning of the word 'humble'. He directly said for Tulips to wash themselves up and wait for him to wipe the floor with them. Of course, those were not his original words, but that was what he meant.

In this situation, the Chinese supporters did not want to see Dynasty being humble—this confidence boosted their morale much more. They all showed their support on the forums. After all, Dynasty had looked almost undefeatable throughout the Division Regulars. The Chinese players had very high hopes for Dynasty. The last thing they wanted to see was Dynasty doing what the Temple of Gods had done the previous season.

The various professionals analyzed the match before it started. Most of them felt that Tulips was slightly stronger—even the official host of the event thought so. They placed Dynasty in the challenger's position.

Galaxy Times did a conclusive report.

"King Admiral and Lost Angel have both made their victory announcement. Indeed, both of them have the potential to win. They will definitely have an exciting and unpredictable battle that will stay suspenseful until the very last moment. Let's look forward to who will be the final winner."

The day of the opening match soon came.

Countless players swarmed into the live broadcast channel. Other than the official channel, there was also the Galaxy Times' channel, which invited guests to watch the match together. Many viewers chuckled upon seeing the guest list of the Chinese version Galaxy Times—Bun-Hit-Dog was in it.

Bun-Hit-Dog's video career was blooming. He had finally turned himself into someone famous and now had both fans and haters. Him mixing with the other guests who were all pro players looked quite entertaining.

The two teams had entered the match venue with their Gathering Crystals long ago. Led by the host, King Admiral and Lost Angel both did a short interview on the scene before going to make preparations.

While waiting, the commentators and guests speculated and started chit-chatting.

The female commentator of the Chinese version Galaxy Times said to the guests, "The match is about to start soon. How about you guys try to predict the result and tell us which team you think is more likely to win. Oh, and please do tell us the reason for your choice."

The replies of the guests were all similar. They all said Tulips was strong, but they felt that Dynasty had a higher chance of winning. They then went on to give plenty of logical reasons for their choice. Mainly, it was just because they did not dare support the opponent in front of the Chinese viewers.

That was all except for Bun-Hit-Dog, who was not like the others. His position was extremely firm and without hesitation.

"I support Tulips; the French team will win!"

The guests were all surprised.

The commentator could not help but ask, "Are you sure? Why?"

"Well, it's a little difficult to explain..." With a serious face and tone, Bun-Hit-Dog said, "Have you ever heard of reverse psychology?"

The commentator was speechless. He had thought that Bun-Hit-Dog had lost his mind, but it turned out that he was just joking.

After Bun-Hit-Dog explained, the comments finally turned from all question marks into countless 'The French will win' comments.

After the commentators and guests joked around and chatted for a while, the match officially started. The relaxing atmosphere instantly became intense. The viewers all focused on the match.

The first match was a team match. The broadcasting view followed both teams at all times. Han Xiao was mainly looking at Dynasty.

The venue was random, and it was a rather complicated terrain. After Dynasty entered, they did not hastily look for the enemies but took out one mechanical item after another.

The commentator spoke at a suitable time. "Dynasty has chosen the steady strategy. They've used mechanical items to create an advantageous situation for them. One thing I should mention is that the items Dynasty is using are all Black Star series machines. The Black Star Army has a full set of machinery products. This has given the teams in the Shattered Star Ring division an advantage in designing their strategies. Comparatively, team Tulips does not have this advantage."

Bun-Hit-Dog nodded and added, "Definitely. According to my investigations, the players in the other divisions lack methods of obtaining set equipment as easily as the Black Star Army. Although the pro players are still able to gather a full set of top-notch equipment, this will have taken them more time."

As soon as the Black Star Army was mentioned, the Chinese players were like on steroids. The comments were filled with 'Black Star is awesome', 'Notice me, captain', 'Dragon Emperor licker here', and so on.

When the Black Star Army was mentioned in an international event such as this, the Shattered Star Ring players became extremely exhilarated. The Black Star Army was the bridge that connected the many players in the Shattered Star Ring—it had become their shared language.

Han Xiao was rather surprised. He had not been mentally prepared for the sudden mention. He suddenly had a strange feeling of 'Wherever I'm not, my legends are'.

The match continued. The two teams moved on the map and finally discovered each other. They quickly approached each other.

The viewers immediately grew nervous. They held their breath and waited for the intense clash between two strong teams they had expected...

However, dreams and reality are often very different. The actual situation was far from what they thought it would be.

There was no intense battle between two similarly strong teams—Dynasty thrashed Tulips from the beginning to the end, beating them up and ending with an overwhelming victory.

The commentators and guests were at a loss of words. The Chinese viewers were beyond exhilarated. On the other hand, the viewers of the other countries were stunned. Most did not support either of the teams, but they did look forward to an intense battle. To their surprise, the champion of the previous season was overwhelmingly and easily defeated.

The Duel that followed ended with Dynasty's complete victory as well.

The official casters and judges were all stupefied. The host wanted to make the opening match an exciting battle between two extremely strong and skilled teams. This was also why they had invited the champion and the first runner-up of the previous season. To their absolute shock, Tulips had been easily crushed by Dynasty.

It was Dynasty's complete, one-sided victory. The comments went crazy, and the Chinese spectators were overjoyed.

Han Xiao was not surprised by this result at all. In his previous life, Tulips had also been the champion of the first season, but they had become a normal, stronger than average team in the second season and almost did not even make it to the International top 8.

As for Dynasty, they were much stronger than the previous season. To Han Xiao, this result was very normal.

Although Tulips was the champion of the previous season, the French lacked a special advantage that the Chinese players had—there were too few hateful comments!

Unlike the Chinese players who had been fighting in such a harsh environment, they had no pressure. The Chinese players were always motivated to become better so that they would not get so many hateful comments. However, Tulips became relaxed after winning the championship.

In the same opening match in his previous life, the two teams had been Tulips and the American team Devil, where Tulips was also demolished by Devil. Now that Dynasty had taken over Devil's place in the first season, the one that demolished Tulips became them.

After the opening match ended, the various professionals all changed their minds and started praising Dynasty as they usually would, praising the winner after the match.

The teams of the other countries all saw Dynasty as the strongest competitor and focused on studying the match recordings, trying to design better strategies.

Dynasty's victory was sensational and received a lot of attention. Their fame surpassed that of the other three clubs very quickly. The Chinese supporters all cheered for them and almost saw them as their main team. With their excitement and joy also came their very high hopes.

The majority of the players in team Dynasty were somewhat nervous.

As members of one of the biggest clubs, they knew full well that this situation was a double-edged sword. Of course, if they kept winning, they would surpass everyone else and almost become god players.

However, once they lost, the mistakes of every single one of them would be indefinitely enlarged, and they would be drowned by the hateful comments. The more attention they got, the more pressure they would receive. King Admiral was the only one unaffected by this at all.

After the opening match, the International All-Stars officially commenced. The strong teams fought each other in entertaining ways to kick off the International Regulars.

The champions of all nine divisions showcased their skills and displayed their strength.

The schedule for this season was very tight. The end of the All-Stars was followed by only a few days of rest before the Division Finals started.

In the Shattered Star Ring Division, the eight teams were split into four pairs based on their ranking: Dynasty vs. Nine Gates, Rivervale vs. Fanatics, Long Sky vs. Fried Eggplants With Fish, and Temple of Gods vs. Thunder Storm. The format was best of five.

The most interesting pair was Long Sky vs. Fried Eggplants With Fish—the two biggest clubs met in the first round. As only the top four could qualify for the International Regulars, this meant that one of them would not be able to qualify.

In the previous season, Fried Eggplants With Fish had not been able to enter the International Regulars. This time, their morale was extremely high, and they had sworn to defeat Long Sky in order to qualify.

Sadly, Long Sky still won. Fried Eggplants With Fish did not qualify once again and went to the corner to draw voodoo circles.

Very soon, the first round of the Division Finals had ended. As expected, Dynasty defeated Nine Gates and kept their momentum.

Rivervale had a close, intense battle with Fanatics. At the match point of 2:2, Frenzied Sword and Evil Sword surged at a crucial moment and barely defeated team Fanatics, led by Yan Ran. Rivervale entered the top four.

The result of Temple of Gods vs. Thunder Storm, however, was very unexpected. Rainy Kim wiped the floor with Li Ge, eliminating Temple of Gods with a score of 3:1 and entering the top 4. Temple of Gods joined Fried Eggplants With Fish in drawing voodoo circles in the corner.

The top 4 was determined—Dynasty, Long Sky, Rivervale, and Thunder Storm. The result was quite surprising for many viewers. Two of the biggest clubs could not qualify for the International Regulars.

The top 4 teams were already qualified for the International Regulars. Next was the fight to be the Divisions champion. This was an honorable achievement as well.

The second draw made Han Xiao suspect that Frenzied Sword had touched Feidin beforehand as well. The two biggest clubs were due to face off against each other, Dynasty vs. Long Sky, whereas Rivervale had drawn the comparatively weaker Thunder Storm.

Frenzied Sword had only started to lead a team this season. Originally, team Rivervale was just a second-tier or even third-tier team, yet they qualified for the International Regulars. They were definitely a dark horse and attracted a lot of attention.

As a Mechanical Pugilist, Frenzied Sword's style was diverse, mature, and steady. He was much more famous compared to the previous season. He had started to make a name for himself in the pro scene.

Due to Han Xiao, Frenzied Sword had chosen a different class from his previous life. However, based on his current situation, his pro career was much smoother.

Chapter 649: Group Taunt

After a few days, the result of the second round of the Division Finals was decided. Dynasty defeated Long Sky steadily, and Rivervale barely beat Thunder Storm. Dynasty met Rivervale in the last round for the championship.

Frenzied Sword could not carry on his luck from before; their raw skill difference was too vast, and he could not lead Rivervale to victory. In the end, they finished first runners-up, and Dynasty were once again the Divisions champions.

King Admiral had made the announcement before the competition started that they would finish both Divisions champions and International champions. They had already achieved one of them. Dynasty continued to attract more attention as time went on; countless players hoped that Dynasty could really live up to their words.

To Frenzied Sword, getting the first runner-up the first time he led a team was satisfying enough. His team still had a lot of room to improve and practice their teamwork. Rivervale was certainly the dark horse of this season, and they obtained a lot of new fans.

Long Sky defeated Thunder Storm and got the Divisions second runner-up. If not because they had met Dynasty in the second round, Hao Tian's team would have been the first runners-up of the Divisions.

The results of the various divisions were decided, and the Divisions ended. There were more than ten days to rest before the International Regulars.

There were no more matches in the various divisions. The Internationals could not be viewed at the scene and only watched on the broadcast. Hence, the players did not remain on the planets used for the Divisions and went to do their own stuff while paying close attention to the forums.

Due to the Divisions, countless players did not do any mission during this time. Only more than a hundred thousand mercenaries in the Black Star Army and very few players were still taking on missions. However, although the business was neglected, not only did Han Xiao not make a loss, but he made a humongous amount of profit instead.

Most of the Ability Potions were sold. The business of selling machines and repairing equipment was also quite profitable. Han Xiao had made many tens of millions of Enas, almost doubling his bank account while emptying the wallets of many players.

With this money, he could purchase more fleets and recruit more freelance mercenaries. During the version update when he would not have the help of the close to a million players, he would have to rely on the money that he had earned from them to develop himself. Ten years was not a short period of time—the more money he could make before that, the merrier.

After the players left, Han Xiao returned to Base No.1 and sent out a message to recruit people from all around the Star Cluster. He started to prepare for the secret war that was about to break out between Klent and Purple Crystal. His current focus was to get more Favorability from Purple Crystal and obtain the Cutting-Edge Knowledge. Before he obtained the Cutting-Edge Knowledge from the Purple Crystal Civilization, he was not planning to personally take on any other missions.

However, Han Xiao received a mission that he could not reject—it was a message from the Sky Ring Army.

One mercenary team from Sky Ring encountered dangers that they could not resolve during their mission. The initial mission was an ordinary mission to deal with the rebellion on a planet. According to the employer's explanation, the strongest person among the enemies was just Grade B. However, a Calamity Grade enemy appeared. The Black Star Army was the nearest ally that Sky Ring had, so this team could only request emergency reinforcements from Black Star.

Black Star had become one of the top mercenary groups long ago, but he still maintained his partnership with large mercenary groups such as Sky Ring. Usually, Han Xiao would definitely help them himself since it would not be too much trouble, but this time, he did not want to go there himself. Hence, he called Lagi over.

Ever since he joined the Black Star Army, the previously unoccupied Magic Research Lab had become Lagi's territory. He spent every day there doing research and studying. Using his words, he was 'doing meaningless things to make time pass faster while waiting for himself to rot and grow old.'

However, despite being extremely pessimistic and negative, his raw skills were too high. He improved the magic aspect of the Black Star Army single-handedly. At the very least, a Grade A Mage's enchantment effect was far superior to a Grade B's. Han Xiao had already gotten Lagi to re-enchant his mechanical suits and weapons, which considerably increased their stats while adding many special effects.

Han Xiao planned to send Lagi to do this mission. No matter what, he was the only Calamity Grade officer, and he had to at least take on some responsibility.

With Lagi, the Black Star Army could deal with Calamity Grade missions even without Han Xiao. He did not have to do everything himself anymore.

Sylvia brought Lagi to Han Xiao's room, and Han Xiao cut to the chase. "I have a mission for you."

"I knew it." Lagi sighed. "Bad feelings often are proven to be right."

Han Xiao ignored him and explained, "One of Sky Ring's team requested reinforcements from us. The enemy is a Calamity Grade. Currently, in the army, you're the only one that can deal with a Calamity Grade other than myself. As the captain, it's not suitable for me to settle this kind of low priority matter. Hence, you will be going there to rescue them. This is your first mission. I believe in your strength. You can pick any spaceship from the hangar apart from mine. The information about the target and the coordinates have been sent to you."

"I have a question."

"What."

"Can I not go?"

"Take a guess."

Lagi tested the waters and asked, "If they are already all dead by the time I arrive, does that mean I don't have to do the mission anymore?"

Han Xiao squinted and said, "Are you thinking about taking a detour to purposely waste time?"

"I'm exposed..." Lagi had a bitter expression on his face.

Is this person even reliable at all? Veins popped out on Han Xiao's forehead. He sighed and said, "Quickly get going. I don't want to see your first mission end with a failure."

Lagi gave a long sigh. He looked up at the ceiling of the room at forty-five degrees and said, "Sigh, I'm probably going to be killed by the enemy. I never thought sacrificing myself in my first mission would be the end of my life. I want to write down my last words before leaving..."

"Quick—ly—go!"

Lagi left while sighing and shaking his head. Sylvia was trying so hard to hold back her laughter at the side that she was tearing up. Her cheeks were inflated, and she was pressing her mouth with her hands, letting out some suppressed laughter.

"Teacher, where did you dig this treasure out from?"

Han Xiao shot her a glare and said, "He's just a little pessimistic at most. At least he's useful and much stronger than you, yet you can still laugh? I told Reynold to supervise you. Have you been learning from him properly? Are you done with your homework?"

"Done long ago!" Sylvia's expression instantly collapsed. She snorted unhappily, swung her ponytail, and left angrily.

Han Xiao curled his lips.

There were many officers in the Black Star Army. In Han Xiao's eyes, the ones that had the potential to reach Grade A were only Herlous, Aroshia, Feidin, Sylvia, Harmon, Reynold, and Hila and Aurora, who were training under Ames. Reynold was currently the closest to Grade A, and Sylvia was the furthest.

Sylvia had achieved Grade A in his previous life, so Han Xiao always had high and strict requirements for her.

...

During the rest time, all the qualified teams from the various countries were announcing the status of their training every day.

Although Temple of Gods did not qualify, Li Ge was very smart—he volunteered for his team to help in the training for the top four teams in the Divisions, helping them in their conditioning before the Internationals. This got him some attention, and his reputation slowly recovered. The other strong teams saw this and did the same thing.

Coincidentally, in the eyes of the fans, this situation became the Chinese teams uniting due to their strong sense of collective honor. They had let go of their disagreements in the past and were helping their opponents, all so that the Chinese would become the world champions. Therefore, the Chinese players became even more passionate and excited.

Before the Internationals started, the reporters interviewed all the qualified teams. The teams from America, Sweden, Japan, and Korea all declared they would be the champions. Due to Dynasty's outstanding performance during the All-Stars match, the reporters mentioned Dynasty specifically and considered them candidates for the top spot. The reporters asked these teams if they had the confidence in beating Dynasty. All of them announced that they would defeat Dynasty with confidence.

The break quickly passed. The International Regulars that the audiences from all around the world were looking forward to arrived.

The thirty-six teams from nine divisions all entered the venue. The venue was an arena even bigger than the previous season. As usual, the first day was the opening ceremony and the drawing of lots to determine the groups.

There were still three groups—A, B, and C. The teams would fight every other team in the group once, and the top eight teams with the highest points would qualify for the International Finals.

Long Sky entered Group A, Dynasty and Rivervale entered Group B, and Thunder Storm entered Group C. The stronger and comparatively weaker teams were rather evenly spread out through the three groups, unlike the previous season where the skill differences between groups were enormous. This time, there was no 'weak group' or 'group of death'. This meant that there would be almost no luck involved—one could only enter the finals through actual skills.

In Han Xiao's previous life, China had only reached the top four in the second season. This time, both Dynasty and Long Sky had a chance of becoming the champion. Han Xiao was quite curious about what the Chinese teams could achieve this season under his influence.

The International Regulars officially commenced. The fans from the various countries cheered for their favorite teams passionately. It was boisterous and full of life.

When the competition arrived at the mid-stage, the situation started to get clearer. The spectators had a rough idea of which teams were stronger.

Dynasty maintained their momentum and stayed at the top, second was Sweden's Tomahawk, and America's Devil followed.

Long Sky was fifth. Hao Tian seemed to have been holding back during the Divisions and only went full out at the Internationals. They showed the skills of a champion worthy team.

Both Thunder Storm and Rivervale were in the upper half of the list and stayed competitive. The average strength of the Chinese teams was very high, so the Chinese fans were very surprised and excited.

To the Chinese players, the Internationals were going extremely well. Dynasty and Long Sky both had the ability to qualify, while Rivervale and Thunder Storm seemed to have a chance of entering the top eight.

However, in the second half of the competition, something controversial and upsetting happened.

In the Survival matches that involved four teams, Dynasty repeatedly faced the situation where the other teams cooperated to eliminate them first. They were unable to get any points from the Survival matches, which resulted in their top position to get shaky, even starting to show signs of being surpassed by Tomahawk and Devil.

Originally, it was almost certain that Dynasty would have the most points in the end, but now it seemed to be slipping away right through their fingers. The Chinese supporters were furious. Countless Chinese viewers strongly and blatantly expressed their rage and contempt toward the teams that worked together on the various forums.

Posting hateful online comments was a basic ability of the Chinese players. The Mandarin language is deep and has a history of close to 5,000 years. Every player had experienced countless bloody verbal battles. In this environment, not to blow one's own trumpet, but in terms of cursing and hateful comments, the Chinese were superior compared to all other countries.

The forums became another battlefield. The fans of the other teams wanted to protect their team's reputation and argued that since the Survival mode was a scrimmage, working together was a sensible, logical strategy.

However, to the Chinese players, logic was as useful as farts, not to mention they were the victims in this situation. Their merciless and relentless cursing and toxic comments defeated the enemies and forced them to retreat.

This nonsense cracked Han Xiao up. He loved to see his countrymen curse; it could always give him a full day of joy.

Actually, it was not unreasonable for the other teams to work together in Survival. They were not doing it because of Dynasty's results but because Dynasty was too strong. If they did not work together, Dynasty would most likely be the final winner.

Dynasty was not worried about qualifying with their current points, but the other teams had to fight for the top eight positions and needed those points. Hence, eliminating Dynasty first was indeed a sensible and reliable strategy.

This online argument affected the organizers, who told Dynasty to say a few words in order to end all this nonsense. However, not only did King Admiral's reply not extinguish the players' passion, it poured another gallon of gasoline onto the flames instead.

"No big deal, one who's not envied isn't talented. No matter how they work together to fight me, the only difference it will make is what ranking we will qualify with. When it comes to the finals, I will teach them the meaning of life one by one!"

King Admiral directly taunted everyone. The Chinese players were so exhilarated that they hoped the finals would start now so that they could watch Dynasty thrash every opponent.

Han Xiao got goosebumps.

To provoke all those people at once, Dynasty was really not afraid of dying at all!

However... it did make things much more interesting.

Chapter 650: Milestone

The top six places were practically solidified, and Dynasty as well as Long Sky had locked in their qualifications in the regulars.

In the second half of the International Regulars, although the Dynasty team had encountered a siege in the Survival battle, they maintained unparalleled momentum during the team and ring battles. They secured first place, not allowing any of the following teams to overtake them.

The competition for the seventh and eighth place was the fiercest. Because the gap between seventh to thirteenth was miniscule, with only the last few matches left, there were seven teams with the opportunity to qualify. Rivervale was one of them, and as for Thunder Storm, it was a pity that they could not. While Rainy Kim was beautiful, the value of esports did not lie in one's appearance. She could not support her team with her skills alone, so they missed out on the chance to qualify.

Frenzied Sword and Evil Sword became the Captain and Vice Captain respectively. With their potential stimulated after so many battles, their cooperation had become more tacit. The fans regarded them as the symbol of the Rivervale team, calling them 'Two swords combine as one'.

There was only one game left in the regular season. Rivervale was tenth, only a few points away from eighth. This last game was their last hope of qualifying.

The team in eighth place was Hydra from Japan. Surprisingly. Hydra's opponents for their last game was Long Sky, whereas Rivervale would face off against Team Kimchi from South Korea.

In one of the rooms within the Black Star Base No.1, the Rivervale members were called over by Frenzied Sword for a meeting, analyzing the situation.

Frenzied Sword knocked on the table with a serious tone. "Long Sky is ranked fourth whereas Kimchi is ranked sixth. Both are strong teams, and there is no possibility of getting an easy way out. If we want to fill the gap in points between us and Hydra, we need to cut a lot of points from Kimchi and have Hydra tie with Long Sky. Only then will we have a chance to qualify."

"It's too harsh! Hydra can be said to be evenly matched with Long Sky, but Kimchi is also a strong team. I'm not even sure if we can win." Evil Sword shook his head.

"In addition to scoring a victory in the team battle, there is still a way to score a lot of points." Frenzied Sword slowly spoke. "The duel battle allocates points based on the number of people who are inside, so if Evil and I go beyond our level and slaughter the other side, we'll be able to rake in a lot of points."

"It's true that if we do well in the duel, we'll be able to pull apart in terms of points lead," Evil Sword replied, "but... Kimchi cannot be looked down on. Even Dynasty does not dare claim that they can wreck Kimchi totally."

"This match is our only chance. We must score more points at all costs! I've already taken out all the Ability Potions in the warehouse, and we have about sixty-seven potions left. If we cannot get into the finals, there's no use in them. Thus, we'll just finish all these potions in this final match and try to get as many points as we can."

Everyone present felt their spirits being lifted up.

Evil Sword's eyes glowed. "Leader, are you going to use Black Star's Character Summon Card too?"

"That's right. As long as we can enter the finals, we'll have achieved our goal. There's no need to wait any longer." Frenzied Sword nodded in return.

"Then, we might just be able to pierce through Kimchi." An expression of joy appeared in Evil Sword's face.

Because there was enough inventory, Han Xiao did not use the Gene Extractor on himself, so the store did not have his Ability Potion. However, right before the Pro League, Frenzied Sword had completed a mission with a high rating and had drawn out a blank Character Summon Card through his random reward.

He had remembered that, during the First Pro League, he had utilized the Character Summon Card [Black Star's Advent] to completely crush his opponent. Without hesitation, he immediately used his blank Character Summon Card to generate Han Xiao's Character. This Character Summon Card became his ace in the hole.

At this sort of crucial match, Frenzied Sword decided that it was time to utilize the card.

...

In this final match, Rivervale had become the focal point for all China audiences. With Dynasty and Long Sky having qualified, if Rivervale could do the same, it would mean that for this year's International Finals, there would be three teams from the China region. What a proud matter that would be!

In the team battles between Rivervale and Kimchi, the two sides duked it out. However, Kimchi made every effort they could to create a seamless defense, and only by using an Ability Potion did Rivervale finally clinch a miserable victory, obtaining a meagre score.

Many of the China viewers were quite discouraged. With only this paltry score, they practically lost the chance to overtake Hydra.

Not many of the viewers were optimistic about the duels, as only Frenzied Sword and Evil Sword would be battling, whereas the rest of the team would be on the sidelines. Just based off individual strengths, Kimchi had two people who had gotten into the finals for the Singles battle. While Rivervale could win, they probably did not have much chance of obtaining more points.

However, the moment the duels began, Frenzied Sword gave the audience a pleasant surprise while giving the Kimchi team a huge shock.

The moment Frenzied Sword stepped onto the stage, he activated tens of Ability Potions in one go, immediately adding a long list of Buff Statuses to his property panel. His entire body glowed, looking like a warrior of legends.

The commentators had their spirits refreshed. "Oh, it seemed like Frenzied Sword and company are getting desperate, and now the pressure is on team Kimchi!"

Every professional team had their own ace, and the Ability Potions that Han Xiao sold were the aces of most Chinese teams, which had left a huge impression in the Pro League. It gave the other teams tremendous headaches. Due to the randomness of the Ability Potion's effects, they could not take any sort of measures against them.

However, the time effect for the Ability Potions was limited, and along with the numerous matches, every Chinese team was saving them; one used would be one less. After all, the finals would consist of five rounds, in which three wins were needed.

That being said, it seemed as though Frenzied Sword had thrown the situation of finals away, fighting as though his back was against a cliff. He unleashed a frightening combat capability, punching through two of the opponent's players.

Team Kimchi knew that there was a time limit to the Ability Potions and only sent out their normal members, dragging the time out to grind down Frenzied Sword's buffs.

"Team Kimchi has chosen the optimal delaying tactic. While Frenzied Sword has defeated two players, a majority of his Buffs have almost run out. Let's take a look at the next player Kimchi is sending out... oh! They've sent out their ace! It seems like they wish to take the chance to end Frenzied Sword's streak!"

The third pick from team Kimchi was their team's ace, which was also one of the players who had entered the International Singles. At this point, Frenzied Sword only had a little more than half of his HP remaining, as well as a third of his Mechanical suit's armor.

This situation was extremely unfavorable, and a majority of the Chinese players felt their hands slick with sweat as they began to panic.

At this point, Frenzied Sword took a deep breath before activating his only Black Star Character Summon Card.

A translucent figure of Han Xiao appeared behind Frenzied Sword, clad in black with an expressionless face. He had a hand placed on the head of Frenzied Sword.

"Alright, Frenzied Sword has activated yet another new ability. This is... wait a minute, did I see this scenario in the last Pro League?" As the commentator spoke, his eyes bulged open.

When the commentator finished describing the Buff, the spectators were all dumbfounded.

[Advanced Strengthened Life]: Taken from Character Summon Card—Han Xiao.

Increase Health based off the END attribute at the ratio 1:60.

In addition, +25% Resistance, and for every 40% decrease in Health, +10% All Attributes temporarily.

Time limit: 20 minutes.

"F*ck me, this... this is cheating!" The commentator could not help but curse.

The countless viewers were also shocked silly.

The extra Health added was more than his original total Health!

A few of them realized that Frenzied Sword had also utilized Black Star's Character Summon Card in the previous Pro League.

Black Star again!

Since this Buff came from the Character Summon Card, it meant that this was an ability belonging to Black Star himself. All this time, the Attributes of Black Star had remained a mystery to the players. The players only knew that Black Star was abnormally strong but did not know his specific capabilities.

But right now, Frenzied Sword's buff revealed the tip of the iceberg of Black Star. However, just this tip was enough to shock the players into silence.

A Mechanic actually has a meat shield-like talent—doesn't that mean his Mechanic abilities will be even more perverted‽

Or is it that the Mechanic profession can actually awaken such a meat shield like talent?

With such a powerful endurance related ability, Frenzied Sword continued to battle on, steamrolling through another three players before being defeated. Evil Sword then burst out, taking down the final opponent with some difficulty.

The points for the duels were calculated based on the difference between the number of people lost on both sides. On Rivervale's side, only Frenzied Sword had lost, reducing the total number of losses from Kimchi by one. That was the total number of points awarded to Rivervale, and they clinched an overwhelming victory.

Cutting through five with himself, making a name for himself!

Rivervale obtained a large number of points, and them going to the finals would depend on whether Hydra was able to obtain points from Long Sky.

Long Sky did not disappoint the public. They did not hold back at all, beating Hydra up thoroughly and only allowing them to obtain a scarce number of points. Because Hao Tian was close to Frenzied Sword, along with everyone being part of China, he was willing to help Frenzied Sword with this favor.

After the battle, Long Sky obtained overwhelming praise, with the tag of 'Good Comrade of China' plastered on them.

Under the gazes of tens of thousands of players, the results of the eight final teams were released!

Dynasty ranked first, Long Sky ranked fourth, and Rivervale managed to squeeze in and knocked Hydra out of the top eight by two points!

Frenzied Sword's gamble had paid off!

Out of the four Chinese teams, three had made it into the finals. Only China had this sort of result, and the players from the region felt their blood boil as excitement filled their hearts.

Being able to qualify was a surprise, and squeezing out the Japanese team made it all the more gratifying. In this Pro League, none of the Japanese teams were able to get into the finals, and they made a hubbub of noise on the forums.

Han Xiao was also quite surprised by this result. He knew that the standard of the Chinese teams would be better than in the past, but he did not expect it to be so good!

To have three out of the eight slots for the finals, only America had achieved such a result in his previous life. This achievement was also only ever done once, but to think that China had achieved this in the second Pro League!

The players cheered on the forums, but no one foresaw that this was a milestone enough to be carved into the annals of Galaxy's history!

Han Xiao knew that even after many years, even in the future Versions, there would still be people who would continue to talk about China's brilliant achievements in this season.

In the finals, they were to fight based off their rankings. The first placed Dynasty would thus be pitted against the eighth placing Rivervale. The players felt this internal rivalry to be a pity, but this was how the rules of the competition went, and they had no way to change it.

"Frenzied Sword's luck has come to an end. However, to be able to reach the finals is a result to be proud of. For a new battle team, that's quite the accomplishment." Han Xiao was quite satisfied. The Chinese teams had performed well, and this was a form of promotion for the Black Star Army.

As for Long Sky in fourth place, they faced Kimchi, who were fifth. The Chinese players did not wish to see an internal battle and thus turned their sights toward the fight with the Korean team.

However, Han Xiao was not interested in the finals. He merely threw a mark on Lagi, continuing to observe his performance.

Although Lagi had mentioned that he would take a detour, reality proved otherwise. He had rushed straight to the mission site and had already reached the place where the Sky Ring Mercenaries had requested assistance.

Chapter 651: The End of Season Two

In the Fawn Star System, Planet Capelotti was ruled by the Vinstark Civilization, a planet level government under the Black Raven Civilization. The Vinstark race had feathered wings and looked like humans born with the ability to fly. The buildings on Planet Capelotti were tall and resembled trees. They had platforms outside the buildings like branches.

Vinstark was peaceful and laid back. They were satisfied with being ruled over by the Black Raven Civilization. Thus, they were frequently troubled by those with different views on this matter and extreme nationalists. Rebel organizations constantly appeared. There were many other examples similar to this across the entire universe.

A Sky Ring Army team had accepted a request to eliminate a rebel organization called 'Bullseye'.

The leader of this team was [Ice Sorcerer] Goa, a Three-Ring Level officer, Grade B Super, who had once fought alongside Black Star on Floating Dragon. She had always worked near the Fawn Star System.

According to Vinstark's data, the strongest person in Bullseye was a Grade B. This was originally just a usual combat mission. However, Goa did not expect that Bullseye would have hidden a Grade A. Plus, this Grade A was not someone that no one had heard about; he was a Vinstark who had been banished many years ago. His name was Getorald.

Now that he was at Calamity Grade, he wanted to come back and overthrow Vinstark's rule. Not only was he the real boss of Bullseye, he was also the mastermind behind many other rebel organizations. He was basically behind all of Planet Capelotti rebels.

In a wasteland somewhere, a small aircraft was escaping quickly. Behind it were hundreds of aircrafts.

"Bullseye has found us again. We have been hiding and escaping for so long that we don't have much fuel left. Captain, what should we do?"

In the cockpit, the survivors of the Sky Ring team were piloting the aircraft in panic.

"Keep running. I have requested reinforcements from the Black Star Army. They will definitely come. We have to hang on until they arrive."

Goa clenched her teeth. Her magic robe was covered in bloodstains and dust. After so many days of running, she was in a very bad state and extremely exhausted.

She had only fought with Getorald once and was absolutely crushed. She could not cross that enormous gap between Grade B and Grade A. If not for sheer lucky, her team would have been wiped out.

Their fuel quickly burned up. They started to decelerate, and the enemies were catching up. All the Sky Ring mercenaries were on edge, and Goa grabbed tightly onto her staff uncontrollably.

This time, a communication request suddenly popped up on the screen. Lagi's despondent face appeared.

"Hello, the reinforcements you ordered have arrived. Anyone still alive? If not, I'll be leaving."

The people were overjoyed, and Goa quickly replied. "We're still alive. We are currently in danger and require help urgently. The coordinates are..."

After she gave the coordinates, Lagi hung up the communication. They heaved sighs of relief and smiles appeared on their faces.

"Black Star's reinforcements have finally arrived!"

"Great! We're saved."

Suddenly, Goa realized a problem. "Wait a minute, I told them that there's a Calamity Grade among the enemies. Why was the person earlier not Black Star? Did he not come personally?"

Their expressions changed slightly. They all knew the Black Star Army quite well and were aware that only Black Star was a Calamity Grade. It seemed that they had not heard about the Black Star Army having another Grade A.

Goa could not help but worry—she only hoped that the reinforcements were reliable.

Suddenly, everyone's hair stood on end. An enormous Shockwave Blast rocketed toward them and landed on their aircraft.

Boom!

The aircraft exploded into pieces. A spherical magic shield was blasted away, bouncing on the ground a few times before stopping. The magic shield disappeared, exposing Goa and the others in it. The staff in Goa's hands was shining—she had protected all her team members at the last second. She was drained and gasping for air.

This time, hundreds of enemy aircraft caught up and surrounded them.

From the direction where the Shockwave Blast came from, a winged man flew there at high speed and stopped above them. His eagle-like eyes looked down on Goa and the others, sharp as a knife. This bird was indeed the Grade A Super of the rebel organization, Getorald.

"Humph, Sky Ring's people. I hate mercenaries the most. Blame it on yourselves for sticking your nose in something that has nothing to do with you. You deserve to die."

Getorald flapped his wings. A ball of dense, pale-gold Pugilist energy gathered on his hand. The strong sense of danger made Goa and the others freeze in fear.

Hu!

Just as Getorald was about to land the killing blow, a spaceship dashed through the clouds and descended from above. He turned around and looked at it.

The spaceship stopped outside the encirclement. The hatch opened, and Lagi slowly floated out. Seeing the danger that Goa and the others were in, his expression turned bitter.

"I'm early..."

Getorald frowned and asked, "Who are you?"

Before Lagi could open his mouth, Goa replied, "You're done for. He's our backup, the Black Star Army's ... Er, what's your name?"

Goa only just remembered that she did not even know his name.

Lagi sighed. "If you ask my name again, I'm going to leave."

"Black Star's man‽" Getorald heard the conversation between the two of them, and his pupils uncontrollably constricted.

He was not afraid of the Sky Ring Army because Sky Ring's headquarters were very far from there. However, the Gavin Star System was right beside the Fawn Star System. He feared the Black Star Army and realized that he was in a pickle.

Even Getorald had heard of Black Star. Black Star's position in the Colton Star Cluster was way higher than his.

Alarmed, Getorald started to think of a solution. "The Black Star Army has interfered, so my plan can't go on. I can only kill this Black Star mercenary before leaving the Colton Star Cluster to wait for things to settle. If I continue to stay here, the Black Star Army will send tons of troops to deal with me sooner or later. Luckily, only one member of the Black Star Army came this time. If I kill him and Sky Ring's people, I will be able to conceal what happened here for a short time to give me time to escape."

Getorald had made the decision. He loudly ordered, "Everyone fire! Kill these Sky Ring mercenaries!"

The faces of Goa and the others changed drastically as they hastily defended themselves. They were in an extremely bad state. As long as they were continuously fired upon, they would end up either dead or heavily injured.

The cannons of all the aircrafts lit up and were about to fire.

Getorald rushed toward Lagi, turning into a meteor covered in flames—he immediately used his full strength.

At this instant, Lagi sighed. A very old and simple staff appeared in his hands out of nowhere. Lagi then lightly tapped the air with it.

"Spacetime Secret Spell—the Seventh Dimension."

Hum!

An invisible shield rapidly expanded and wrapped around everyone present. At this instant, every movement in the shield stopped as if the spacetime was frozen. The expression on everyone's face was fixed.

However, everyone's ability to think remained. They could clearly experience the feeling of being completely unable to move, but they could not control their bodies. Even Getorald was stationary in midair.

The Great Mechanic Han, who was spying, almost spat out the snacks in his mouth.

Isn't this ZA WARUDO[1]‽

The spacetime magic was the most difficult magic style to master. Plus, it was very dangerous. When spellcasters studied it, one slight moment of carelessness might cause them to die without even leaving a corpse behind. It required extremely high talent.

Not everyone could become the targets of Albert and those people. Lagi was not a member of any large organization—he was alone. Hence, there was only one reason that Lagi was a target.

His strength!

In this spacetime territory, Lagi was the only one that could move around freely. He cast spells continuously and destroyed all the aircrafts. This time, Getorald finally escaped the spell. Without saying a word, he turned around and fled.

His confidence was completely shattered by Lagi's one spell.

Lagi did not chase him. The mission was to rescue the Sky Ring mercenaries; he did not want to waste his energy chasing someone of the same grade. He floated toward Goa and the others, sighed, and said, "Get on my ship and let's get out of here."

Goa quickly nodded with respect. She could not help but ask, "Are you a new officer of the Black Star Army? I've never heard your name before."

"It's best to never hear it." Lagi's expression became more bitter.

The other Sky Ring mercenaries exchanged looks of shock. The Black Star Army finally had the first Calamity Grade officer, and he was so strong. Black Star did not have to carry everything on his shoulders anymore. They had a feeling that their Sky Ring Army was being surpassed by the Black Star Army.

Goa had a very complicated feeling. She still remembered a few years prior, when Black Star was just a small mercenary group. As a team captain of Sky Ring, their strength had been on par while she had the support of Sky Ring, so her position was higher than Black Star's.

Now, however, she was still a team captain in Sky Ring, but Black Star had become someone very important in the Colton Star Cluster and rather famous even in the entire Shattered Star Ring. The difference in strength and position between the two of them had completely changed.

With Black Star as someone to compare herself to, Goa felt as if she had been standing in the same place throughout the years and felt discouraged.

At this time, on the other side of the Observer's Mark, Han Xiao's eyes were sparkling brightly. His fingers rubbed his stubble, and he could not help but smile.

"Looks like I've found a treasure..."

A few days later, the second season finally came to an end.

The eight teams in the finals had attracted the most attention from the start of the competition. All the fans were cheering and rooting for their teams.

In the first round, Dynasty defeated Rivervale, entering the semi-final, while Rivervale stopped at the top eight. This result was no surprise for almost everyone.

Long Sky defeated Kimchi 3:1, eliminating Kimchi and entering the semi-finals.

Two Chinese had entered the semi-finals, and the Chinese fans could not help but wish that the final would be between two Chinese teams.

Sadly, the results of the draw of the second round placed Dynasty against Long Sky and Devil against Tomahawk.

The Chinese players felt it was very unfortunate for Dynasty. After entering the finals, Dynasty had gone up against a Chinese team in both the first and the second round.

The second round was very intense. The peak was right ahead—neither Dynasty nor Long Sky would hold back. Many viewers were saddened by their bloody battles.

Before the match, many people thought that Dynasty had a higher chance of winning. However, the result was unexpected. Under Hao Tian's lead, Long Sky showed extreme toughness and barely defeated Dynasty at 3:2, entering the finals.

Dynasty stopped at the top four and could only compete for second runner-up.

After the match, many reporters interviewed team Dynasty, and King Admiral had nothing to regret.

"We spent too much energy before the match. Hao Tian is my old rival. He really fought amazingly this time. I hope they can bring the championship trophy back for China. Brother, you won our match, so you've got to win this. Viewers, scold and swear at them as much as you can so that they don't dare lose."

A reporter with ulterior motives mentioned King Admiral's words during the Regulars, wanting to give him a hard time. However, King Admiral did not mind it at all.

"I originally wanted to educate the teams of the other countries, but in the end, I was educated by my countrymen. Never mind, I lost to one of us anyway. Hao Tian, you've got to become the champions. At least using the excuse of us losing to the champions will not get me into so much trouble."

All the reporters laughed, even the one that asked the question.

Very soon, it was Second Prince's turn to be interviewed. His comments were the usual. "It's absolutely the captain's fault that we lost. This means that we need to have someone else as the captain. There's no need to consider anyone else for that other than me. It's time for King Admiral to retire. He's already a middle-aged man—why the hell is he even still playing games?"

The interview of Dynasty was very joyful and slightly brushed off the remorse of the Chinese players. All the pressure and hope was on Long Sky.

Originally, Dynasty was the team that had the highest chance of becoming the champions. Now that Long Sky had defeated them, if they did not become the champions in the end...

However, not only was Hao Tian not panicking, his morale was very high instead.

Ever since the start of this competition, Dynasty had been the center of attention. He and Long Sky, however, had been quietly saving their energy like sharpening a sword.

In the finals, this sword unsheathed at last!

The passion and energy of everyone in Long Sky erupted all at once. They had the confidence to slash through everything before them!

Their opponents were the American team, Devil, who had defeated Sweden's Tomahawk and entered the finals.

Devil was the second favorite of the competition right after Dynasty. They were the last obstacle between China and the world champion!

Tens of millions of players across the nine divisions were watching the final. This popularity had never been seen before.

Even Han Xiao put down what he had on his hands and watched the finals from the start to the end.

Watching the intense battle between the two teams, his emotions were fluctuating with the situation of the battle. For an instant, it was like he had returned to the younger times when he was cheering at the top of his lungs for the Chinese teams, only to end up disappointed.

In the end, the score was 3:2.

The last Devil player collapsed in the ring.

Devil had fallen.

Long Sky was still standing.

The final victory belonged to Long Sky, to China!

"World champions!"

The Chinese players were madly exhilarated.

Even in his room in Base No. 1, Han Xiao could hear the cheering outside his windows!

[1] This is a reference to Jojo's Bizarre Adventure. "ZA WARUDO!" (also known as The World) is a phrase that is used by Dio when activating his power, which is time stopping. Back

Chapter 652: Version Update, the Start of Ten Years

The forums became a sea full of joy. The Chinese players were filled with excitement.

After Long Sky became the champions, Dynasty defeated Tomahawk and were placed third.

In the top eight teams, three of them were Chinese teams, one was the champion, and one was the second runner up. This astonishing achievement made many proud.

Long Sky received the most praising. Hao Tian had proven his skills and earned himself a ton of fans. The fame of his teammates, Sleepy Winter and Twinkle Fried Rice, grew enormously too. Even the Dynasty fans were happy for them from the bottom of their hearts.

Some thought that what had happened to Dynasty was regretful—if they did not face Rivervale and Long Sky consecutively, both the champion and the first runner-up teams might have been Chinese teams.

Due to the outstanding performances of the teams that they admired, countless players were praising how exciting this season was nonstop. After watching the entire season, they discovered one phenomenon.

During the finals, the Chinese teams did not lose even once to a team from another country!

Hence, some people found new words to praise their teams.

"The only ones that can beat us are ourselves!"

Han Xiao did watch the events after the match such as the award ceremony, the analytics of the season, and so on. Seeing that Long Sky were the winners, he had a rough guess about the future situation.

The Chinese teams had achieved extraordinary results in this season, and this would have a long-term effect. He knew his countrymen well. No matter what competition it was, as long as a fellow countryman was the champion, it would definitely pique their interest. Hence, there would be many new Chinese players in the next version, far more than in his previous life.

The Shattered Star Ring division, where the champions were from, was the headquarters of the various Chinese clubs. Therefore, many new Chinese players would choose to be born in the novice planets in the Shattered Star Ring. These freshies would become the new blood of the Black Star Army in the next version!

The current player count was far from the peak. The amazing results obtained by the Chinese teams would also affect Han Xiao very positively—good results meant more newcomers for the Black Star Army, which also meant that the quantity and quality of his leeks would be increased.

In this season, the Chinese teams had used various Black Star series mechanical devices. These were basically advertisements for the Black Star Army. Similar to how the American teams chose Planet Winterfrost to showcase the advantages of the Demon Race so that many players would feel that Demons were very strong, the Chinese teams' performance made many feel that the Black Star Army was very strong. The machines used by the Chinese teams brought Han Xiao quite a lot of attention.

...

Season two of the Galaxy Pro League had ended, but its popularity lasted for a long time afterward. However, after most of the players had their fill of fun, they finally focused on other issues.

The end of the Pro League meant that Version 2.0 was about to end as well.

Speculation concerning the storyline of the next season became a hot topic on the forums once again.

In the Shattered Star Ring, Bun-Hit-Dog's video was mentioned, the one that consisted of Han Xiao's conversation with Frenzied Sword and the others. The video hinted that the next version would be related to the Crimson Dynasty and sparked a lot of discussion.

"What could the Crimson Dynasty's goal in the Shattered Star Ring be?"

"Who knows? Anyway, in the next version, we will definitely be more involved in the fight between the organizations in the galaxy."

"Maybe it's the same as the start of Version 2.0, having to face a huge disaster as soon as we log in. I'm guessing that the Crimson Dynasty is the final boss."

"I'm not really interested in the storyline. All I'm interested in is what will happen to our Black Star Army. After the last version update, Black Star became the faction that guided us into the universe. I wonder how the Black Star Army will change after this update."

"I hope it won't disappear. We farmed so many Contribution Points for so long. If the Black Star Army is gone, it will all have been for nothing."

Due to past experiences, many players were curious about what the Black Star Army would become in Version 3.0.

The Chinese players basically looked at the Black Star Army as their main faction. Furthermore, it was one of the biggest reasons that the Chinese teams were able to achieve such results in the Pro League. Therefore, this issue received a lot of attention.

Han Xiao had been keeping an eye on the forums too, but even he could not give a clear answer to this question.

"The new version is about to arrive. This time, the gap is ten years..."

Han Xiao shook his head. Under the Crimson Tide, this would be a very tough ten years. Klent's secret war and the third round of [Prey]... there would be all kinds of danger.

In his previous life, when Version 3.0 started, the secret war between Klent and Purple Crystal was at its climax. That was when the players came into play. This meant that the secret war might go on during the entire time before the version updates.

The Black Star Army would spend the next ten years in battles. There would be both risks and opportunities.

When the players returned after ten years, Han Xiao did not know what would have become of the Black Star Army.

There would be many alliances forming in the next version. They would be the hidden competitors in recruiting the players. In Version 3.0, the Black Star Army would no longer be the 'guiding faction'. Han Xiao had been wondering how to make use of the next ten years to increase the attractiveness of the Black Star Army.

The current players had spent a lot of time and energy on the Black Star Army throughout the version, so they would not change factions easily. Keeping the old players was not an issue as long as Han Xiao operated the Black Star Army properly during the version update.

What he needed to go for was the new players in Version 3.0. Other than the effect brought by the Pro League, the Black Star Army had to have at least the same amount of resources as the other alliance factions.

The players' achievements during Version 2.0 and the profit made from the players were the only assets that Han Xiao had to get through the following ten years.

The Pro League was the last opportunity to harvest leeks for Version 2.0. Near the end of the version, the players would bank their fortune and wait for the next version.

As soon as Version 3.0 arrived, the Black Star Army would rocket in terms of strength!

After all, the players in Version 3.0 would be able to level up to Grade B.

Millions of Grade C Supers and millions of Grade B Supers were completely different.

Beep beep!

This time, the communicator suddenly vibrated.

"You have a new message, hum..."

Han Xiao took out the communicator. It was a message from Ralph, telling him to go to the mother planet of the Purple Crystal Civilization. Section Zero had confirmed all the organization members and summoned the leader of all those organizations to officially announce the creation of Section Zero.

"This organization is formed at last."

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

...

The Blacklight Stealth stopped at the port of the Section Zero headquarters, which was on the Curved Blade garrison satellite orbiting the Purple Crystal Civilization mother planet. Han Xiao followed Dodder, the foreign affairs emissary, into the garrison satellite and came to the hall.

At this time, more than two hundred rather well-known people were gathered there. The moment that Han Xiao walked in, those people all turned and looked over with different expressions on their faces.

Before Section Zero was officially formed, most of the people there did not know who the other members were. Due to what had happened with Black Star a few months ago, many had guessed that Black Star had joined Section Zero, so not many of them were surprised.

"Not bad, Black Star is a reliable comrade."

Many had the same thought in their mind and nodded at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao saw some familiar faces in the crowd, including chest hair monster Jayne and do-nothing Gadeli, who had once fought alongside him, and some organizations that had followed him to eliminate Albert's gang.

Among them, the ones that had the biggest organizations were the Arc Light Organization leader from the Severide Star System, the Hero Group leader from the Skywalker Star System, and the New Phylen Rebels leader from the Rain Star System. Other than those, there were also many other organizations that were much bigger than Han Xiao's. His Black Star Army was above average.

Ralph stood before the crowd. His face was serious, and his tone was formal.

"Everyone is here. As you all know, the purpose of Section Zero is to protect the Colton Star Cluster and guard against the Klent Kingdom's invasion. The enemy you're about to face is the Tyrant's Bloodshed Land. Due to reasons that all of you know, we and Klent can't use our official armies. The Colton Star Cluster's safety is in your hands.

"You will all become important allies of one another, cooperate with each other, fight alongside each other, and guard against the Bloodshed Land's invasion together.

"I hereby announce the official creation of Section Zero!"

This time, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

New Faction [Section Zero] activated!

Favorability: 1,500/3,000

Current Relationship: Friendly

...

In the hall of Black Star Base No.1, many players had gathered.

It was the day of the version upgrade, and the update would start in less than two hours. Many players gathered in different bases before logging off. The players were now experienced with this and knew that the best choice was to wait in a stronghold in groups before the update. Base No.1 had the most players.

This was because Long Sky, Dynasty, and Rivervale had all decided to log off there. Many players had gone to look at those players.

After Hao Tian was done speaking to the passionate fans, he bade farewell to King Admiral and Frenzied Sword.

"I'm logging off."

King Admiral smiled and said, "Little Hao, let's have dinner in a few days. Call Fried Eggplants With Fish and the others too."

"Sure." Hao Tian nodded.

Li Ge heard and asked, "Hey, what about me?"

"If you're that shameless, we welcome you to come without an invitation." Second Prince curled his lips.

"It's decided then, see you there," Li Ge said in a serious tone.

Frenzied Sword was stunned. He remembered Li Ge to be very proud, what happened?

Compared to the Temple of Gods, which did not achieve any notable results in two consecutive seasons, Long Sky had finished top four and champions, while Dynasty was second and third. Therefore, Li Ge could not maintain the confidence to be proud anymore. He did not want the Temple of Gods to be forgotten, so he could only put away his pride and hang out with these people. That way, he could at least benefit from all the attention that they were receiving.

"By the way, Sword, bring your team over for the dinner too. It's on me." Hao Tian suddenly recalled his buddy Frenzied Sword.

Frenzied Sword was stunned for a moment, then overjoyed. He had been dreaming of becoming a god tier player, and now, he finally felt that he was one foot into Hao Tian and the others' circle.

Twinkle Fried Rice's eyes sparkled. "Since so many people are coming, we might as well invite Thunder Storm, Fanatics, Nine Gates, and all those teams as well. We should all celebrate for a few days."

Li Ge immediately supported this idea. All the teams gathering together would definitely be huge news. He would benefit from it, too.

Hao Tian thought about it and said, "Okay. Anyway, we did not celebrate enough after winning the championship. Let's enjoy ourselves during the holidays."

They chatted for a while happily and logged off one after another. The players around also turned into white lights and disappeared.

Very soon, the hall became empty.

At the same time, Han Xiao, who was on rushing back, saw a notification on his interface.

Version 2.0 Update Activated!

Saving data... Save complete!

Player forums closed.

Update Duration: Unknown. Please wait patiently.

"And so it begins..."

Inside the Blacklight Stealth cockpit, Han Xiao had a melancholic expression on his face.

Ten years...

...

A spaceship left the desolate region, and the countless stars ahead were reflected on the porthole.

Stephanie looked at the bright stars ahead and smiled.

"We're finally here, the Shattered Star Ring."

Chapter 653: Ten Year Plan

"With all the players disappearing, the size of the Black Star Army will be reduced considerably, and there is a need to make new plans."

Han Xiao began to carefully think about how he should resolve this matter.

He was still less than thirty years old, and when Version 3.0 was released, he would be almost forty.

Han Xiao did not worry about his age. He was a Grade A Super, after all, and had injected himself with longevity medicine before. Living two to three hundred years should not be an issue at all. In ten years, his appearance would still be the same, young and suave.

Han Xiao already had a brief outline for the development of the Black Star Army over the next ten years.

"My main focus should be to accumulate strength. Without the players to bring me a long stream of benefits, the main focus of these ten years should be to convert all the benefits that the player's brought me in Version 2.0."

His assets from Version 2.0 included the twenty-three bases in the Garton Star System, almost two thousand battleships and over seventeen million Enas in savings. Furthermore, the numerous employment missions that the players had completed had also greatly increased the fame of the Black Star Army.

NPC mercenaries were different from players. Every death meant that he would have one fewer mercenary. While hiring freelance mercenaries was a solution, grooming fresh blood for his Black Star Army was more important. Han Xiao decided to increase the investment in the training camps so that he could ensure a constant flow of new mercenaries and also reduce his costs.

Apart from the mercenaries at the bottom rung, Han Xiao also needed to groom the officers at the top. With the current level of the Black Star Army, Grade B Supers were no longer rare and could only be considered the middle rung. They truly lacked Grade A Supers at the very top. Currently, the only two Grade A Supers were Han Xiao and Lagi.

"Hmm, I need to try and recruit new Grade A Supers while grooming those with potential such as Herlous, Feidin, and Reynold. I wonder how many Grade A Supers I will be able to groom over the next ten years."

Han Xiao stroked his chin. In his previous life, Sylvia had already been a Grade A Super in Version 3.0. These ten years should be Sylvia's growth spurt, and Han Xiao needed to stimulate her growth further so that she could transform from a capable female secretary into a competent helper.

However, accumulating their strength did not mean that they would have to remain low profile. The secret war started by Klent would be the largest conflict on the outside, and there would be opportunities hidden within risks. Han Xiao would naturally participate in the war.

In order to obtain Cutting-Edge Knowledge, Han Xiao had joined Section Zero to farm favorability points with Purple Crystal. This was one of the most secure paths. Cutting-Edge Knowledge was something that he could not lack. Even if it was not a Class Advancement requirement, Han Xiao would still want to obtain it.

At the same time, he was killing two birds with one stone. As long as he could render huge merits in the secret war, he would have the right to become a long-term partner of a Star Cluster civilization like the Bloodshed Land. This would then be the stimulus to restructure the Black Star Army and allow the Black Star Army to take another step forward in the Colton Star Cluster.

With the accumulation of resources from Version 2.0 and the support that Purple Crystal gave to Section Zero, Han Xiao would be able to accumulate his strength. If he wanted to receive more resources from Purple Crystal, he would have to achieve a higher status in Section Zero and render large merits.

All the first-rate organizations such as Arc Light, Hero Group, and New Phylen were both his reliable allies and his competitors. They were extremely large organizations that received greater support and resources. If Han Xiao wanted to receive more resources, he would have to prove his superiority.

"Currently, both parties have not begun to fight, and there is still some time to prepare before the war. Apart from the development of the organization, my own strength will also have to take another step forward. The amount of experience that I have accumulated should be enough to bring me up to level two hundred."

The strength of his organization was only an external force; his own personal strength was the most important.

Ten years was enough for Han Xiao to convert all of his experience points into combat strength. As for whether or not he would be able to reach beyond Grade A, Han Xiao was not too sure either. He did not know the level requirement for beyond Grade A.

If he used the gap between Grade B and Grade A as a reference as well as the increase in his strength as he leveled up, Han Xiao estimated that he would need to be at least level 240 before reaching beyond Grade A.

The accumulated experience might not be able to take him to beyond Grade A, but Grade A+ was definite.

As long as he could find a few more powerful skills and talent, he should be able to defeat the majority of Grade A Supers.

"I am currently at level 170, and the Class Advancement Mission is delaying me. If I want to obtain Cutting-Edge Knowledge to complete my Class Advancement, I need to farm 6,000 favorability points with Purple Crystal and improve my relationship with Purple Crystal to 'Reverence'."

After deciding on the general direction to take, Han Xiao returned to his base and began issuing orders.

First, he shrank back the range of operations. Without the presence of the players, the efficiency of the Black Star Army would be greatly reduced.

At the same time, Han Xiao took out a large amount of funds to purchase raw materials and spare parts. He got the various military factories to construct small sized spaceships. The logistics department under Reynold's lead was no longer the same as before, and its scale was many times greater. They could already construct their own spaceships. Although they were only capable of building small assault spaceships, the Black Star Army was still able to save a great deal of money. This was one of the preparations before war erupted.

Another sum of money was used to hire even more combatants. Currently, the Black Star Army had more than 100,000 registered mercenaries, and Han Xiao was prepared to increase this number by four to five times. Money was not an issue at all.

The other Black Star mercenaries had also noticed the disappearance of the players and were extremely puzzled by the matter. However, Han Xiao did not bother explaining anything to them. Even if they had a thousand different guesses, it would not be able to change the present situation.

While a portion of the upper echelons who knew about the Inhumans were surprised, they were not too shocked. They were only worried about the Black Star Army after the disappearance of the Inhumans.

For this, Han Xiao had specially summoned all his high ranked officers.

In the room, all the officers of the Black Star Army streamed in.

Han Xiao got straight to the point without beating about the bush. "The Inhumans have disappeared again, and we don't know when they will appear again. This isn't the first time that this has happened, and the Klent invasion may happen in the near future. We will be accepting the Purple Crystal's employment in the future and will participate in the war as a member of Section Zero. We need to make our preparations."

Everyone nodded with different looks on their faces.

"Lagi, you are the only other Calamity Grade Super apart from me. If the situation on the battlefield gets intense, we may need you to lead a force on your own," Han Xiao said.

"Sigh, war again. I have a premonition that I will be sacrificed this time," Lagi said with a bitter expression.

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

Right at that moment, Reynold suddenly interrupted.

"Your Excellency Black Star, he isn't the only Calamity Grade."

As everyone heard that, they all turned to look at Reynold.

Han Xiao's eyes lit up and asked, "Could it be that you..."

Reynold nodded, and a rare smile could be seen on his face, "Just a few days ago, I successfully stepped into the Calamity Grade, and I am now a Grade A Super. This is all thanks to your tutelage."

Han Xiao was overjoyed. With Reynold's stepping into Grade A, his Black Star Army would have a total of three Grade A Supers. This meant that the Black Star Army exceeded most Section Zero members.

This was truly good news!

Reynold had come under his wing a few years ago, and after learning for such a long time, he had finally advanced into the next grade. While Han Xiao was surprised, he was not too shocked. He had known that with Reynold's talent, it was only a matter of time before Reynold entered the Calamity Grade.

However, it was truly timely for Reynold to step into the Calamity Grade right before war broke out.

By the side, Herlous could not help but be slightly disappointed.

He was the first to follow Han Xiao, but his status was now being taken over by newcomers. However, it could not be helped since his strength was not sufficient. Becoming a Grade A Super was not something that would happen overnight, and he had not touched the door frame of Grade A yet.

After the Sunil incident, Herlous had sworn to follow Han Xiao for life and was frustrated that he could not provide more help to Han Xiao.

Everyone's reaction was different. The Volga brothers were as carefree as ever, Feidin smiled without saying a word, Sylvia clenched her fists and swore to work harder, and Aroshia was daydreaming by the side.

Han Xiao's gaze landed on Aroshia. The [Reboot] mission was currently in the second phase. He had managed to find most of her memory fragments through the players, and only a final location was lacking before the mission could be completed.

It was just that the final location was too deserted, so Han Xiao had not taken her to complete the second phase of the mission. He was not too eager to complete this mission because Risda had already revealed some information, suggesting that the final target of the [Reboot] mission would be to deal with Manison from the Mechanic Empire. Since Han Xiao knew that he would not be able to complete the mission any time soon, he was not in a rush.

He did not want to provoke a beyond Grade A Super for nothing with the other party being a member of the Ancient Ones.

Not just the Black Star Army, all the members of Section Zero were also preparing for war and hiring new members.

Ten days later, a piece of news shook the entire Shattered Star Ring.

Bloodshed Land had invaded the Colton Star Cluster with their army!

This meant that the secret war between Klent and Purple Crystal had finally erupted!

This was like a spark that caused the Crimson Tide to explode!

The conflict between the seen Star Cluster Civilizations escalated to the point they broke out in war. Many large organizations and secret groups within the Star Field also began fighting each other. The Shattered Star Ring was thrown into chaos with many factions being formed.

The most dangerous period had finally arrived!

All members of Section Zero received a notice from Purple Crystal that requested them to arrive at the battlefield.

When Han Xiao received the notice, a notification also popped up on his interface.

You have triggered Grade S faction mission [Secret War: Section Zero]!

Mission Introduction: The Klent Kingdom has invaded the Purple Crystal Civilization, and you have chosen to stand on the side of the Purple Crystal Civilization.

Mission Requirements: As a member of Section Zero, listen to orders and force all invaders out of the Colton Star Cluster.

At the end of the mission, your reward will be based on the rating of the mission.

Note: As a strategic mission, there are three ways to improve your rating.

Complete the strategic objective of the mission.

Kill or capture the troops of the opposing faction.

Complete the mission successfully.

This is one of the Main Storyline missions of Version 3.0. I have triggered this mission during the version upgrade period.

Han Xiao had already predicted that this would happen.

This was a Grade S Main Storyline Mission, and players could choose between Klent and Purple Crystal. He had already joined Section Zero, which was akin to choosing Purple Crystal.

In his previous life, Version 3.0 had been released when the secret war was at its peak. The players had only returned at that moment to choose which faction to join.

This Grade S mission had a pretty simple introduction on both sides. Regardless of the faction that won the war, the players on both sides would still be able to receive rewards from the mission. The only difference would be the rating received for the mission.

After a series of experiments by the players, there were a few ways to cause a fall in mission rating. First, disobey the orders of their faction. Second, betray the faction. Third, lose the war before the Universal Civilization intervened.

I triggered this mission at the start of the war, a full ten years ahead of time... Han Xiao frowned.

This meant that this mission would definitely take a long time to complete, and the secret war would last throughout the ten years of the version upgrading period.

On the other hand, it also meant that he would have more time to farm his mission rating.

I am afraid that the next ten years shall be spent in war. After resting for two to three years, I think that I have rested enough.

This would be completely different from the few short-term employment missions. This was a long-term war.

Han Xiao stood up and walked out of the room.

"Phillip, summon everyone to go with me to war."